marvluebke: th3dis1Ayy th3dis1Ayy th3dis1Ayy
Izimoney92100: hi hi hi
Iliftmymousealot: what up
hardtarget4: yo
boompowpoq: hey
saintmthw: whatre you eating
justdatobi: Hey
xdarkmaga: hey
0xsam: I’m hungry af
Izimoney92100: wadduuuuup, first time catching you online
asvp_sui: Hey
theGunrun: Howdy
mirceau: Sup Ice Tea Time
hannefuggi: Hi
xdarkmaga: what we doing today?
CasparBaIT: oy
fourhundredtwenty: hi
Fatmetheny: Yoooooooo
speeddrawing101: HELLO
marvluebke: :D
samtheprogram: samtheprogram subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 10 months!
on111: Pog
fourhundredtwenty: GunRun Clappy
bigduddas: yoyoyo
mirceau: Tea Time ?
epicmegusta12: oyoy
boompowpoq: remember to clean the burger with alcohol first
squiggly_nibba: Dman two days in a row it's a miracle
TheNakedFlame: Hell yeah
i_macuser_i: Hi @georgehotz
CasparBaIT: lol
jbnunn: jbnunn subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 4 months!
NonTrivial778: we need some sovit music
Aehoard: hey George! how are you?
CasparBaIT: <3
blasio115: no :)
beersnbits: you're the man George!
smurfd0: science :)
speeddrawing101: what are you eating?
TheNakedFlame: Consistent streamer PogChamp
bichid69: live stream boisssss
on111: i love watching your youtubevods to learn
prafaeltsantos: <3
phelipe3: dude, I usually watch you on 2x. You're so slow in real life!
icyvran: George have you used Wolfram Language?
Danilok100: we all gonna loose our jobs
RobinMalfait: Hah, I was just looking at your vid of yesterday!
jamesmaloney: You can still eat burgers if you get drunk in the meanwhile
0xsam: Pickles?
mirceau: I missed you George! More streaming 2020 and I’ll subscribe
schrammel: what we doing?
mehmetislicik: SeemsGood
erichtp: we live in a society
hardtarget4: Jebaited
WillGreen98: Heyo
lambdaman0f: im already subscribed :(
samtheprogram: i just moved to san diego, what's good food here post quarantine
Danilok100: capitalism will collapse
Iliftmymousealot: do you still have meat in california?
filipeoliveiraa: heyo
b2kemann: peter schiff was right
inshelootts: right now
aliman_21: hi
henistein: Hi george how are you doing? =D
bigduddas: monkaW
Kertoip007: 1st time watchin u live, cheers George
filipeoliveiraa: monkaS next month
inshelootts: Hello my little broder
dr_set: F society
er_ricotta: what are u doing?
hardtarget4: WFH for the foreseeable future FeelsGoodMan
on111: monkaS
bichid69: whats with the black background hotz, y u racist
inshelootts: ahhh
b2kemann: but washington post told me it was the flu
jordanoBC: what up bro !
anthraxvirus322: cmonBruh
bobda_builder11: what are we doinggg
ScrubLifeChoseMe: eyy
bichid69: its literally called SARS-COV-2 BRO
RobinMalfait: corona is the group; covid19 is the disease, sars-cov-2 is the virus
dr_set: They named corona because they didn't want to called SARS so people would not panic
er_ricotta: 1000 death/day in Italy :(
anthraxvirus322: @robinmalfait 5Head
aliman_21: @georgehotz what if they just decide to end the simulation?
nanodanger7: nanodanger7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 22 months, currently on a 22 month streak! 22
bigduddas: SCAMMM TRAIN
parviz_gc: hi
ScrubLifeChoseMe: @georgehotz what u munchin on?
sambukahot: Hello! You are a professional and this is a very cool motivation for development! thanks👍👍👍
guacDev: jorge!!!!
ido1m: inb4 "man who cracked iphone now cracks coronavirus"
bsx1123: 0.1 for flu is a bit low
fourhundredtwenty: what do you say to germanys death rate then?
BesterGester: https://www.worldometers.info/coronavirus/country/italy/ Look at closed cases
bradfox2: 9.9 not normally age distributed
nvda9: check out bing covid tracker.
dr_set: What about this guy from Stanford saying that we suck at testing and stats? https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/17/a-fiasco-in-the-making-as-the-coronavirus-pandemic-takes-hold-we-are-making-decisions-without-reliable-data/
jamesmaloney: Italy is full of old and oversized people, it's kind of normal
bradfox2: 9.x whatever
boompowpoq: @er_ricotta no mai piu di 500
mehi9h: ooo I missed the streams
robbsalm: cosa?
thecoldwar32: hey
mars4real: Pog
BoxerU: yo
bradfox2: Italy median age much higher than us
anguelov: anguelov subscribed at Tier 1.
vloood: my internet sucks, and i have webpass
robbsalm: i am italian ;) what are you going to do today @georgehotz
fourhundredtwenty: check out germanys death rate
squiggly_nibba: China is lying
icyvran: This is a really interesting topic for a stream
boompowpoq: @jamesmaloney you are talking without actually knowing what is true.
s4j0k5: check Serbia
bichid69: how did we erradicate SARS v1?
vloood: stream keeps cutting out
ISD_Schogol: "finished in china". have you considered that they simply stopped reporting to make themselves look better?
Max_kappa_keepo: Trusting china LUL
prafaeltsantos: Portugal!!!
drparse: if you're 20yo it's flu, if you're 70yo it's SARS
jbnunn: stream's good here @vloood
squiggly_nibba: @bichid69 we didnt it died out
tutnjarko: 99% of deaths in italy had other diseases
blackklopi: almost no cases in russia, iran, irak etc
ackxhpaez: It's a chinese biological weapon people!
aliman_21: irak lmao
er_ricotta: wait a few days and in Germany will be a mess too
SnadderG: Have you looked into the connection between smoking/high pollution and death rates?
mumubecks: Iran has high death rate
yourboibl: yourboibl subscribed with Twitch Prime.
blasio115: @blackklopi they just dont publish anything lol
Edelknecht: "More than 99% of Italy’s coronavirus fatalities were people who suffered from previous medical conditions, according to a study by the country’s national health authority." (Bloomberg article '99% of Those Who Died From Virus Had Other Illness, Italy Says')
bichid69: @squiggly_nibba why/how? I don't remember it being this big a deal
anthraxvirus322: 10iq chat
robbsalm: china's pollution is insane
blackklopi: @blasio115 could be
yourboibl: just got my comma ai sweatshirt and that shit is comfy as hell
nvda9: some countries hiding the actual information
ackxhpaez: I like those odds
n8tfly: Nice duuud
icyvran: Will be alive, not fine
Izimoney92100: WASH YOUR HANDS
Filiadelski: except if you have asthma like me, then god help you
mitsukomegumii: Take a look at the R factor for SARS vs COVID-19
ScrubLifeChoseMe: @georgehotz so if someone gave u 100 skittles and told u 10 could kill u, would u eat some of those skittles
Atlas03: dont eat bats
boompowpoq: healthy individuals under a certain age death rate is the statistic which would be meaningful
ScrubLifeChoseMe: -reddot
a_ato: age * 100
Max_kappa_keepo: Problem is that hospitals get filled up
CompestLive: Hello again
er_ricotta: George where do you live?
SHAVEYY_: mukbang!
mattdougherty22: thanks for streaming
reduf: I'm leaving after the eating stream Kappa
bichid69: Whats the difference between human and bat COVID?
matn1400: What's up
alphagainzzz: where is the burger from?
robbsalm: today a 34 yo healthy guy died with covid in rome
bradfox2: @boompowpoq right
nico_d0t: You're eating fries and my room stinks fries
CompestLive: What if the cheif had corona lmao
Atlas03: i had thai food today FeelsGoodMan
h3ku: There is an interesting article about the death rate calculated based on the cruise ship where everyone was tested, so it take into consideration asymptomatic caseshttps://www.statnews.com/2020/03/17/a-fiasco-in-the-making-as-the-coronavirus-pandemic-takes-hold-we-are-making-decisions-without-reliable-data/
icyvran: SeemsGood
nvda9: poor countries population gonna wipe out
vloood: Italy has ppl dying all cause cuz hospitals
hastingspb: @georgehotz where burger from?
grenaderaven: i watch on youtube normally, are those vids edited or raw stream
vloood: Up by a lot
dohtem213: George, fuk the burger and let's find cure for coronavirus. you can sell it to countries for billions
liamcaccetta: ahaha what the fuckis happening
smurfd0: this seemed like good papers https://www.reddit.com/r/Virology/comments/fgzuaf/eli5_what_is_the_difference_between_covid19_and/fkazfba/
wateroraqua: yo what are you doing
mattdougherty22: YT is raw
Krakken_TM: rip economy
b2kemann: for c in crisis: freedom -= 1
theonlymonkas: what yi
zgamer0123: Geo i'm from spain i can't enjoy the society
theonlymonkas: what you eating?
nico_d0t: running Comma Ai in cure finding
TheMixStar: so george is now going to analyze the virus? lol
xrealyy: vaccine incoming by geo
icyvran: https://www.wolframcloud.com/obj/examples/COVID19Gene
icyvran: https://datarepository.wolframcloud.com/resources/Genetic-Sequences-for-the-SARS-CoV-2-Coronavirus
wateroraqua: he's hacking coronavirus?
sulphur: what's your draobyek, and yes. I do expect a timeout.
luigifrcruz: SARS-CoV-2 can spread more easily because you can infect someone before you show symptoms. This doesn't happen with SARS v1.
saintmthw: corona ai
charlesz31415: shake shack?
johanoutdoors: monkaS
Spisepower: monkaS
Atlas03: monkaS
dorkmo: george touching every part of his face
SpaceGhost8: *cough* monkaS
64pillars: monkaW
Penguino138: Was that Corona couhg?
khiomtv: monkaS
anthraxvirus322: monkaS
Fulk33: 6000 / 30000 = 20% different
theonlymonkas: monkaS
mars4real: monkaW
TheMixStar: rip george
dohtem213: Geo did Trump contact you for vaccine?
khiomtv: CHAT xqcL_HF
boengels: boengels subscribed at Tier 1.
liranisme: why many years of experience you have?
nvda9: 2% fatality rate
alxhotel: What's cooking?
johanoutdoors: @georgehotz Why didn't you want to stream in 2020?
liranisme: how*
charlesz31415: covidAI
uduver: Hello, hello!
SHAVEYY_: I bet geo doesnt even know his ABC's :)
ScrubLifeChoseMe: LUL
nanodanger7: Choo Chooo HypeGriffin2
ISD_Schogol: *Not yet
boengels: pleasure to be here
Atlas03: LIES
h3ku: There is an interesting article about the death rate calculated based on the cruise ship where everyone was tested, so it take into consideration asymptomatic cases https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/17/a-fiasco-in-the-making-as-the-coronavirus-pandemic-takes-hold-we-are-making-decisions-without-reliable-data/
th3_g3nt3lman: hey George
Iliftmymousealot: nice
ScrubLifeChoseMe: ???
hairybardikles: hairybardikles subscribed with Twitch Prime.
64pillars: is it a beyond meat burger
mitsukomegumii: lul
ScrubLifeChoseMe: lmaoo
samtheprogram: choo choo HypeGriffin2
realolejka: your first rap album almost ready
micos7: I got that sht in Plague inc ,started in China nuked the planet really fast
SHAVEYY_: 69
kiikoh: level 1 hype, otherwise known as "the minimum level of hype"
anthraxvirus322: 1
devm0d: Burgers prevent sars v2
bichid69: is there a vaccine for SARS?
xioph: Hey George, just wondering if the earth is flat?
Krakken_TM: hey gorge so ok lets say this virus needs attention. but what do you think that countries that just before quarantine their borders were open
tajpouria: f yall who separating the virus
finnad: no there is no sars vaccine afaik
khiomtv: touching face DansGame
johanoutdoors: @georgehotz Why didn't you want to stream in 2020? People appreciate you on here.
martinstuessy: ey georgie
kektobiologist: you think it's more than 4 percent? or less?
liranisme: what's the best way to become a hacker?
socialnotsocial: so how awesome are your lungs going to be after recovery?
bobda_builder11: i had influanza type A
SHAVEYY_: *researching corona whilst touching face*
martinstuessy: @georgehotz can we dockerize corona?
bradfox2: look at the net economic impacts of shutdown vs deaths
Atlas03: u buy a hachet and start hacking @liranisme
Krakken_TM: @socialnotsocial in most cases people recover from this with flu symptoms
finnad: you touch your face a lot :D
Izimoney92100: touching ur face YouWHY YouWHY YouWHY
Krakken_TM: its not something fatal
bichid69: @SHAVEYY_ hahahahaha
krilltwitch: https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fimmu.2018.01581/full THIS//
Krakken_TM: its just that transmits so easily
webxl: What was accomplished in pt1??
yourboibl: this?https://i1.wp.com/virologydownunder.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/Influenza-A-virus-schematic.jpg?ssl=1
theonlymonkas: nothing
Krakken_TM: that people can overcrowd the hospitals
b2kemann: @georgehotz you should try jupyter lab, it's sweet
SlowlyRunnin: !uptime
25missedcalls: martin shkreli could help now...
drparse: george was washing hands before it was cool
Krakken_TM: and there will be decisions on who gets to live
xioph: are u debugging corona in prod?
TheMixStar: idek what is this
OLEM13: covid-19 is not dangerous itself, what is killing people is the viral load
liranisme: how to become a hacker?
kiikoh: why do these sites look so bad
shanumbra: LUL
Initial18: @xioph We want the bugs in there to prevent Corona from doing what it should be. alieldThink
Iliftmymousealot: they dropped the zero day
derowon: derowon subscribed at Tier 1.
Bo0sted05: what are you trying to do
kiikoh: not even the url is pretty
kektobiologist: they look perfect
Krakken_TM: also guys even if u wear an EFFECTIVE mask make sure u use correctly, not touching the front part with your hands and then scratch ur face etc
theonlymonkas: LUL
SHAVEYY_: because researchers cant write code @kiikoh
nico_d0t: It is called polymerase
DevoE444: covid 19 is a buffer overflow
bichid69: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/nuccore/KU922529
peter35_: eat your own batsoup
tiagodopke: looks better than most websites
TheHareld: What is he exactly doing by the way? I'm lost
xioph: myaocat just dmed me thanking u for banning him @georgehotz
webxl: What are the odds an SV hacker saves us from Great Depression II?
Penguino138: Pangolin Soup
nvda9: George types 200wpm
jagger_rsw: based on the case of Germany, where do they the most tests per capita, the mortality rate is ~0.3% - 90deaths / 25k tested
elezaun: What's up? What we learn
TheNakedFlame: crazy how nature do dat
luigifrcruz: Genome for Avian Flu: https://nextstrain.org/flu/avian
Krakken_TM: @webxl none
FSRoosta: Severe conditions are nearly always accompanied by a bacterial pneumonia alongside the virus
harbad: did he you say that the president contacted you @georgehotz ?
nico_d0t: https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article/figure/image?download&size=large&id=info:doi/10.1371/journal.pone.0181969.g001
lexhonecker: George, what's your goal today?
bradfox2: German fatality rate source?
Kubissus: @jagger_rsw they misclassify the deaths thought
mitsukomegumii: H1n1 genbank dump: https://www.genome.jp/dbget-bin/www_bget?genbank-vrl:FJ966082
theonlymonkas: are you working with the goverment?
Kubissus: If you die while having coronavirus and some other illness they will report that you died from the other ilness
Iliftmymousealot: https://www.rki.de/EN/Home/homepage_node.html
xrealyy: the instance of a guy who can become anyone he want in just a matter of days, nice hotz
jagger_rsw: @Kubissus no idea - they probably do tests on those who died - source of data: https://coronavirus.jhu.edu/map.html
champ900: hey george
guacDev: jorge jorge!!!
Atlas03: ofc he is but hes not allowed to tell @cjocol2201
catacata92: maybe there are quite a few variations of flu
theonlymonkas: LUL
b2kemann: top users of internet: 1.trump 2.isis 3.geohot
robbsalm: when an ai expert saves the world
nvda9: it's cool. bing.com/covid
Krakken_TM: in 2017-2018 71.000 people died from flu
h3ku: https://rnacentral.org/search?q=swine
bichid69: stitch em up bro
Fulk33: @georgehotz your not gonna find a single genome for the flue as there are thousands of different viruses. The flue has mutated like a gazillon times
harbad: they don't database the whole virus? weird.
schrammel: what are you trying to do?
Jakobo06: I think that they are typically segmented due to the shotgun sequencing method
alphagainzzz: !commands
alphagainzzz: dam
tarasyarema: hey, do you like advent of code?
Jakobo06: its expensive
bichid69: !commands
harbad: I think @jakobo06 is onto something
djcows: Shoud i go get some fast food before society shuts down completely?
jmp0ut: hey, folding@home stufF?
liranisme: how do I become a hacker?
jmp0ut: biohacking already on ACE codons
jmp0ut: ?
nvda9: who believes that it's biological weapon. bs
Krakken_TM: this virus is an excuse for the greatest depression
Jakobo06: For a highly accurate sequencing you typically use illumina sequencing, which only works for short dna sequences
ad_1337: @liranisme first of all you need a black hoodie
theonlymonkas: @djcows yes
harbad: it's not the flu
cybermajestic: hello hotz
harbad: it never was the flu. people are just stupid.
bichid69: its not the flu bro
myuchelys: 'flu-like symptoms'
myuchelys: not its like the flu
railander: the symptoms at least
bichid69: symptom my arse
jmp0ut: angiotensin-converting enzyme 2 (ACE2)
hypertextlabs: what did you end up getting to last night, quick recap possibly?
Wraken__: pasteur in France got the whole genome @georgehotz
jmp0ut: see metacyc
SHAVEYY_: @liranisme install arch linux to become a true haxor
robbsalm: george how do you know about this shit?
Penguino138: Some on in politics started that BS to make us feel safe
ancientchineseelder: Def ain't no flu
Beldathas: Hello from France ! demOiii
cybermajestic: @georgehotz what are you doing?
gyne: boomers be like it's just the flu
bsx1123: People are saying that because the symptoms are the same
bichid69: not every cough is the flu
ancientchineseelder: Supposedly 700k actually died in Wuhan
socialnotsocial: what are your top picks for second order effects? and top 10 anime battles?
ancientchineseelder: look at the cams online, nobody out there
jmp0ut: @georgehotz check metacyc.org
harbad: Don't believe nothing politicians say.
bichid69: if you cough when you're stabbed that's not the flu
jmp0ut: or EMBL
jagger_rsw: what george is trying to do, I just joined, is he trying to prove sars-cov2 is not h1n1?
zennydmt: will u post these videos on youtube?
theonlymonkas: LUL
Krakken_TM: countries didnt even close borders just before quarantine
Krakken_TM: shit is suspicious asf
xanax_and_bj: When you look at videos of Italy hospital inside, you see almost all of the corona patients are severely overweight
champ900: what are you eating
Krakken_TM: and suddenly every1 is doing the exact same legislations
ad_1337: HHKB Pro 2?
dvdutch: Whatre we doin rn
jmp0ut: https://www.ebi.ac.uk/
jmp0ut: that as well
Krakken_TM: worldwide policy
bichid69: do we have a vaccine for SARS?
risenn_: !uptime
hastingspb: where burger from
jmp0ut: genomics database
catinthepimphat: covid-19 is the disease caused by the virus
xioph: top 5 conspiracy theories?
ancientchineseelder: its 5 AM rn but here's wuhan cameras : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vu4EOyji76s
maxpokerrr: any more cooking streams?
Erixp: covid-19 is the disease right ?
kubaaa6: Can you watch donald trump talk live and reeact to it? Hes talking rn
webxl: Trump was like "the flu kills way more (now)"
gyne: LUL
25missedcalls: can u heck nasa nao?
ancientchineseelder: for anybody interested
robbsalm: an healthy 34 yo died of covid today in rome
painpainmorepain: ليممن تمنبيب منتننتب ﻻهص حهشب
railander: LUL
smurfd0: its probably becase it mimics a flu
bradfox2: try and predict mutations
Crypod: blame Valeant Kappa
dvdutch: Covid19 is the disease, novel coronavirus is the virus I believe
painpainmorepain: يمنن عهبىس
champ900: do you think it will be over in a month
tajpouria: 700 people!!!
xioph: is covid-19 a type of burger?
lidermaury: the government created coronavirus to reduce the population
painpainmorepain: يسي
SpaceGhost8: orange man will save us
painpainmorepain: منني
jijoe99: PogChamp
dvdutch: No cap
TheBusbyBabes: well sars killed healthy people
painpainmorepain: سيشض
painpainmorepain: للر
Penguino138: Exactly
painpainmorepain: صثش
hypertextlabs: "were not watching Donald Trump talk about it"
catacata92: :)) cool
painpainmorepain: يبخؤن
djcows: preach
mars4real: amen
hypertextlabs: ato
sfingrs: And here i am in Serbia waiting for my burger delivery for 3 hours :(
painpainmorepain: صمش
Crypod: Jebaited spam ?
bichid69: can we corona the borona?
hypertextlabs: good shit
joaofoliveira: we do have animal vaccines for covid already
joker2k999: rant maybe?
lawli3t__: Hello from France !
Penguino138: Even my educated brother got convinced it's just a flu.....
anon_v28: why do you always seem like you're on adderall?
osuiw: heyo, just came from the first part on youtube.
guacDev: صمش صمش صمش jorge!
jagger_rsw: I must say US is interesting society, Trump says something, and the whole country doesn't care ;). As in, in Germany Merkel says something, and Germans and EU pays attention :)
robbsalm: hello from rome
zennydmt: have u studied infection diseases before?
Krakken_TM: @georgehotz so whats going on there. is going outside restricted?
railander: my dad is in a hyper state of stress because he can't take his eyes off the news, despite better judgement from me
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz привет геохот
webxl: Massive stimulus incoming
kubaaa6: If he was on adderall he wouldnt be eating lmaooo
xioph: can we weaponize burgers as a counter attack to covid19?
saintmthw: "im on vyvanze"
Danilok100: we all gonna be jobless
djcows: he's on coffee
bichid69: 721 peeps boissssssss
tarasyarema: go do some advent of corona challenges!
mars4real: eating stream Pog
nvda9: china hid the news
eiscosogin1: because europeans are addicted to government like heroin or crack
bradfox2: build a virus rna embedding nn and see if we can predict future mutations
bichid69: 721 OMG
xrealyy: dont eat shit geo, nutrition foodie only
railander: borgar Kreygasm
tarasyarema: i liked when you solved advent of code
finnad: 8000 cases omegalul
maxpokerrr: trump is master troll
osuiw: !streamtime
ls111: can u eat like that even on adderal?
komocode_: doom eternal
Izimoney92100: is this an eating stream??
otaky152: @shaveyy_ ты сука кто
joaofoliveira: search for the animal covid vaccines already available
Rahleo: everytime i show up food is being consumed
krilltwitch: that burger looked so good!!!
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
a_ato: zoraoWUT zoraoWUT
jmp0ut: @georgehotz https://www.genenames.org/data/gene-symbol-report/#!/hgnc_id/HGNC:13557
jmp0ut: target
o______________________k: squadPH squadPH squadPH
osuiw: !UPTIME
joker2k999: LUL
Nafferza: KEKW
djcows: quarantine gang
dvdutch: Does China have a propensity for producing coronaviruses? Including SARS
ancientchineseelder: george smoke some weed
nvda9: some countries are angry at china
harbad: lol, yes they are
64pillars: xqcM 📈
khiomtv: I wonder why LUL
painpainmorepain: ijew
lidermaury: cause everybody is at home
theonlymonkas: lets cook something
xioph: thoughts on covid19 as a SaaS?
hypertextlabs: hack the box
noobaj: @georgehotz how can you expect everyone to understand those paper? just asking
o______________________k: squad4 KEKW
b2kemann: quarantine brooo
RoboticMind90: Lets start coding
Izimoney92100: ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
farlopote: HerbPerve
Fobechi: Were all so bored
webxl: because no one has anything better to do!!
fedman2010: everybody is sitting home watching twich )
lawli3t__: @georgehotz Try do an sql injection into covid-19 and dump the dbs for view his informations !!! NotLikeThis
jagger_rsw: It's like with bitcoin, you make a stream at the right time and call it 'blockchain ai for crypto' and 2k viewers ensured
dvdutch: CaaSaaS? @xioph
Iliftmymousealot: chat is getting real trollish
webxl: They killed sports
khiomtv: KEKW users DansGame
osuiw: @georgehotz whats your uptime?
zombiedigital: @georgehotz build urself a lab and get a covid-19 infected guy somewhere who wants to experiment. LULW
icyvran: There are a lot of people in their homes, that's why many people are watching the streams
harbad: @liranisme obviously you spam a hacker's twitch chat.
kostilin13: europoors taxed to death
fedman2010: what is the best programminglanguage ?
railander: never heard of that one
tome_silva: lung fibrosis
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: geohot more like geosexy
dvdutch: Good question
gyne: supposed irreversible lung damage
FSRoosta: nobody knows
happy_havok: @fedman2010 whatever fits your needs the best
khiomtv: @fedman2010 Scratch
bichid69: jokes on you, I already can't breathe at night without a ventilator
Erixp: @fedman2010 there isnt a best one
dysoco: I believe there are some reports of lung scarring but nothing conclusive yet, might only be a few outliers
lawli3t__: @georgehotz Try do an sql injection into covid-19 and dump the dbs for view his informations !!! NotLikeThis
railander: @tome_silva lung fibrosis your life is 2-5 max
SHAVEYY_: @fedman2010 BASIC
Madogstony: wait did you sleep last night?
brofessorbob: North Park checking in.
xanax_and_bj: @georgehotz Do you think Bill Gates is behind engineering this virus?
jmp0ut: answer
l1ttlemtman: 700 people
mars4real: that magic bag has infinite food LUL
jmp0ut: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
javadragoniv: @fedman2010 machine code, learn 10101010
wpreston: wpreston subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Izimoney92100: TOUCHING YOUR FACE WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace
l1ttlemtman: that's insane
gyne: there was a headline going around that it could make men infertile but haven't seen any basis for that
finnad: @xanax_and_bj lol
jmp0ut: angiotensin 2 catabolysis thats why
dvdutch: Teach yourself @liranisme
nvda9: is he in NYC
zombiedigital: there is a conspiracy with bill gates foundation and covid-19
jmp0ut: it's not a conspiracy
theonlymonkas: JOe rogan
jmp0ut: it's genetic engineering
bichid69: jokes on you, I already can't breathe at night without a ventilator
Plurmorant: @zombiedigital event 201 WutFace
brofessorbob: Do you know anybody who has the Covid-19 in San Diego?
xxtrippyhippyxx_: why havnt you streamed in a while???
mars4real: chat WeirdChamp
Rahleo: science and science only :D
gyne: it's the chemtrails broooo
osuiw: that'd joe rogan yo
kostilin13: KKona why not
jagger_rsw: I think george touched his face - hello, police!
Iliftmymousealot: what's the mission for todays stream?
brodie_codie: better question how to be a cyber security analyst
Crypod: later-food is better than now food
Tsoding: monkaS
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: WutFace
Madogstony: !uptime
khiomtv: Rationing food PogChamp
emilwallin: WutFace
guacDev: ice cube on floor!!!!
klaazdw: hey guys
Madogstony: rip
Erixp: ice on floor
railander: DROPPED SHIT ON FLOOR!
lawli3t__: @georgehotz Try do an sql injection into covid-19 and dump the dbs for view his informations !!! NotLikeThis @georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz@georgehotz
vaskogomez87: soggy fries lol
Izimoney92100: ICE ON FLOOR
robbsalm: he s gonna slip
dvdutch: Ice cube
dorkmo: touchingnface chewing ice
lidermaury: please talk to us
xrealyy: sugary green tea?
shlver: he didn't wash his hands before handling ice DansGame
xXICEW0LFXx: green tea is where it's at
osuiw: @georgehotz you dropped ice on the floor yo
yevheniiushtyk: how do i stop being a noob, george?😞
curlypyoob: how do you get all the DBC files from the car manufacturers
carcharotch: he gonna slip on it WutFace
harbad: lol peace guys, it's just ice
Quad___lol: dropped ice DansGame
hairybardikles: Do you like black tea geo?
bradfox2: Ito en
FSRoosta: wash hands you reprobate
mrhdr: Tsoding sup komrade
osuiw: so your one of those guys huh
railander: dropped ice DansGame
nvda9: sometimes George looks like Jerry from Rick and Morty
theonlymonkas: eminem-godzilla
dvdutch: The floor will soak it up
brodie_codie: study the owasp top 10
jmp0ut: @georgehotz https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
Tsoding: mrhdr, tsodinKomrade 7
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
xioph: thoughts on turning covid19 into an ice cream flavour?
tarasyarema: hey solve some challenges here https://adventofcorona.hackersatupc.org/
Erixp: rip wood floor
djcows: Pick up the ice!
jagger_rsw: PS3
bobbyjoeboy: StoneLightning StoneLightning
brodie_codie: then sans top 25
icyvran: What do we talk about?
xXICEW0LFXx: I've been watching archives on YouTube for the past two days straight lol so i"m glad to finally catch a live stream
a_ato: ice
mars4real: LUL
chusiv: Ok so nothing alike the flu, whats next George?
vaskogomez87: its just water guys lol
emilwallin: LULW
wpreston: the chance of damage seems high considering the staff are limiting access to the patients and making less changes to the ventilators than usual.. good article on the current status of a patient's care is https://www.propublica.org/article/a-medical-worker-describes--terrifying-lung-failure-from-covid19-even-in-his-young-patients
miraeldoto: whats goiing on here
Izimoney92100: WASH HANDS
o______________________k: LUL
khiomtv: coughing monkaS
davidbarreroo: !height
Keyeh: heyy george, check childish gambino new album its sick
aptgetmark: is there any courses that you have done that you would recommend ?
brbdontdie: hey george, you social distancing?
marvluebke: @o______________________k what a name :D
guacDev: i will watch the ice cube until it melts
74c55639: @georgehotz do you like the show?
javadragoniv: @georgehotz BRO JARED FUCKED COME ON
SgT_Vimes: Watchu say about Epstein now?
krilltwitch: shoot. he coughed
bobbyjoeboy: CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob
miraeldoto: @aptgetmark are you kidding?
dvdutch: What are we trying to accomplish this stream?
lexhonecker: @georgehotz what is your goal today, George?
o______________________k: @marvluebke squadHYPERS
b2kemann: cold t4a?? i'm gonna make myself a hot one as a demonstration
nvda9: lmao he read it.
ancientchineseelder: Pneumonia usually has permanent effects on lungs. What will be interesting to see how much more severe COVID does or doesn't make it
xioph: @dvdutch pretend we know how biology works
Crypod: MEV-1
64pillars: xqcC FBBlock touching face
jmp0ut: junk dna
KaleSC: yeah, whats the goal today?
harbad: they didn't strip the white space??? lol
Fulk33: https://github.com/Urinx/alphafold_pytorch
brbdontdie: george, you are being a baad role model with your hands touching your face
dvdutch: Build a coronavirus API
mikhailangelo: its only 8 letters who cares 4Head
brofessorbob: trimer
mars4real: hoursW
jagger_rsw: we should notify twitch, he's touching his face
harbad: shut up about touching his face, it's fine.
Tsoding: exploit vector LUL
SnadderG: Any nice people in chat that can tell me why I would use jupyter lab over notebook?
brbdontdie: but its for his own health
Madogstony: cyber
gyne: ace 2 PogChamp
bobbyjoeboy: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jagger_rsw: @harbad trump says it's not
nvda9: George is a good rapper.
railander: mers monkaS
lidermaury: hes not
eyesonlyug: George, what're we trying to do in this stream?
jmp0ut: because you're looking for HCoV-NL63 not COVID-19
Kmerck313: This amazing
harbad: do you believe everything politicians tell you?
Crypod: wow
b2kemann: why itsn't there more biotech in the world?!
brbdontdie: can covid 19 be spread like a computer virus?
champ900: @georgehotz if you met trump what would you say to him
Fulk33: https://github.com/Urinx/alphafold_pytorch
KaleSC: what we doing today?
brofessorbob: Share the link
elezaun: Please clarify Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome is a Syndrome not a virus. If not related to Corona virus family, What virus does it look like? Shooting the shit.
bichid69: run md on it
Quad___lol: just ask US government for more corona info LUL I bet they can handle you a vaccine as well
brbdontdie: so basically can computers catch the virus?
DrPeacock: people asking "what we doing today" when it literally says it in the title lol
bichid69: molecular dynamics bro
o______________________k: squadCozy squadL squadCozy squadL
dvdutch: You guys think remdesivir will work?
khiomtv: Corona a literal exploit of humans
St47ik: fold them good
Waldoqq: Waldoqq subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak! Wtf I didnt get an alert you were streaming how long you been on for?
catinthepimphat: 3 separate protiens are required to make the spike
robbsalm: what's a protein?
joker2k999: 10mins.
mars4real: @drpeacock bold of you to assume people on twitch read titles LUL
xlionel775: are you going to keep doing biology shit or it's a one time thing?
yevheniiushtyk: yevheniiushtyk subscribed at Tier 1.
harbad: @robbsalm look it up
brbdontdie: @robbsalm its like chcken or steak
bichid69: download the pdb
railander: @robbsalm prob way ahead of you LUL
DrPeacock: @mars4real why wouldnt they lol its a big font?
harbad: you have internet, use google
robbsalm: chill brro
yevheniiushtyk: vibe check
foti_kasparov: Finally able to catch your stream ! Europe gang
robbsalm: i am studying cs not biology
brodie_codie: same
nvda9: ok boomer @robbsalm
brbdontdie: after autonomous vehicles, george is going to create a hospital startup
maxpokerrr: bio hacking george
b2kemann: cs will merge with bio, it's the next revolution
Crypod: so basically we need something that will achieve penetration on this virus only and no other cells. then let white blood cells in?
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz so what are you trying to achieve exactly?
brodie_codie: might be right
jmp0ut: you have to sideline an apoptosis routine specific to the virus than the host which is too difficult as your heart will die
harbad: Proteins are what make up most of our bodies. They are made up of amino acids and are the structures that make things work in our bodies.
brofessorbob: This is a waste of time. Let's CTF!
brbdontdie: i could see him moving into creating cyborgs and stuff
Quad___lol: replace proteins with fibre and problem solved
robbsalm: @harbad how are they represented in that genome?
Beldathas: We have the same chair as you in my workplace
catinthepimphat: you need to focus on the closed state when it is outside the cell
jmp0ut: heart break hotel
brodie_codie: CTF SeemsGood SeemsGood
jmp0ut: is what this is
djcows: That ice is melting fast, it will leak in between the cracks of your floor and your house will explode, better pick it up
b2kemann: a to insert cell above, b for below georg...
brbdontdie: @djcows i don't think that's how houses work
tykabmo: well what type of cell does Covid-19 infect?
DevoE444: Is coke cola killing the virus ?
catinthepimphat: identifying a proper epitope to create an antigen from for our WBC to attach to
brofessorbob: Is this a kaggle competition or something?
harbad: the genome is just a collection of codes with start and stop codes with protein sequencing 'codons' in between. Each codon read to create part of proteins.
byte_baron: i hearrd swallowing your toothpaste kills coronavirus?
railander: coughing monkaS
gclawes: ASN.1 is like old-school protobuf
khiomtv: monkaS
bichid69: nah bro kaggle's lame
ToxicVulpes: coronaS
Fastela: So many windows
dvdutch: Proteins have a file type
dvdutch: ?
djcows: @brbdontdie Oh oops my bad
champ900: what do you hope to achieve
Quad___lol: it is spreading through web monkaS
VanishBlox: sup George, how's progress Goin?
catinthepimphat: @tykabmo epithelial cells in your lungs
1shortking: file.protein
iskjmss: guys what came first? the protein or the computers?
socialnotsocial: kaggles for pussies who can't cure cancer
byte_baron: ethernet cables carry the coronavirus apparently
VanishBlox: sup bois
jmp0ut: you dont want covid-19 you want hcov-nl63 which is the actual human variant
emiven: are you using tab nine?
VanishBlox: the DNA
jmp0ut: which is disgusting
harbad: think of codons like like short bash scrips to run small programs.
nudax: nice to see you again
maxpokerrr: if i drink corona bear will i get corona?
brbdontdie: hey goerge, did your computer get its vaccine yet?
zombiedigital: corona hackaton
Edelknecht: Corona doesn't work upside down. So Australia is safe
gabo_sk: hello
brofessorbob: I thought GEO would be on linux.
brbdontdie: you are exposing your pc to coronvirus
VanishBlox: I was just watching the comma ai archive video of it
VanishBlox: of yesterday stream
dvdutch: He probably got linux on a VM
nvda9: imma bout to buy hazmat suit
tarasyarema: ADVENT OF CORONA
FaustPetrovich: FaustPetrovich subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 5 months, currently on a 5 month streak! 777 people are watching
Keyeh: kek
Erixp: kek
zombiedigital: KEKW
Crypod: KEKW
yevheniiushtyk: kek
djcows: kek
VanishBlox: kek
inDOObitablee: KEKW
dvdutch: KEKW
railander: K E K LUL
harbad: @georgehotz check whitespace
carcharotch: kek
m113v: kekw
khiomtv: DansGame
filipeoliveiraa: KEKW
phrixus_bro: kek oh my god
St47ik: Any new mutations?
brbdontdie: does george play league of legends?
tome_silva: this is a waste of time
monst3rcow: kek MaxLOL
troxtheone: destroy that virus!
VanishBlox: nature is a troll maaaan
1shortking: where is my 144 fps cn3d viewer
dvdutch: The white supremacists made the virus confirmed
VanishBlox: GAY
harbad: they aren't identical
St47ik: MrDestructoid
maxpokerrr: KEKW can cure corona
Crypod: curvyHmm hmmm voltron
harbad: they are different, only in structure.
osuiw: I was thinking more like Megatron
yevheniiushtyk: voltron LUL
nvda9: ctf
osuiw: looks more like a jet
VanishBlox: GG
DevoE444: is Corona a form of Ligma?
railander: GG
Erixp: ggg
brofessorbob: Glycine? Brah
lexhonecker: George, I think you will need to get PyMOL for displaying the proteins correctly
foti_kasparov: That's a nice looking protein
VanishBlox: corona virus is epic gamer guys
Jakobo06: Barcoding maybe
osuiw: @DevoE444 nice one dude
lexhonecker: That's what the pros use
tauzN: @DevoE444 ligma what?
TheHareld: What in the actual fuck is he doing? Does he have biology degree or something or?
bichid69: get chimera or nglview
harbad: like normal prions vs mad cow prions, they are made up of the same thing, just folded differently.
St47ik: the whole worlds is in chaos cuz of 8 kb of genetic data NotLikeThis
Crypod: alright, which one of you made this virus? that's twitch-speak right there oshiMad
bichid69: nglview bro, integrates with jupyter
harbad: slightly different folds
brofessorbob: It's called a trimer.
pomprocks: is this like figuring how how a computer works by measuring the size of the chips?
ragemaster999: @georgehotz what are you trying to do?
logi6000: impossible he's streaming!!!
brofessorbob: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protein_trimer
maxpokerrr: any coomers?
1shortking: wow
nvda9: it's 3 .30 am here
Erixp: PogChamp
icyvran: What are we going to do tonight George? George: The same thing we do every night, Watcher. Try to take over the world.
VanishBlox: I'm a zoomer
dvdutch: "try-mer"
toast_ps: l
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
toast_ps: L
Quad___lol: MEAT SPIN
bichid69: ngL
dvdutch: Trimmer has 2 "m"s
Draco401: ngL
shlver: LUL
yojana57: what's happening now?
Keyeh: OMEGALUL
cutza: lol
bichid69: ngL lol
govlog: u should fuzz the coronavirus syscall to find a kernel rce
dvdutch: We gon cure this before the stream ends
viper262_: NGL view
Draelios6: NGL VIEW bro
VanishBlox: MrDestructoid
lidermaury: im just here for u guys in a chat
Waldoqq: NaCl?
robbsalm: we got this
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz just fuzz it :)
yevheniiushtyk: first corona jailbreak when?
1shortking: u codemonkeys sure know a lot about biology all of a sudden
Crypod: Not Gonna Lie View Kappa
pomprocks: biology is like alien technology that we are always trying to figure out how it works
VanishBlox: not gonna lie view
dvdutch: not gonna lie
nvda9: does corona die in high temperature
VanishBlox: fuck u person for saying it before me
Crypod: LUL
b2kemann: jupyter lab!!!
harbad: "this mac sucks" love ya @georgehotz
murkythunder: @1shortking codemonkeys made an algo detecting cancer better than any doctor, we masters of everything
mumubecks: nvda9 no. summer temps wont help us. check it out
法國人: People playing animal crossing onTwitch right now. Meanwhile George Hotz trying to cross-over things
Usisuvach0: @nvda9 yes at 56 C or above
m113v: @nvda9 yes thats why go in the oven
Fastela: @nvda9 I've read it does, for temps higher than 70 degrees celsius
Fastela: 56? ok
Usisuvach0: yes
Usisuvach0: 56
logi6000: are we gon find the cure
nvda9: i thought it's rumor
Krakken_TM: 56?
xeroeffect: Do you have enough toilet paper?
Krakken_TM: i heard 22 KEKW
bichid69: restart the kernel
dvdutch: Will you not end the stream until we find the cure?
jmp0ut: medium chain fatty acid sidechaining?
Krakken_TM: fkin missinformation
jmp0ut: a human can manage
djcows: Just warm the earth up and corona will go away
harbad: buy a bidet, tp problem fixed
jmp0ut: a virus cannot
mumubecks: not just hand washing. Put hands in boiling water
shlver: just cut off your handw
theonlymonkas: LUL
Krakken_TM: @mumubecks no hand washing is enough
Svr123456789: Hey science !
logi6000: we all know he's just doin this cause that porn star said she'll fuck whoever finds the cure
Krakken_TM: but u have to do it right
Krakken_TM: for 20s
gabo_sk: what is he doing?
dvdutch: Who @logi6000
VanishBlox: you guys know that death cures the virus right?
eaterenrgy: @gabo_sk Saving the world
liiiiiig0: PogChamp
Xent12: @logi6000 lmao which pornstar said that
harbad: oh, that's cool as hell!
St47ik: PogChamp
TommyBates97: where you all from chat?
dvdutch: pog
Crypod: wow nice
gabo_sk: oh cool
logi6000: look it up @dvdutch
TheMoatman: What library's doing that vis?
Erixp: PogChamp
klaazdw: POG
Jehhred: This is some next level Data Science!!!!!
eaterenrgy: Pog
NewManSD: PogU
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm
b2kemann: <3
jmp0ut: which pr0n star is pushing for proteomics
alphagainzzz: Kreygasm
zol0: WayTooDank
Draelios6: Pog
jmp0ut: i love her already
lidermaury: twitchslam coronavirus?
phelipe3: you're clever AF
VanishBlox: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
xanax_and_bj: You should work for Bill and Melidna gates foundation
o______________________k: squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ
DevoE444: there is no cure for any virus cause all viruses transform
nvda9: 80% people will recover
Kmerck313: Wait which pornstar?
gorgai: I dont understand anything PogChamp
Draelios6: No FFZ FailFish
xeroeffect: Who’s brain is that?
Beldathas: Pog
SgT_Vimes: So, is this...biohacking?
St47ik: twitchcoq twitchcov
dvdutch: Nvm she ugly
shlver: we need you full screen
alycia: first time live in what 6 months ???
Svr123456789: Are you trying to learn to the corona virus to drive a car ?
logi6000: @gorgai look it up
theonlymonkas: LUL
MownarN: First time here excited to see u stream George! U made me way more interested in programming than I already was
icyvran: 848 viewers
PiroFloydian: oh hey he came back
yevheniiushtyk: that's a lot of ice
joker2k999: LUL
brofessorbob: How's Corona in SD? Is it as bad as the news makes it to be?
pomprocks: i think this is the learning to type part of learning to program
carcharotch: quick reminder that ice cubeis still melting
m113v: how can i donate you @georgehotz
St47ik: NotLikeThis
emiven: What is we haced.. the coronavirus... :O
theonlymonkas: ice cube
harbad: they bind to receptors, for those who don't know. The 'spikes' stick out of the viral body and attach to cells. Then the virus injects it's genome into the cell.
Crypod: we need a magnet monkaS
railander: ice cube PunOko
dvdutch: Get the tablets out
robbsalm: let's eat some zink
s3bastians: @georgehotz Hello! You are the self-driving car guy, right?
Erixp: eat zink monkaS
Tsoding: The ice cube is almost melted :(
oanto80: please buy a descent mic
iskjmss: shame they made the titanic out of zinc
myaocat: test
Draco401: This dude LUL
gabo_sk: monkaHmm
brofessorbob: Comrade Tsoding is here
osuiw: the mic is fine
TheMoatman: Suck on some coins, they have plenty of zinc
myaocat: im unbanned PogChamp :) <3
harbad: no
harbad: lol
Tsoding: @brofessorbob, monkaS
Keyeh: descent LUL
DevoE444: eating zinc after burger, i can see the irony Kappa
hastingspb: they made it out of sink
Iliftmymousealot: l-theanine caffeine stack?
gabo_sk: coronaS
GeneralSoak: no we need more zinc
brofessorbob: I hear Russington DC is well this time of year.
jmp0ut: because it works on angiotensin 2 enzyme catalysis for transcription
logi6000: for everyone asking whick pornstar it's Lola Taylor
lidermaury: its almost 900 people
jmp0ut: you janky biohacker bruh
dvdutch: Did u guys hear the titanic sunk
snorting_milk: snorting_milk subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 7 months, currently on a 7 month streak!
harbad: capsid - the shell body of the virus
nvda9: George that chair is good?
Draco401: @dvdutch Really!?
luismario0o: I don't know what he is doing..
jmp0ut: biology does not work on logic gates it works on resource efficiency
byte_baron: @dvdutch fake news
dvdutch: Yea look it up
tykabmo: @georgehotz can you go get me popcorn and a diet coke?
Draco401: No way
champ900: lets see some hacking
jmp0ut: hydrolysis
St47ik: @champ900 biohacking
brofessorbob: It's biology
Cas_9: I think you should start with an introduction to Biology course
alycia: what exactly is he doing ?
Tsoding: @alycia, he's hacking Ligma-19 PogChamp
St47ik: @alycia saving the world
gabo_sk: hacking coronavirus
theonlymonkas: do you use zinc to prevent hair loss?
salz_pfeffer: I'm in for the intro bio with you
harbad: @georgehotz they are differently folded, each protein is made up of the same pieces, just folded differently
robbsalm: great idea
railander: lets see it FeelsGoodMan
alycia: Is he using Corona science to jailbreak ?
jmp0ut: @geohotz check this: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
brofessorbob: Central Dogma of Biology. Do you know that?
wootawee: phylogenetics/evolution of molecules
Darian141: @georgehotz love ur content bro! keep up the great work!!
mumubecks: Why no hacking for cancer or aids? corona hype train?
nvda9: It's Deep Dive in Corona
marvluebke: wat
marvluebke: LUL ^
theonlymonkas: LUL
gabo_sk: x d
logi6000: we all know that @georgehotz is just doing this so that he can fuck that pornstar that says she'll fuck who finds the cure
brofessorbob: Cancer has too many causes to ever have a singular cure.
robbsalm: LUL
lidermaury: what was it
iFAK: @georgehotz please jailbreak covid19 and rescue humanity. Would ultimately love to run unsigned code but stopping it would suffice. Cheers from Canada m8
DevoE444: @Quad___lol good observations keep going Kappa
salz_pfeffer: ah the python example
Okayge_TeaTime: one more "xD" and im out 😡
barrenaps: Is this an open source project?
theonlymonkas: xD
Darian141: xD
Nedeljko99: Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA
gabo_sk: xD
marvluebke: xxxxxxxxxDDDDDDDDDDDD
lidermaury: xd
VanishBlox: xD
cutza: xD
DevoE444: xD
Darian141: xddddd
iskjmss: xD
gyne: xD
St47ik: bring back XD
nvda9: xD
VanishBlox: xDd
djcows: xD
railander: @brofessorbob well did you see the discovery published earlier this year? seems very promissing
yevheniiushtyk: xD
Nedeljko99: Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA Marko Njegomir je PICKA
gabo_sk: Dx
djcows: y u so cute xD
St47ik: Cx
VanishBlox: dicks
gabo_sk: ¯_(ツ)_/¯
gyne: so why would more zinc mess with the molecule
dvdutch: link @railander
bichid69: I hate biopython its shit
SgT_Vimes: ”Python tools for covid-19”, that was my initial idea too!
mumubecks: why is the marking text all the time?
brofessorbob: @railander Which study?
outlier2: josiah zayner has a bioengineering course: https://www.the-odin.com/bioe101/
byte_baron: dude, just ml the cure already man, people are dying
VanishBlox: marking text means you hack better and that's a fact
socialnotsocial: that ice cube still hasn't melted, pretty much proves global warming is a scam
railander: @dvdutch @brofessorbob https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-019-0578-8
byte_baron: machine learn the cure!!!
theonlymonkas: LUL
robbsalm: wutt
Erixp: LUL
harbad: lol I thought you loved it!
gabs2819: LUL
dvdutch: thankls
bichid69: exactly my poiny
dvdutch: thanks
abnerrrrr: hello george <3
bichid69: biopython is shit
jmp0ut: yes
jmp0ut: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
liiiiiig0: PYMOL @georgehotz
shlver: what are yo utrying to do?
Smube: hack the stock market
1shortking: LULW
Erixp: LUL
foti_kasparov: noobs
canpake7: Damn, didnt even finish the first part
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
triple__m: ban him
theonlymonkas: not me
St47ik: The world is collapsing NotLikeThis
SHAVEYY_: ban time PogChamp
TheGpSd: Hi
railander: @dvdutch @brofessorbob it cured all cancer tested on rats
theonlymonkas: ban LUL
numlox: numlox subscribed with Twitch Prime.
gyne: wyd b 😳
wpreston: https://coursera
VanishBlox: what are you trying to accomplish?
sal_gent: the disrespect level is rising Kappa
ragemaster999: @georgehotz https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
Kmerck313: BAN
DevoE444: Greta Tunberg has the cure, you heard it here first
dvdutch: Too bad covid will kill us all before cancer does @railander
logi6000: everybody gangsta til geohot gets the ban hammer ready
railander: monkaS @dvdutch
VanishBlox: 😳
brofessorbob: @railander Thanks for sharing. I'll have to take a deeper dive
matn1400: <3
SHAVEYY_: you should go to fortniteburger.net
Erixp: its a <3
b2kemann: covid is the new ban
harbad: protease is an enzyme
harbad: it breaks down proteins
robbsalm: oh shet
dvdutch: Dont go to that site
railander: @brofessorbob for laymen, scishow did a video on the paper
法國人: it looks like all it wants is love :D
VanishBlox: what are you trying to accomplish George?
0xC3301: 0xC3301 subscribed at Tier 1.
SHAVEYY_: @VanishBlox monkaS
GHFear: coagulating exception descriptors
0xC3301: 0xC3301 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
0xC3301: 0xC3301 gifted a Tier 1 sub to jagger_rsw!
harbad: protease enzymes are also used to separate strands of dna or rna to be transcribed
1shortking: @VanishBlox goodnight sweet prince
0xC3301: 0xC3301 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 2 in the channel!
0xC3301: 0xC3301 gifted a Tier 1 sub to jaegerbott!
0xC3301: 0xC3301 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 3 in the channel!
theonlymonkas: me
0xC3301: 0xC3301 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Jadess!
gabo_sk: anygifters?
Crypod: J smol MiniK
St47ik: protease enzyme for breaking down of proteins
klaazdw: w0w
iskjmss: knutOil
PistolPetez: i dont want a sub
gabs2819: Pogchamp
BrodatyWhiteBear: @gabo_sk You can be Kappa
法國人: @0xC3301 please don't gift me a sub, I try to keep my account vanilla
ipo___: Anything groundbreaking yet?
nvda9: !
railander: dodged EZ
CompestLive: I want a sub haha
canpake7: Where we at right now?
champ900: are you afraid of the heinekenvirus
torukmnk: torukmnk subscribed with Twitch Prime.
VanishBlox: I want a sub
samthedogg: I wanted a sub to this
smurfd0: https://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/article?id=10.1371/journal.pcbi.1000589
foti_kasparov: https://github.com/jorvis/biocode
VanishBlox: I want a tasty sub sandwich
robbsalm: ahahahah
railander: goatse WutFace
Atlas03: rooAww_RB
ragemaster999: @georgehotz https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gtr/genes/59272/
samthedogg: I get notifications when he streams
bichid69: dude, surely run some md
Atlas03: Kreygasm
bichid69: try jax-md
nvda9: George should make more music
robbsalm: it looks like death
bichid69: it looks cool
法國人: are proteins always symmetrical ?
St47ik: they're really like little bio-machines
Jadess: :)
St47ik: MrDestructoid
harbad: proteins are almost never symmetrical
ipo___: I wish I could read all text simply by double clicking... these cyborgs
keith282: @ragemaster999 we were looking at ACE2 yesterday
ProtoLambda: watching python streams instead of writing python, living the live, lol.
o______________________k: squad1 squad2 squadOK squad200
harbad: viruses usually have symmetry for structural strength, otherwise they wouldn't survive harsher environs
法國人: @harbad don't they tend to be ?
railander: what? pretty sure they have
railander: its been promoted everywhere
harbad: no
Usisuvach0: i just don't get it how it stays so long on surfaces
brofessorbob: Anyone know anybody in San Diego directly infected with Covid-19?
zangerxx: why is ubuntu better then windows ? is it only for vim ?
nvda9: I'm getting the walking dead vive here. people are wearing hazmat suit.
Backrub: biometrics
DevoE444: we need to inject the female covid 19 to kill it Kappa
gclawes: @georgehotz they have started folding@home covid projects, they just don't have a dedicated category for it yet
Crypod: what is Linus folding for then? monkaS
Backrub: do you get a notification on your phone when your password is used??
cutza: they have, it is under "any disease"
sal_gent: @georgehotz they told users to put the client in Any to help with COVID-19
Penguino138: Linus just started folding COVID
St47ik: Java DansGame
foti_kasparov: Java GUI sucks
0xmilan: 1st time I get to watch this live. it's 11 PM here
gclawes: if you run the folding agent you'll see covid work units come through
Fundlak: java FeelsOkayMan
gclawes: but you can't select for it yet
phrixus_bro: love java
Tsoding: Looks more like GTK 🤔
o______________________k: JAVA :D <3
NaT3z: How much does George know about these topics before beginning a project?
info303: they should advertise foldingathome on twitch for all the gamers to help out with covid-19
supnerdstv: whats he doing?
Nawelz: that cpu sound LUL
railander: noise PunOko
法國人: Java :D
info303: all those video cards
1shortking: its gonna blow monkaS
iGalactic: monkaS
Erixp: plague inc monkaS
robbsalm: nice
o______________________k: MAC B LUL LUL K PR LUL
gabo_sk: monkaS
samthedogg: a professor from my college made software for folding protiens
on111: monkaS
railander: yes LUL
samthedogg: https://ifestos.cse.sc.edu/software.php
lidermaury: who is monakS
KhanDesi: how do I play this stream at 2x speed?
edu4594: yes
Fundlak: yes
Erixp: yes
toast_ps: yes
gorgai: Yes
robbsalm: yes
javadragoniv: oh yeah
champ900: yes
marvluebke: yes just a little bit
Klairm_: How you doing during the lockdown? @georgehotz
joker2k999: looks like it.
ls111: i hear a fan
shlver: blue yeti nice LUL
djcows: it's fine
gabo_sk: FeelsGodMan
toast_ps: spit some bars george
Atlas03: its the same u use for asmr
Backrub: i have that too
GPlay97: GPlay97 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
emotional_baggage: >really nice microphone
railander: i think the issue is your apartment accoustics
TheBusbyBabes: CPU? i thought that was a plane taking off
ragemaster999: rapper btw LUL
perzibes: -380
gabo_sk: FeelsGoodMan
wainemier: started
emotional_baggage: >blue yeti
Nawelz: sounds like when my IDE is indexing files
SHAVEYY_: rape?
astr0nils: just find the vaccine already bro OMEGALUL
GoOnAli: blue yeti PepeLaugh
lidermaury: blue yeti is overrated
ICAntF331MyFAce: @railander 👈
djcows: get a seperate streaming pc
robg_10: whats harder hacking chrome os or corona
法國人: does he use zsh ?
harbad: What is interesting about viruses is that they are the only thing (almost alive) that has symmetry. but only in capsid proteins. spikes are not symmetrical, the genome is not symmetrical.
prafaeltsantos: @o______________________k it'a rlly old MBPR
St47ik: protein machines
wpreston: sounds like internal mic to me
1gonyali: I hearing the air sound now :D
c0alman: :D
brofessorbob: You should connect with your boy Siraj. He's been diving into bio hard.
ipo___: CPU cooling down
alycia: after this stream corona is defeated
bichid69: try ambermd
IndoPridePinoy: how do you know they are not using all those video cards to create another virus?
ragemaster999: the crypto miner is still running
gabo_sk: can you rap about coronavirus?
dvdutch: So CRIPSPR Cas9 is the future of healthcare
zangerxx: what is he trying to do ?
keith282: trap trap bernie sanders trap
VanishBlox: BAN BAN BAN BAN
cutza: ban
ipo___: what a botnet
Loutlot: Loutlot subscribed at Tier 1.
canpake7: Click on the siri icon to get the fan to speed down CarlSmile
VanishBlox: BAN
St47ik: isn't that for the Anti-virals
thickbordiga: turn on the WH press briefing just announced 100% tariffs on all trade with China
cockwizard69: monkaS
railander: monkaS
o______________________k: LUL
brofessorbob: You can block Ace2
jmp0ut: but then your heart stops
harbad: that's the easiest way to prevent the virus from replicating..
TheBusbyBabes: monkaS
cockwizard69: monkaS 👇
jmp0ut: so that doesnt work
DevoE444: does viruses have sexual orientation? KappaPride
gabs2819: monkaW
keith282: @zangerxx we're making a vaccine through python, only subscribers get it
GoOnAli: ive realised its physically impossible to code without touvhing your face
railander: @jmp0ut Jebaited
o______________________k: squadKey squadA
djcows: Hey Siri, find a cure for coronavirus
Klairm_: how you doing during the lockdown? everyone k?
dvdutch: stream animal crossing instead
zangerxx: @keith282 thank god im a no vaxxer anyways
matn1400: it does
lidermaury: everybody gangsta till ban
harbad: stopping spikes from binding with cells
tome_silva: worms
Waldoqq: @thickbordiga fake news
Crypod: so soap is just a bunch of warms?
Erixp: PogChamp
gabs2819: LUL
railander: PogChamp
Crypod: worms*
jmp0ut: why do you think ACE inhibitors are given to cardiac patients
gabo_sk: cool
robbsalm: hell yeah
kurokodairu_: Soap just takes away the fat thats holding together the virus .-.
yevheniiushtyk: why not just inject soap into your bloodstream?
WaeHaKe: PogChamp
maxpokerrr: so we just need to inject soap?
GoOnAli: git pull vaccine EZ
klaazdw: lol
theonlymonkas: LUL
harbad: lol sounds great
FurikuriYugi: Hey what's up buddy long time no see hope you've been good
topped123: hey george what are you doing
VitalyzedTv: LUL
railander: vaccine confirmed PogChamp
St47ik: git clone vaccine
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
dvdutch: github gon save the world
champ900: what are you doing
Wolvey: push the vaccine already
1ntegral_: git clone ...
keith282: git clone geohot/vaccine
iFAK: pull requests??? @georgehotz
railander: clipped and shipped
meemukeisariktk: what are you doing? @georgehotz
ipo___: I just joined ... is it true you made a vaccine???
logi6000: @georgehotz are you just doing this so you can fuck that pornstar that says she'll fuck who makes the cure
bichid69: take a shot of fairy liquid
on111: time to make pull requests for this vaccine
xrealyy: fuck off corona
alternatemule10: what are u doing
VitalyzedTv: hes developing a virtual vaccin
Kaotavn: WhAt ArE yOu DoInG?
Zipzipcekirge: soap the seas and let it rain soap easy cure
法國人: @topped123 he is creating a vaccin in Python
Crypod: oshiThink i see
b2kemann: WE ARE DRINKING TEA
xrealyy: fuck off corona get them soap
yeah_haey: can you find human 0daysq
alkiiis: where is the repo :)
c0alman: Pog
foti_kasparov: Do a vaccine with soap then
el_pirulote: @georgehotz i am a believer
tome_silva: vaccine
iFAK: any edgy forks?
Penguino138: loll
TheNakedFlame: Then put a non-sharing licence on it
jmp0ut: phospholipids
alphagainzzz: @logi6000 source?
harbad: it's from the host's cells
t_lokus: IBM had some protein simulation runs and they published some results I think
maxpokerrr: @georgehotz will i get corona if i drink corona bear?
St47ik: break the lipid membrane EZ Kappa
ragemaster999: the crypto miner is still running
1gonyali: SSSsss haa whaatt :D
theonlymonkas: T E A
brofessorbob: M == Membrane
THX1342: hello... how's the sciencing going
Atlas03: HTATS LEWD rooBlush
dvdutch: My dad said we should make an inhaler that just sprays lysol into your lungs
harbad: the lipid bilayer is from the host.
wpreston: Free course on the basics for those that need it https://www.coursera.org/learn/covid-19
nvda9: virus r just lifeless thing
joker2k999: oh man... lol
Kaotavn: same lol
NaT3z: Lol he's like a hacker Jeff Goldblum
railander: im learning FeelsGoodMan
St47ik: MOAR SOAP
法國人: that looks like a giant orgie to me
Crypod: that's why it's 20 seconds. give the soap more time!
railander: 4Head
21_savior: soap PogChamp
emotional_baggage: i feel like a monkey watching videos like this
joeyskitkat: Everyone safe back home George?
o______________________k: OMEGALUL
iFAK: SOAPPPp
viper262_: true
Penguino138: They're legs dancing lol
zol0: 4Head
Erixp: 4Head
cutza: so we just need a vaccine with soap
o______________________k: 4Head
Cornflays: LUL
canpake7: wait what
Akash_44: 4Head
Nawelz: 4Head JUST
h3x1e_: just inhale soap 4Head
St47ik: 4Head
snorting_milk: LOL
tome_silva: gg
champ900: EAT SOAP 2020
1gonyali: it looks like worm :D
murkythunder: start adding soap to every recipe
Atlas03: inhale soap u mean @georgehotz
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL
alkiiis: Genius
foti_kasparov: VACCINE WITH SOAP
ragemaster999: this guy is a genius PogChamp
canpake7: that does not make any sense
marvluebke: inhale soap = helth
gabo_sk: 4Head
logi6000: @alphagainzzz just look it up
zombiedigital: lmao carona cured "inject soap2
shlver: our cells also encased by bilipid membranes
St47ik: Inject soap 4Head
robbsalm: snort soap
PiroFloydian: No we need to INHALE soap
1ntegral_: Even better smoke soap
info303: do lines of soap
saintmthw: soap vapes Pog
o______________________k: just get better DUD 4Head
mrhdr: u die
gyne: intravenous soap drip PogChamp
brofessorbob: That's just crazy enough to work.
Crypod: big bwain
VanishBlox: EAT SOAAAP LUL OMEGAAA
djinnieee: Eureka!!!
Erixp: WE FOUND THE CURE PogChamp
railander: we found the vaccine PogChamp
joker2k999: lol
b2kemann: smoke soap
theonlymonkas: LUL genius
yevheniiushtyk: that's what i said NotLikeThis
brofessorbob: Inahle soap
saintmthw: soap vapes PogChamp
zol0: vaccine spotted PogChamp
kurokodairu_: Just use soap gas PogChamp
St47ik: almost 1k views PogChamp
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
法國人: inject soap in your blood XD
Fantasma56: JUST DRINK SOAP BRO 4Head
THX1342: drink liquid soap. check
ipo___: what pornstar was that? Kappa
snorting_milk: Snort soap!!
harbad: viruses are somewhere in between alive and dead, they do have metabolic properties, but only inside a host.
inDOObitablee: LUL
Zipzipcekirge: someone in my country ate soap with yoghurt and got sick :d
o______________________k: PogU
Crypod: LUL
Wolvey: LUL
Tsoding: LUL
Akash_44: LUL
Nawelz: this looks fishy 4Head
VanishBlox: INJECT HERION SOAP
Jehhred: EVERYONE STOCK UP ON SOAP!!!!!!
1gonyali: Soap injuction :D
Erixp: LULW
info303: wrap it up boys, we did it
dvdutch: My dad is literally trying to make an inhaler that sprays lysol into your lungs lmao
mj315: LUL
railander: coloring book FeelsGoodMan
C3r0C3r0C3r0: C3r0C3r0C3r0 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
jmp0ut: http://physicell.org/
brofessorbob: Well once in your body the virus envelops itself and hides in your cell.
PiroFloydian: SOAP VAPES
Penguino138: Is smoking weed during COVID times dangerous?
keith282: where's methhead mike? he would love that coloring page lmao
Loutlot: yay subbed
theonlymonkas: paint it
b2kemann: soap destorys the fat covering the rna
tome_silva: do something else
FurikuriYugi: [for l in m: c.append(soap)]
ipo___: GEORGE HUTZ
fireposeidoncx: @georgehotz is the waffle maker still available?
railander: the solution is driking tide pods after all LUL
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
Usisuvach0: @Penguino138 if you are at home it should not be
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
DevoE444: soap is patched by avast Kappa
VanishBlox: where is the github page for cure I wanna pull request
nvda9: washing your hands with cocaine cures corona
melike0009: @1gonyali selamin aleyküm
yrreseason: I wanna do hackintosh, is Hackintosh Gay ?
St47ik: LUL
0xC3301: Tide Pod Challenge 2020?
THX1342: LUL
eazyxlan: Favorite OS for coding?
smurfd0: thats fairly basic, was your hands with soap.. we was taught that when we were 1 year
iFAK: fuck they were on to something
Akash_44: LUL
PiroFloydian: THE ZOOMERS KNEW
canpake7: Are we building a self drinving anti covid-19 cell?
St47ik: Also bleach then Kappa
Crypod: actually don't do that yet, chat monkaS
lidermaury: dont make friends with people who dont have an iphone
yevheniiushtyk: 1k views almost Pog
joker2k999: sketchy breakdown?
AJVGAMES: omg its geohot
dinxpoy: great now they're gonna empty tide pods off the shelves
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 but will it affect my lungs ability to fight it if I eventually got it?
theonlymonkas: temple os
lordFOE: Is that why little kids are safe from the Corona?
lordFOE: They been suckin down tide pods?
iFAK: I JUST WANT TO BE PURE
SnadderG: I bet bleach would kill the bacteria that resides in your throat
cutza: tidepod shortages incoming
s3bastians: https://www.quora.com/If-soap-is-so-good-at-killing-coronavirus-COVID-19-then-why-dont-people-eat-soap-to-kill-the-virus sorry for long link
1gonyali: We move up Soap Injection from Sql Injection LUL
Usisuvach0: @Penguino138 last day i smoked weed was yesterday, and it might make you more vulnerable i am not really sure
harbad: ubuntu, mac, and windows are easily the best because of the community for beginners. But if you're serious, stick with Ubuntu or Mac.
melike0009: @1gonyali la gardaş sen hayırdır
Usisuvach0: but still smoking at home and alone
1gonyali: hi honey @melike0009
Usisuvach0: and not being in contact with others
brofessorbob: Soap injections wont work because a majority of the virons in your body is inside your cells.
Usisuvach0: i think it's ok
VanishBlox: next we start overflowing the DNA of the virus
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 Been on a week break a bit out of paranoia. I go to the store rarely but if it takes up to 2 weeks to infect me....
brofessorbob: Review https://www.technologynetworks.com/immunology/articles/understanding-the-lytic-cycle-what-are-the-steps-310621
法國人: I think by ubuntu he means linux
edu4594: btw i user arch
melike0009: @1gonyali hi
foti_kasparov: "you wash your hands with soap, which makes your hand slippery, causing the virus to fall into the sink and down the drain."
VanishBlox: I use win 10
1gonyali: what a nice place ha honey? @melike0009
sondreal: sondreal subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 8 months! yes
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
nvda9: he doesn't post anything on twitter but has a verified account
harbad: Windows is okay, just gets in the way sometimes.
ELEMENTiQ1337: finally i catched your stream
aknaveg13: Just watched your interview with Lex Friedman
xxdvxx: What if we can use accelerator instead of killer? That mean faster symptons and more quarantine.
Usisuvach0: @foti_kasparov not only that but soap kills the outer membrane of the virus
b2kemann: cmd is bad though
THX1342: @georgehotz did you put that notebook on github?
liiiiiig0: !uptime
Usisuvach0: so it won't be able to survive or spread anymore
gyne: E
St47ik: E
Nopy1: Are coronas spheres, and not 2D-crowns/halos/rings?
zol0: TRUE LUL
railander: E
dvdutch: E
joker2k999: he's been live about an hour.
Tsoding: If it compiles it works PogChamp
St47ik: Any Truers LUL
liiiiiig0: @joker2k999 thanks
logi6000: just skipped online school
zol0: any budget true lulwers LUL
xxdvxx: What if we can use accelerator instead of vaccine? That mean faster symptons and more quarantine.
nvda9: why am I watching this? it's 3:54 am here.
VanishBlox: if lua then print("best language") end
t_lokus: idk much, but IBM supercomputer got some combinations to get in-between the "pre-fusion spike": https://science.sciencemag.org/content/367/6483/1260.full
o______________________k: @nvda9 making a cure and posting it on github :)
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
ELEMENTiQ1337: ELEMENTiQ1337 subscribed at Tier 1.
harbad: BOOM
bichid69: wait, what do these proteins do?
1gonyali: bizim işler böyle işte @melike0009
Landowner555: YES
Erixp: PogChamp
murkythunder: re Pog
St47ik: PogChamp
gabo_sk: Pog
edu4594: lul]
sondreal: PogChamp
edu4594: lul
railander: PogChamp
neogloom: Pog
Coraxxi: 5Head shit
edu4594: LUL
harbad: You got it @georgehotz
VanishBlox: pog
iFAK: POIFECT
Usisuvach0: i don't know in which way computers will help fight the virus, there are lot of tests that needs to be done
railander: vaccine soon bois PogChamp
theonlymonkas: DansGame
St47ik: Biohacking confirmed PogChamp
khiomtv: CTF it
luismario0o: can coronavirus turn into a good person??
joker2k999: making his own covid-library lol
gyne: integrating the coronavirus into the blockchain PogChamp
railander: D:
melike0009: @1gonyali eyi eyi
harbad: hahaha!!!!
ICAntF331MyFAce: alkXD
robbsalm: ahahah
gabo_sk: LUL
mj315: LUL
thebiggaeboi: if his programming does something with this virus im going to be impressed
St47ik: CTC Capture the corona
VanishBlox: LUL
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
robbsalm: savage
cutza: are you going to rebuild it so it kills people more effectively?
thebiggaeboi: im also very lost
saygan_: what's my man working on?
Aecxlol: !uptime
Crypod: more cross-field collabs are needed to solve world problems
Usisuvach0: corona virus is obfuscated :D
Quad___lol: import Vaccine, Bio from CIA
railander: monkaS 👉 cutza
joker2k999: he's looking for 'something cool' in the genome of the corona'
harbad: I know where you're coming from @georgehotz . I'm a CS grad with a minor in biology, bio students don't tend to be super sharp
iFAK: git pull vaccine
Kmerck313: ^^^^Bann
VanishBlox: @saygan_ making a cure and posting it on github
Fulk33: @saygan_ making a vaccine for covid19 and putting it on github
nvda9: good night.
BrynjolfTwitch: Hey George! What you are coding?
St47ik: @nvda9 gn
Usisuvach0: trump is live
logi6000: from CIA_DATA import covid19-plans, vaccine
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
luismario0o: nmmmmmmmm,,.............,,,,,,,,,,,..---------
Killeraing: why are videos only for subscribers?
harbad: reverse engineering covid-19
Erixp: hes making a cure and posting it on github :)
railander: the glyco 4Head
Crypod: it's sweetened?
VanishBlox: @brynjolftwitch a cure to post on github
Waldoqq: trump address on now @georgehotz
St47ik: @Killeraing you can find VODs at comma ai archive youtube channel
dinxpoy: @BrynjolfTwitch the man is literally coding a vaccine and putting it up for free because greedy companies dont wanna do it themselves
THX1342: I think glycoproteins are proteins fat
theonlymonkas: twitchslam
St47ik: isn't glyco sugars?
harbad: true
Samplafied: FrankerZ
railander: you DONT listen to mr trump? 4Head
iFAK: whatcha drinking??
yevheniiushtyk: Not enough ice! LUL
iFAK: oj?
razr22: glycogen
joker2k999: lol not twitchSlam.
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
VanishBlox: THE HOSPITALS ARE A SCAM! BUY TVS
SnadderG: When are you running for president?
dvdutch: If you wanna become a populist listen to him
St47ik: This is TwitchCoV
konradmad: lmfao!!
edu4594: https://twitter.com/OrwellNGoode/status/1240276031682097154/photo/1
railander: trump is funny at least LUL
iFAK: XD
gabo_sk: this is mr robot 2?
MacoNighto: what is he trying to do ?
dvdutch: Vermin Supreme couldve stopped COVID
iFAK: yet Biden is getting the nominee
St47ik: Twitch-CoV-2
theonlymonkas: THE COQ FILES
Micazeera: Hi dude, you can look this? I'm brazilliam developer and i wanna know what to improve the codes https://github.com/Micazera/CoronaVirus
harbad: hey @georgehotz you're my hero, lol
noxpppp: @georgehotz what are you talking about ???
LaneBoyR6: Hack trumps accounts and take him down :D
murkythunder: hes so dumb he cant lie
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kappa
Crypod: he doesn't lie. he thinks it's the truth KEKW
Biniano7: Would you be able to make a program for trading stocks?
railander: you cant lie if you dont know the truth LUL
logi6000: yo Biden is all of Trump's bad parts but creepy. like pedo creepy
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: He does lie
meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeenz: could you tell me why are you doing this? just bored in quarantine?
zombiedigital: kkonavirus-19
dvdutch: He could definitely make that
joker2k999: m-16 = shits getting real.
harbad: he's very old fashioned business, that's all
Crypod: we just need someone he likes to feed him the truth
mascer95: just because it's the truth in his mind, doesn't mean it's not factually incorrect...
SHAVEYY_: if trump made linux we'd all be using linux
VanishBlox: Donald trump is biologist confirmed
jagger_rsw: @mascer95 depending on definition of "fact" :)
Crypod: that's a nasty question Kappa
St47ik: almost 1K views
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
railander: i think he's just really stupid
harbad: ambulance?
logi6000: @shaveyy_ but Linux would have a 200 dollar license
yrreseason: George wtf are you doing right now
ELEMENTiQ1337: dats true
DecayingSkullz: HDR is freaking out
logi6000: @georgehotz those sirens are the Marshal's with the m16
Penguino138: George is making a vaccine to upload on github
mascer95: I believe if you actively avoid the truth to not be lying... it kind of makes it lying... just my two cents
harbad: reverse engineering covid-19
KhanDesi: lol come on, he objectively lies. Obviously, he also believes his truths. But he also lies
Jehhred: I wish I knew that in school. I can't be an labelled wrong if I'm ignorant'
Crypod: yuuuge
railander: monkaS 👉 @logi6000
St47ik: Yuge
gabo_sk: reverse engineering the coronavirus aka save the world
St47ik: Hugh Mungus
Danilok100: trump does not care about the truth
Pasha_Pechkin: stop politic plz, letz hack the corona
murkythunder: TRUEEE
Crypod: oshiThink i see
Klairm_: do you remember demonhades from teamhades? @georgehotz
theonlymonkas: LUL
mascer95: @jagger_rsw of course it depends on the subject. but there are quite a few topics where we have a factual truth (usually science)
VanishBlox: The police are coming George, we are doing too much bioterrorisim
railander: although they should LUL
St47ik: NotLikeThis
harbad: it's all about getting into your head and giving you what you want.
harbad: feeding you a line and drawing you in.
VitalyzedTv: THATS TERRIBLE REPORTING LUL
fwef64: can someone get me up to date with what's been going on so far?
mascer95: @georgehotz I believe if you actively avoid the truth to not be lying... it kind of makes it lying... just my two cents
Penguino138: SAD
jagger_rsw: @mascer95 i don't want to get into philosophical discussion of truth :), but the only thing everyone can probably agree is the law of excluded middle, everything else is pretty much conventional :)
harbad: the world is overreacting @fwef64
dvdutch: It entrapment
St47ik: Reverse engineering politics Kappa
foti_kasparov: Media sucks amn
railander: ye but that's what he signed up for as president, some people need that assurance
harbad: that's what's happening.
tornix98: did trump pay off a pornstar?
railander: it's a panic
Mlewii: you should actually debate destiny
thebootystrangler: how you gonna reveal
St47ik: but the fear is when it mutates NotLikeThis
klaazdw: lol
pomprocks: it's probably spreading a lot faster than they realize
Crypod: re-engineered SARS?dun duuun
sl4ckerman: !uptime
Kyoto_o: death rate is not low, 300k to 10k deaths was 4.5% yesterday
SnadderG: who hasnt payed off a porn star
alycia: he is close to a vaccine
gabo_sk: monkaS fbi
Crypod: LUL
jmp0ut: if they put it on paper how is it not considered prostitution
railander: @Mlewii i don't think he cares about what anything destiny has to say
gyne: sars 2 electric boogaloo
Kmerck313: Lol you would too
FurikuriYugi: fear weekends your immune system
jmp0ut: it's a strange juxtaposition
peter35_: that 'deep state dept' line the other day was hilarious
dinxpoy: it's pretty serious when ppl in their 60's die because they have something simple like hypertension
mascer95: @jagger_rsw tell that to the scienctists working on quantum computing. law of the excluded middle will just be another convention :P
Kyoto_o: is it low to fixed number 7b people on earth, yes, is it low to total amount of 300k? no
pomprocks: there could be 300k people infected. or 3 million. they don't know
osuiw: @Crypod TARS !?!?!
FurikuriYugi: *weakens
viper262_: out of closed cases 13% deaths
Loutlot: legit asmr
THX1342: reports from doctors is that with treatment, people are relatively fine. but while in treatments things are BAD.... like coughing blood felling like you are drowning and needing to be restrained, bad.
logi6000: did he wash his hands?
foti_kasparov: @sl4ckerman Not Modbot found :P George hates bots
Crypod: *flushes and washes*
Nopy1: why not use IDA pro instead of that jupyter BS CarlSmile
Dai_Vern0n: he's he on adderall ? we seem's so active and productive
esence: imagine being a virus and getting cucked by based Georgy
astr0nils: He washed his hands Kreygasm
Penguino138: Count for 20 seconds
thebootystrangler: how u gonna reverse engineer a virus
VanishBlox: covid devolves it's spreading points and then invests them into lethality 😳😳
dorkmo: only washed hands for 10 secondss
gyne: not 20 seconds!!!!!
tornix98: he lied about paying off a pornstar
Crypod: @osuiw MARS monkaS
hawsh: he didnt wash his hands
Tornyl: hello george
harbad: @georgehotz Covid-19 could fix social security issues for the US. I do know that.
joker2k999: lol
GODaruu: the death rate is just low at the moment, its still an ongoing situation so it will change once we get to the end
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
logi6000: he washed his hands
gyne: george hotz is cancelled
jagger_rsw: Not being US-person, the interesting thing about the current wave of trump-like statesmen (bolsonario etc.) is that previously presidents could be shown as role-models for kids. Now, not so :)
1gonyali: microphone is very very good maannn :D :D :D
gabo_sk: wash your hands
foti_kasparov: Didn't wash hands
St47ik: With more infection and spread the rate of transcription errors can make it mutate NotLikeThis
Mlewii: @railander yeah probably, i would just love to watch it
gabo_sk: please
xrealyy: the problem with this is spreading like chat said, numbers might increase really fast, people are dying in their houses due lack of space in hospitals ;<
Biniano7: @georgehotz can u make a program trading stocks with high percentage gain?
Voctolm: it's important to understand how he reacts to it
erichtp: touching face monkaS
esence: wash hands? Do you guys pee on your hands?
Crypod: he did wash his hands. i heard it
harbad: @georgehotz this virus could fix social security issues for the US. I do know that.
railander: dont touch face monkaS
joker2k999: pee could be the cure...
Jehhred: Brad Pitt: 'Well uh, from my multi-million dollar mansion, I have no idea..'
theonlymonkas: 12 monkey
railander: not 20 secs monkaS
zombiedigital: @georgehotz whens the cure ready
recursive_x: still looking up adrenochrome ?
dj_vicio: what??? 20 seconds!
ELEMENTiQ1337: get your hands out of your face george monkaS
Leon_Trolltsky: @biniano7 of course he CAN, will he? Idk. For you to use? Likely not. Haha
logi6000: Geo did you buy Bitcoin. prices are good now
gabo_sk: f
NicksizAdam: @georgehotz hi george, an offtopic question, i'm bored in fkn house and wanna make self-driving application by screen capturing of a racing game called crew 2 by ubisoft. do you have any suggestion as a starting point?
VanishBlox: George has the virus guys😔
theonlymonkas: or is it
peter35_: if the IC spooks hate trump he's can't be that bad
ICAntF331MyFAce: :O
mascer95: @jagger_rsw i agree. and i don't really want to discuss it any further. I also find George rather inspiring. I just find his statements of the past few minutes rather questionable...
yaus_baus: wew
Fundlak: <20 = deth monkaS
theonlymonkas: :0
BrynjolfTwitch: this is the part two of corona project right?There is a video about this on the comma.ai YouTube channel
liranisme: @georgehotz how do I become a cyber expert?
gyne: when a mommy protein and a daddy protein love each other very much...
THX1342: @georgehotz did we figure out how the quine works? how the replicating section of the code makes the rest of the virus?
dinxpoy: cray how nature do dat TriHard
dvdutch: we gon break 1k viewers
logi6000: @nicksizadam sentdex did something similar with GTA. look it up
harbad: all of the green spikes are viral, the rest are left over from the host cell.
dontusethiscode: Remember when @georgehotz made that cooking stream. The birth of Corona
harbad: for the most part.
Gr3ybearddd: @liranisme study cyber security topics..
dj_vicio: how's this program be used?
theonlymonkas: GTA 6
Fundlak: the protein printer go brrrrrr
logi6000: xd
j3ckerd: What's @georgehotz IQ?
NicksizAdam: @logi6000 yeah but it works poorly
railander: it is different than flu but demoraphic most affected are elderly, especially in risk of death
harbad: glycoproteins are usually markers with carbs on the end
saixj: appreciate the streams keep up the good work
VanishBlox: INSERT MAGENTA
Famousix: !commands
railander: 40 or younger very low risk
St47ik: sugars
THX1342: I would guess the fatty "shell" is the glycoprotein
logi6000: @nicksizadam he did that on purpose. it was made to be like a gta player would drive
Penguino138: Almost 1k viewers guys!
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
foti_kasparov: This is the first step of reverse engineering the simulation
THX1342: forgot the name we learnt yesterdat
St47ik: they say it already had mutated once and there are two strands already
harbad: the envelope is from the host cell
dvdutch: Make a public repo @georgehotz
jmp0ut: it tricks the body into thinking it's sugar
xrealyy: is this channel gonna hit 1k live viewers for the first time?
logi6000: look up fluid mosaic model
Nopy1: ah, so high fructose glucose proteins now wtf.
viper262_: 1k
Penguino138: 1k
Nopy1: use real sugar
jmp0ut: then slips in with the sugar
jmp0ut: like a porn star
jmp0ut: in my bedroom
b2kemann: remember the time there were news papers AND gossip magazines?
harbad: @georgehotz the 'copy machine' is the genome itself.
champ900: 1K viewers POG
recursive_x: wouldn't take long if something similar was made
VanishBlox: I want to have sex
murkythunder: `it would be really helpful if you had a bio friend to ask these questions to to give you the faster answer than googling
pedrosantos867: are he for real?
harbad: it doesn't kill the cell right away.
dvdutch: The COVID cure will be written in Swift
Penguino138: 1k
VanishBlox: it's deepfaks
harbad: it blebs off pieces of the host membrane
lordBzzl: automatons being automatons to other automatons
GHFear: It would be safer to write it in Rust @dvdutch
dj_vicio: that's how the flu medicines work. they risrupt the copying mechanism.
bichid69: 1k viewers boiiiiiii!
dj_vicio: but coronavirus is not very similar to the flu
THX1342: You could also break the virus' keys so they can't get past the cell's door (i.e. breaking the spike)
Kyoto_o: you have to be a virologist
avgandrew: !uptiem
brittonx2: cells immune to exploit is the way!
dj_vicio: unlike what news say (lie)
avgandrew: !uptime
railander: i dont think "bio" is enough to know this shit, probably have to ask a virologist
harbad: it applies to all viruses
Crypod: can the virus survive in a body with high blood alcohol? curvyHmm
theonlymonkas: PixelBob
r3mote: welcome back :-)
dvdutch: *Novel* coronavirus
GHFear: @Crypod no
murkythunder: yh hotz would be like a hacker friend, he needs a bio friend which is like a version of him, but into bio instead
St47ik: ACE2 receptors are used for people with hypertension to reduce blood pressure
Kyoto_o: would you monetize cure if you have found it? @georgehotz
harbad: but covid-19 itself is a membrane-bound protein.
theonlymonkas: 1K
dontusethiscode: @Crypod yes the virus is an alcoholic
bichid69: isn't the whole thing the capsid?
Crypod: LUL
Hawklite: how do you tell the "copy machine" to only not copy corona cells instead of all cells though?
logi6000: well what if instead of doing all this work. we just hack the CIA
mascer95: @Crypod yes. It does not enter the blood as far as I know
railander: 1k viewers PogChamp
fwef64: How certain are we that he decoded the DNA correctly?
logi6000: it would be easier
NicksizAdam: @logi6000 i also tested a pretrained model that gives predictions as degrees but cannot convert the output to discrete classes, "w", "a", "d", properly. i have degree to pressing time conversion problem
b2kemann: covid: twitter: datascientists assemble!
knickerbockerr: What is he doin
Crypod: interesting
GHFear: @Hawklite the copy machine is in the virus, not the body.
bravech: bravech subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
harbad: reverse engineering covid-19
Penguino138: The copy machine is in the office
BrynjolfTwitch: !time
jmp0ut: every cell membrane does
VanishBlox: @knickerbockerr he is making a cure to post on github
knickerbockerr: Pogu
dj_vicio: is he RE it or creating a program ?
dontusethiscode: 1k viewers pog stream
mascer95: @fwef64 I would say pretty certain. Otherwise the development of tests wouldn't have been this quick
jmp0ut: cytosolic fluid hacks
pedrosantos867: !uptime
St47ik: @georgehotz ACE2 receptors are used for people with hypertension to reduce blood pressure so it's not easy to stop the exploit NotLikeThis
railander: @knickerbockerr finding a vaccine and posting it on github PogChamp Kappa
FargioFarmani: finally am catching a livestream!
THX1342: @georgehotz that image under replication ilustrates the 3 main parts of the code. 1 creates the envelope and 2 create the capsid (from what I understood)
Nedeljko99: Marko, uloguje se Marko, uloguje se Marko, uloguje se Marko, uloguje se Marko, uloguje se Marko, uloguje se
lordBzzl: seemingly simplistic machinery
o______________________k: anyone buy the mac pro thoughts ?
Betazz: do you think the virus mutates?
saixj: are you going to reach out to any pharmaceutical companies if you find some good leads
Lizardan: @o______________________k it's great
jmp0ut: @georgehotz look up cytosol
Tramb0x: brief tinder
deep5: what machine is he using
harbad: @georgehotz the virus is encapsulated by the bilayer from the host, which protects it from the environment. the bilayer is also how it tricks the host cells to pull it into them.
railander: all viruses mutate quickly afaik @Betazz
Betazz: oh
FargioFarmani: I have the 16' and its great!
inexitu: the virus does mutate
o______________________k: @Betazz mutates everytime it enters a new hosts i believe
Usisuvach0: @Nedeljko99 sta ti je bre mentalen eden
Usisuvach0: sto spamsh ti ebam facata
logi6000: let's just hack the CIA instead. copy the cure. and also while your in just find the aliens locations
jmp0ut: find my location
Crypod: @o______________________k get slightly higher spec than you need. don't want to get stuck with a machine u can't upgrade when chrome decides it needs more ram
VanishBlox: so we can clap alien cheecks
jmp0ut: signal hack and life memories being sidelined for pennies on the dollar
logi6000: @vanishblox you already knew it
jmp0ut: brainjacked victim
Fundlak: he is already watching through your camera :)
pedrosantos867: Which keybord are you using?
Betazz: dayum tho New York's the epicenter just like division predicted
theonlymonkas: BAN
harbad: once inside the cell, the membrane is shed, the genome is then activated and the viral body releases enzymes to break down the host dna and begin making replicating.
ShakDiesel: LUL
railander: !specs
法國人: @pedrosantos867 read the bio
mascer95: @pedrosantos867 pls read the rules
pedrosantos867: I'm sorry
harbad: enzymes** i forgot to say
Crypod: !bio
theonlymonkas: LUL
bichid69: these may be proteins already in the cell
deed02392: do you have an end goal in mind or is this just for curiosity sake?
St47ik: @georgehotz attempt to stop the exploit https://www.bmj.com/content/368/bmj.m810/rr-2
Nedeljko99: @Usisuvach0 sry bro
logi6000: hack the CIA instead and get the vaccine
Klairm_: when did you started this? @georgehotz
ELEMENTiQ1337: pepeHmm
o______________________k: @Crypod nah im not going to get one. was just curious. 6-8k is insane IMO but I wish :)
bichid69: I dunno I'm just a chemist not a biologist
vaskogomez87: @georgehotz can you unlock the vods for people that can subscribe pls?
gyne: ??? it definitely does
Crypod: @o______________________k even better LUL
harbad: the virus hijacks the host's replication
vaskogomez87: *cant
logi6000: from CIA_DATA import vaccine, alien_locater
法國人: !uptime Klairm_
seffieinsane: can i give u a suggestion. can u just look into how our own body does not kill itself :)
mascer95: @vaskogomez87 I believe most of his VODs are uploaded to youtube
squiggly_nibba: @vaskogomez87 commaiarchive on youtube has all the vods
Ozonemaster: there are a lot of reasons to take rna and write rna
法國人: nvm
seffieinsane: our body can take care of the rest
avgandrew: @logi6000 KAPPA
Klairm_: @法國人 not this stream, where did he started researching about covid-2019
St47ik: attempt to stop the exploit https://www.bmj.com/content/368/bmj.m810/rr-2
harbad: no, canada
noobaj: LUL
Ozonemaster: Ur cells use RNA for the creation of any protein
vaskogomez87: @mascer95 @squiggly_nibba wow, thanks guys
railander: they stopped naming pathogens after real places
法國人: @Klairm_ pretty sure he started from this stream tho
seffieinsane: @georgehotz look into how to body reacts and stop it from killing then the virus will get stopped anyway
Klairm_: @法國人 and what's the actual goal?
St47ik: using ACE2 inhibitors like in ppl with hypertension
lidermaury: ban me
Apocalyptic0ne: https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2010/05/100528210736.htm
Lizardan: I have a feeling George is going to end up enrolling in Med School after this
jmp0ut: you would have to use an ACE blocker and synthetic sugars to survive as well as fluid breathing equipment
Betazz: viruses and antibodies
logi6000: @klairm_ to find the cure so the pornstar will fuck him
jmp0ut: PFC ventilator
jmp0ut: fluid filling the lungs is not fun or cheap
Klairm_: @logi6000 what xDD
o______________________k: squadCozy squadL
railander: @Lizardan nah that's not as interesting as AI
法國人: @Klairm_ sorry I think he made a stream yesterday for 4 hjours, Just trying to understand more how the virus works I suppose
smurfd0: kinda weird, like Sars, didnt really hear much about that besides some elite athleats got killed by it...
liiiiiig0: LUL
Lizardan: @railander true
Crypod: just go to udemy LUL
St47ik: ScamSchool
jmp0ut: its a scam by oldie foldies
o______________________k: pay 400k in debt Pog
Fundlak: LUL
jmp0ut: fuck that noise
Orestes13: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
lidermaury: med school and law school are cool
jmp0ut: just become a porn star
recursive_x: lmfao
deep5: LUL
jmp0ut: and launder money
Square___: guys, what is he doing lol
Muzyd: PREACH
jmp0ut: what pr0nhub?
inDOObitablee: Ban
St47ik: Medicine in python
aleman578: nice
logi6000: @klairm_ a pornstar said that she'll fuck who find the cure
harbad: agreed, that's why I'm not in biology anymore.
theonlymonkas: BAN
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
AndreiKnight: sit down sherlock
Betazz: agreed
AresD7: They found medicine in Japan: avigan, seems to be working
dj_vicio: fuck doctors
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: ???
aleman578: hi
jmp0ut: what about just brain in a box living cybernetic fantasies
d3adb33: finally I join live from Germany! Nice to see it live!!!!!
railander: vaccine on github soon PogChamp
jmp0ut: or coming to life for war
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
murkythunder: cure the coronavirus (python tutorial)
Kjjj11223344: Hell yeah!!
yaus_baus: 3d printed vaccines
Smube: u cure corona yet
dvdutch: Open sourced COVID
re1mond: Hi, Tony Star!
yaus_baus: yeet the corona away
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 So should I avoid smoking for a few days/weeks until COVID blows over? I'm in Idaho only 30-40 cases so far
inDOObitablee: @Square___ hes making a vaccine and postingit on github
jmp0ut: have you seen engineering yeast to produce opiates thoug
gogenhub: Thats what im trying with my startup: https://genhub.co/
dvdutch: Make a COVID library
Leon_Trolltsky: Genius
socialnotsocial: thoughts on university?
jmp0ut: you can create more heroin than afghan in a week
VanishBlox: hey George I found a YouTube video by the WHO on how the virus works https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ
dj_vicio: doctors live to scam people with vaccines and insurance $$ . Hackers are the real heroes!
jmp0ut: it's already done
b2kemann: print infinite burgers
Usisuvach0: @Penguino138 i won't smoke for 2 weeks from now on
lordBzzl: thought emporium always pushing the bar
AresD7: Search for Avigan
Betazz: even coding how to make machines smell
Usisuvach0: i am from Macedonia 115 cases so far
railander: Jebaited
Usisuvach0: 30 new today
Betazz: LUL
jmp0ut: chinese labs produce heroin for so dirt cheap it's throwing all of CIA's efforts down the drain
法國人: LMAO
Akash_44: Jebaited
klaazdw: lol
liiiiiig0: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LULW
bokeee_: LUL
St47ik: LUL
youngsachi: LUL
Snowlav: Jebaited
jmp0ut: no more drug moneys
Digital_donger: :tf:
harbad: nice
deep5: KEKW
Nyt1k: Jebaited
PiroFloydian: Jebaited LUL
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 So basically wait till the voluntary quarantine blows over then re-analyse?
harbad: very nice
logi6000: XD
foti_kasparov: KEKW
smurfd0: <3
Greaser_1: :-)
St47ik: LUL LUL LUL
Muzyd: GOTTEM
VanishBlox: GOTEM
b2kemann: loool
Julll: LUL
Kustex: hehehe
xxdvxx: GOTTTTEM
THX1342: YES!
Crypod: Clap Clap
recursive_x: lol
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Jebaited Jebaited
logi6000: let's fucking go boia
deep5: Clap
Usisuvach0: @Penguino138 who knows man
AresD7: U know about avigan @georgehotz ?
Rairden1: the 2012 BBC doc (life inside a cell) is excellent
THX1342: I linked his channel dozens of times yesterday :D
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
FurikuriYugi: PJSalt
lordBzzl: what happens if you get Copper ions in your body
THX1342: glad you watched ity
Usisuvach0: just don't smoke
Digital_donger: he hates us Jebaited
dvdutch: LMAO
Crypod: it's not even April 1st wolfCry
Usisuvach0: repair your lungs a bit
jmp0ut: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4924617/
St47ik: always check the link LUL
Betazz: this is getting out of hand tho
VanishBlox: 4Head 4Head 4Head 4Head
abhinavneelam: what you engineering now?
lordBzzl: Copper is bad for viruses and such
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 I don't NEED to I just wanted to make sure I wasn't being paranoid instead of safe
re1mond: !uptime
jmp0ut: Complete biosynthesis of opioids in yeast Stephanie Galanie,# Kate Thodey,^ Isis J. Trenchard,^ Maria Filsinger Interrante,^ and Christina D. Smolke^*
Kustex: can i get corona through this stream?
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 Thanks of course
bravech: HahaHide
gogenhub: i meant turning biology into information tech
jmp0ut: gang gang
Apocalyptic0ne: "For example, the SARS virus also requires a lipid-rich environment for its replication, so her lab now is working with SARS researchers on determining what lipid is necessary for that virus's replication." https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2010/05/100528210736.htm
dvdutch: Should I do my homework due at midnight or help cure COVID with geohot?
Usisuvach0: well like i said i smoked yesterday
Crypod: can we make the zinc rust and break off? oshiThink
th3_g3nt3lman: TheIlluminati
Usisuvach0: but today no
DevoE444: @georgehotz hows is the virus react to PH
pedrovictortech: What's the actual goal?
SHAVEYY_: geo creates virus
TheBusbyBabes: you dont have it D:
re1mond: !up
SHAVEYY_: sells the solution Kappa
Usisuvach0: i spit all the mucus that creates the smoke today
Usisuvach0: and i feel a bit cleaner
noobaj: is there any data on people who've recovered/immune to the virus?
lordBzzl: nanobot with a copper backpack
SHAVEYY_: no
jmp0ut: hire robots to package and sell all the drugs and rig them with heavy ordinance as well as self replicating and fabricating more to hold them together as well as beryllium plating the facility so that radar has problems penetrating it
Betazz: create a virus to kill the virus
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 I don't get that crazy of mucus from smoking weed
SnadderG: No proof that you go immune @noobaj
jmp0ut: see a black box with robots do not go near it
JLO_: wa hassan mach m followi
icyvran: Mutations
lordBzzl: @Betazz that's an idea, what happens after?
Usisuvach0: it's nasty @Penguino138
jmp0ut: it's a nuke spot
theonlymonkas: saint laurent
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 Maybe get a filtered bong and slow down :p
Klairm_: there are people that got infected again after got recovered btw @georgehotz
Betazz: @lordbzzl I dk LUL
logi6000: George so when is the military coming with the M16's due to marshall law
THX1342: can you share this notebook right now @georgehotz ?
recursive_x: how long to learn the codes
jadams: ratirlSalute
Usisuvach0: ok @Penguino138 but here i smoke joints
stuartlz: @Klairm_ Fake news
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 Yeah joins are much harsher. But we should probably all avoid any form of it till we have more clear answers.
PiroFloydian: so basically hes translating covid19 to code so he can hack it
Usisuvach0: yeah
THX1342: LUL
Klairm_: @stuartlz not fake news dude, happened here on spain
Usisuvach0: i am stopping to smoke
yaus_baus: machine learning powered molecular synthesizer for psychoactive drogs
harbad: @georgehotz the best way is to stop the virus by inhibiting its glycoprotein spikes from attaching to the receptors that start host cell endocytosis.
lordBzzl: @Betazz could be an issue...
Usisuvach0: i got some weed on aside
THX1342: smashing that stripped ELF
Usisuvach0: hidden good
bebytesback: This is serious some of the best content on twitch, Thanks @georgehotz
habituss: Hey, I just got here, can someone explain what is the program he is reverse engineering?
mandjevant: Yo what's he doing?
Usisuvach0: but i won't smoke some weeks
theonlymonkas: BAN
harbad: covid-19 is what he's reverse engineering.
VanishBlox: BAN BAN
Lizardan: @habituss coronavirus
Penguino138: @habituss He is making a vaccine to upload to github
recursive_x: not even a doctor can figure that
mandjevant: but... but... how
deed02392: @harbad is making sense
Penguino138: @Usisuvach0 I started my break on 3/15, got plenty of alochol
noobaj: @klairm_ the test's were wrong
ackxhpaez: Self-driving virus?
habituss: How the fuck is corona a program lol ?
yaus_baus: were hackin rona
Penguino138: Rona season bb
lordBzzl: viral envelopes need to go on strike
THX1342: everything is code in the simulation, habituss
harbad: nucleocapsid is just the body of the virus. it's just inside the lipid bilayer.
Usisuvach0: @habituss we are all programs
VanishBlox: @mandjevant he's geohots, he jailbroke the iPhone so he can jailbreak the virus too
Usisuvach0: our brain is the same as computer 0;s and 1;s
gyne: genetic...code
againstZzZ: habituss dna is basically algorithm
pogu: @habituss It's a thing that is programmed to do things in response to things, literally program
Kustex: @habituss we're all in the simulation mate
FurikuriYugi: Corona is a Mexican beer lol
Apocalyptic0ne: a virus is an organic hacker come to take your shit
DevoE444: DNA is computer like technology but more advanced @habituss
theonlymonkas: LUL
murkythunder: dna would be a data structure
esence: atom is a primitive data type
THX1342: wait til the IOT folk get a wiff of Biotech....
habituss: Alright, but where does the code comes from ?
b2kemann: wallstreet hits the floor
Apocalyptic0ne: rna sequence
lordBzzl: quarks are the primitive data type
harbad: it is the part of the virus that holds the genome and (in the case of covid-19) it is very weak. which is why it doesn't survive outside of a host for very long.
VanishBlox: dna is kinda like binary
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz thoughts on university?
bichid69: engineering boiiiiiiiiii
harbad: dna is only slightly more sophisticated than binary
THX1342: socialnotsocial his thoughts: it's a scam
robg_10: Does QIRA work with this ?
SHAVEYY_: genes are like binary
SHAVEYY_: they can be on or off
PiroFloydian: dna is basically in base 4
dvdutch: school is definitely a scam
VanishBlox: is dna like bytecode?
harbad: it's more like base 8 because of dna and rna
chusiv: He took the genome, translated it into RNA and then by isolating bytes he gets to split it into the different components of the virus.
Betazz: is there no such thing as a good virus?
Betazz: like bacteria
dvdutch: Is quaternary actually used for anything?
harbad: and codons then make it even more complex
lordBzzl: universe is weird, simple things become complex things
St47ik: @Betazz viruses aren't good or bad
recursive_x: I'm confused
VanishBlox: they just wanna fuck mate
St47ik: they're just genetic data moving around
theonlymonkas: NotLikeThis
THX1342: Betazz I think all viruses kill the host cells in their replication so I would say: no
Kustex: what is he trying to do?
foti_kasparov: university is the place people that seek for social value go
Betazz: hmm
murkythunder: why dont we create aids for sars
THX1342: unless you get a virus that eats only cancer cells
THX1342: that would be nice
alkiiis: @Kustex programming a vaccine and posting in on github
bichid69: ITS THE SAME ONE BRO
peter35_: deepmind released something with their alphafold about ncov i think
theonlymonkas: @foti_kasparov PogChamp
VanishBlox: and your body is their perfect sex chamber 😏
lebop: what is he doing
Penguino138: University is a place for either doctors, or people who don't know what they want to do with their life so they waste it
lebop: ?
Betazz: viruses even take over bacteria then
harbad: there is such thing as a good virus, look up bacteriphages
lordBzzl: we need to bring the fight to virus nursery..
jadams: 5Head
harbad: they can be used for amazing things
THX1342: oh yeah bacteriophages... true
lordBzzl: or the virus womb
St47ik: @Betazz oh wait there are actually good viruses like Bacteriophage
Landowner555: in a university you have labs to actually work with this stuff tho
Br4nnon: true
saintmthw: wow i just got called out
THX1342: russians are all into bacteriophages
esence: but I want to take a loan
Darkm1ght: fuck that world of warcraft comment hits hard
DevoE444: i study only Greta
kingpin9: this guy is making a point
bokeee_: atpRtsd
murkythunder: CORONA GO TO THE POLLS
murowski: me
dvdutch: The internet > university
SnadderG: You need university when you are dumb like me
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
RomeoR77: hey boss!! What r we doing?
Betazz: @stuartlz haha
VanishBlox: I'm playing MINECRAFT
bravech: Don't worry I'm just wasting time watching you
Jehhred: This idiot right here is reading news
Br4nnon: i'm self studying fullstack js web dev
sondreal: news LUL
Penguino138: Pokemon Go to the polls
cutza: doomsurfing
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: ME IN TIK TOK
Strfkrs: Ok dad
fwef64: Yeah, let's stop wasting time watching this stream.
lordBzzl: @St47ik any other good viruses?
Makifun: just get learned
o______________________k: facts
dvdutch: George sounds like a libertarian
VanishBlox: streams over guys
gyne: like how to get into uni PogChamp
theonlymonkas: he is
Landowner555: doing this stuff with biology is the equivalent of reading about sex
peter35_: true FeelsBadMan im addicted to twatter
St47ik: @lordBzzl T-Virus Kappa
SHAVEYY_: I stopped playing vidya games once I started programming
foti_kasparov: Always remember that bro that said once that the internet is the biggest equalizer ever in the history of humanity
SHAVEYY_: video gamers are for zoomers
djcows: wuhan bat soup flu
b2kemann: kong flu!!
THX1342: YEEEPPP
THX1342: PREACH
gyne: racist cmonBruh
Nopy1: aaaaah non pc detected!!!
Penguino138: Delicious Pangolin soup anyone?
bokeee_: @Donique9 atpQuan
pogu: How does he have full access to ncbi
alfyfav: make a clip about that
dj_vicio: seafood market my ass. Biochemistry lab you mean.
recursive_x: lmfa8
THX1342: damn right.. get skills
o______________________k: LMFAO
lordBzzl: @St47ik coool
yaus_baus: wuhan seafood mmmm delicious
iron_lasagna: hi :)
o______________________k: squadOmega
pogu: Isn't ncbi like bajillion dolalrs a month
harbad: same virus? I thought they were two different strains. @georgehotz
Apocalyptic0ne: @george check out this article
Apocalyptic0ne: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2982146/
smurfd0: isnt there 2 strains?
TheBusbyBabes: a guy made soup so bad he crashed the world economy
Betazz: yes
Betazz: 2
ackxhpaez: The Chinese name is the "US Army bio-weapon"
dj_vicio: here we go
St47ik: NotLikeThis
VanishBlox: I bet the guy who made the bat soup is so happy everyone knows his soup now :D
harbad: catalytic activity - using energy to create something
MrDrSpace: George streaming POG
bichid69: yeah theres the L-Type and S_type
iron_lasagna: McDonalds has closed :(
DevoE444: hack CIA if you want to find the cure Kappa
logi6000: watch there be some exotic strain of weed that cures it
SHAVEYY_: the chinese name is 阴茎病毒
murowski: oh shit chemistry
lordBzzl: we have a viral envelope and some rna stuff and a few connectors and that's it?
recursive_x: is that in round up
lordBzzl: how do they even form
bichid69: L-Type and S-Type are the two strains
harbad: they form in host cells
d3adb33: but it is organic chemistry - not anorganic :)
dvdutch: Blue dreams cures COVID
SHAVEYY_: we wouldnt get viruses if we stopped fucking animals Kappa
St47ik: @lordBzzl like everything else, evolution
theonlymonkas: click click click
Penguino138: @dvdutch Blue Dream weakens your lungs for if COVID hits u
logi6000: @dvdutch ha that sounds good
iron_lasagna: Pog?
ybdev: ybdev subscribed at Tier 1.
DevoE444: @SHAVEYY_ good one
logi6000: blue dream my favorite
ktzkalash: geo finding the cure lol
noobaj: L-Type & S-Type, L-Type is more contagious and it affected wuhan
murkythunder: this is useful LUL if you know how to use it
theonlymonkas: LUL
dvdutch: I dont actually smoke weed thats the only strain I know lmao @Penguino138 @logi6000
harbad: VIRUSES ARE REPLICATED ONLY IN HOSTS. VIRUSES DO NOTHING OUTSIDE OF HOST BODIES, THEREFORE VIRUSES ARE NOT CLASSIFIED AS 'LIVING'.
DevoE444: this virus looks like sushi
saheenshoukath: wait I didnt signup for biology
noobaj: the one causing outbreak outside of china is S-Type
jadams: copy and paste :)
Penguino138: @dvdutch Well Dutch Treat is the best and it's in ur name lol
o______________________k: squadOmega
logi6000: yo so if I smoke enough blue dream then I won't have any lunga for the Corona to attack let's go
SHAVEYY_: dose the virus have a heartbeat
montreehall: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OOJqHPfG7pA may help
mabac95: wtf is he doing?
lordBzzl: @St47ik true, amazing universe designer
theonlymonkas: BAN
dvdutch: I think I smoked blue dreams once and had a panic attack
sircrocodile163: George stop studying chemistry. You will end up like Martin Shkreli LUL
SHAVEYY_: BAN
Penguino138: @mabac95 He is making a vaccine to upload to Github
Crypod: LUL
inDOObitablee: He's making a vaccine and posting it on Github @mabac95
iron_lasagna: Print("Cure"); :)
SHAVEYY_: @mabac95 making a vaccine for github
harbad: @SHAVEYY_ they don't have a heart.
SHAVEYY_: wtf how
dvdutch: You should be listening to the cure rn
harbad: @georgehotz yes
omisyss: What is the advantage of using jupyter instead of just running a Python file
TheSpeedyLive: what is he doing?
saheenshoukath: imagine if he really find a cure
theonlymonkas: Martin Shkreli vs Geohot
murkythunder: would the information be public?
smurfd0: its made by he-who-must-not-be-named :P
Rovelo: @georgehotz human testing is hard to to LUL
inDOObitablee: He's making a vaccine and posting it on Github @TheSpeedyLive
SHAVEYY_: @omisyss you can experiment way more
SHAVEYY_: better for learning
MrDrSpace: Sick, A virus causing a lockdown and we know zilch. That's comforting.
Penguino138: @TheSpeedyLive Vaccine for github read the chat bro
mabac95: Ty guys
dvdutch: Medical scientists arent as hyperfocused as programmers @georgehotz
VanishBlox: @thespeedylive making a cure and posting it on github
SHAVEYY_: @mabac95 github.com
drake_elite: can i get this pdf
iron_lasagna: so what would be the benefit if he actually achieved what hes trying to do?
Landowner555: u would be a pretty legit bioinfomatician
Penguino138: hilarious how many keep asking what he's doing and our answers
logi6000: @iron_lasagna a cure
esteve_11: esteve_11 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
SHAVEYY_: @iron_lasagna making a vaccine for github
logi6000: @iron_lasagna and getting fucked by a pornstar
iron_lasagna: lol
harbad: he's reverse-engineering covid-19
SHAVEYY_: nah nah dude he's reverse-sciencing covid
Foxxy_xx: how was the progress last night? i fell asleep and missed half of it lol
Landowner555: we're gonna strike back china
Penguino138: Lots of people coming to this stream who can't even read apparantly
lordBzzl: can a virus be completely be described in code?
Foxxy_xx: and since im not a sub i cant watch the video back
recursive_x: lol
edu4594: he's creating a git repo for the vaccine
viper262_: @lordBzzl yeah
logi6000: we could just take the North Korea approach and kill everyone who gets it?
Br4nnon: lmao
Nopy1: #hacklyfe
Landowner555: what we need is a vaccine to cure autism
saheenshoukath: that sounds logical
VanishBlox: Wooooho bois give yourself a pat on the back we broke 1k views!!!!??
iron_lasagna: @Landowner555 but arent you enjoying the stream?
harbad: is North Korea really? wow...
SHAVEYY_: bro i'm gonna make so many pull requests to this cure
Kustex: @Landowner555 we need more autism
Landowner555: lmao
foxubu: lol
tykabmo: Has he reversed engineered the coronavirus and solved the world problem?
Penguino138: A lot of stupid in the chat. Kinda liked it when there was 200-300 viewers more
SHAVEYY_: i'm adding leds to the cure PogChamp
d3adb33: maybe soon
dvdutch: I'm gonna make a pull request and put in a line that prints "boobs" to the console
Landowner555: @Penguino138 no u
xxdvxx: Thanks for the stream
iron_lasagna: @tykabmo yeah but a few bugs
brownyyyylocks: are we live or has this stream ended?
T3chHS: if (hasCoronaVirus(person))
saintmthw: @dvdutch hackermans
logi6000: @t3chhs the true cure
edu4594: live
St47ik: 4Head
SHAVEYY_: @T3chHS you dont need brackets if your running 1 instruction :)
sircrocodile163: LULW
brownyyyylocks: made it!
AresD7: @georgehotz there is a medicin they're using in Japan called Avigan seems to work, do you knwo about it?
Lizardan: He’s going down the rabbit hole
iron_lasagna: just do it 4Head
Landowner555: dont we already do that lul
brownyyyylocks: thanks edu!
harbad: @georgehotz those ones might not survive though.
dvdutch: 200 IQ
n00b_Solid: just infect millions squadH
Penguino138: @Landowner555 you think there needs to be a vaccine for autism WutFace WutFace
FurikuriYugi: you can't fix stupid but you can profit from it
SHAVEYY_: so its more like if(hasCoronaVirus(person)) person.killPerson()
T3chHS: @SHAVEYY_ works wither way
Fundlak: LUL
St47ik: LUL
Betazz: there are antibodies
SHAVEYY_: yeah Kappa
T3chHS: either*
thegodofunderworld: Will this stream be uploaded to YouTube?
habituss: he's looking into that now ?
recursive_x: just find the same RNA within the protein that will break down the one already within the subject
Nopy1: and how does different strands of the same virus work??
RobinMalfait: Isn't that literally how they work? :P
bichid69: isn't the issue with the symptoms the immune response itself?
murkythunder: there have been cases where people with corona in china have caught it twice i read
Penguino138: @Landowner555 This stream is brought to you by Autism
camel3: squadLUL squadLUL squadLUL squadLUL
MrYasser2194: yeah thats it
TheKiit: Hi
foti_kasparov: Vaccine is the weakened virus
ybdev: Yes you can get reinfected. Hi!
Landowner555: @Penguino138 lmfao
St47ik: but you need to trigger anti-bodies
Rovelo: LUL you cant just make another virus
lordBzzl: @viper262_ but where do we go from there? we could have a virus template
cutza: That's the S strand
donasaurus: Yeah its that easy... oh wait
St47ik: chewing ice DansGame
esence: lmao, just tell your cells to be prepared
ybdev: We do that with mosquitos.
tiagodopke: chewing ice stream?
harbad: If we don't cough and spread the virus to everyone, then the virus you're talking about would just die in one host. @georgehotz
noobaj: @georgehotz check data available on immune/recoverd people
thegodofunderworld: Will we have the full stream on YouTube?
Betazz: people who got reinfected weren't fully recovered
theonlymonkas: ASMR
maxjowett: lol
kornez: my favorite ice chewing stream PogChamp
murowski: or just kill all old peoples SeemsGood
logi6000: if you listen to anti vaccine people tho it's full of Mercury and pesticides
lordBzzl: new viruses pop up, we whip out our template like a magic wand
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: does george has a discord like other twitch streamers?
VanishBlox: if Person.Infected than Person.kill() Person = nil end LUA BEST LANGUAGE
Tsoding: The Ice Cub near the fridge has finally melted PepeHands
St47ik: @thegodofunderworld on comma ai archive youtube channel
Crypod: indubitably
Rovelo: what about recombination lul
dj_vicio: careful there George. The NWO WANTS to kill people.
dvdutch: Is george any good at chess?
Betazz: so there's no proof that they got infected twice
bravech: PokDarkrai
Andremm2: how do we know that this is not how this all started lol
saixj: can you make you portrait screen smaller
theonlymonkas: no
MrYasser2194: @georgehotz you have to make it weak enough it doesn't do a lot of damage and strong enough it triggers a immune response
raondev: @georgehotz Nice to see you on again <3 love it to watch you while I'm learning for my university stuff
kornez: @georgehotz any mixtape coming?
Rovelo: cant viruses literally share DNA and become a combination LUL
montreehall: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OOJqHPfG7pA
kokiworse: kokiworse subscribed with Twitch Prime.
harbad: @georgehotz we can't see everything on your screen with your handsome face in the way. lol
Loutlot: glycoprotaina are unique to each and often acting as a flag to immune system
SHAVEYY_: twitch staff PogChamp
Rovelo: staff monkaS hide
VanishBlox: George pls install feet cam😳😳
Digital_donger: staff being helpful PogChamp
Digital_donger: Kappa
recursive_x: pretty sure if you distill corona extra into corona light that also works
harbad: the glycoprotein 'spikes' are similar to host proteins for endocytosis.
edu4594: MiniK
FurikuriYugi: cmonBruh
harbad: that's how the virus spreads from cell to cell.
ybdev: I was the girl at the hackathon. People with compromised immune function are basically unable to make any defenses. They can get marrow transplants and then do it.
saintmthw: subscribed twitch staff PogChamp
dvdutch: Somebody play me: https://lichess.org/Uh3hSPWq
Fulk33: Its crazy that there are like proteins that are basically data structures and then there are proteins that run code
Rovelo: @georgehotz please check out Antigenic shift monkaS
Rovelo: for the love of god
evil_tourist: Ideal candidate for the role of Eliot in season 6
Landowner555: ^
artikkk: !followage
edu4594: we live in a simulation
lordBzzl: could a programmer understand a virus...:P
d3adb33: oh boy - season 6 was a mess - i hate it.
Wuthappenedgusy: no but this guy can
xrealyy: simulation... haha
VanishBlox: Yes, he could
lordBzzl: haha
Masturbear: lordBzzl I'm both :) it's bio-informatics
SHAVEYY_: just write an AI to do the research for you 4Head
b2kemann: someone has link to the papers?
murkythunder: make vaccine cure generic so we can cure all viruses at once Pog
lordBzzl: what's the simplest virus there is?
thegodofunderworld: What is his objective?
FargioFarmani: somebody play me: https://lichess.org/o8Da6fkl
sondreal: LuvPeekL hello
thegodofunderworld: I just came here
thegodofunderworld: What is he trying to do?
DevoE444: ctr alt del , end covid.exe gg you won
VanishBlox: ai find solution: killing every human
Br4nnon: it
theonlymonkas: BAN
Br4nnon: it's in the title**
saheenshoukath: reverse engineering the coronavirus #lockdown
saixj: do you plan on streaming again tomorrow around this time
d3adb33: reverse engineer the corona virus
lordBzzl: can repeat @georgehotz technique but on something simpler
info303: are we doing unsupervised learning now?
dorkmo: post corona virus cure to github
yevenesh: can bubble sort solve coronavirus?
SHAVEYY_: post coronavirus to github pls
saheenshoukath: how can I use the cure once found? git clone it ?
bichid69: deepmind computed these structures here
bichid69: https://deepmind.com/research/open-source/computational-predictions-of-protein-structures-associated-with-COVID-19
thegodofunderworld: Wow! reverse engineering !!! I should have expected that. It's hacker stuff
SHAVEYY_: put the cure on gitlab plsplsplspls
mabac95: @dorkmo how he's doing it? searching stuff on google?
recursive_x: other than using crisper anytime the protein mutates to break down the auto communal parts idfk
bobert_____: bobert_____ subscribed at Tier 1.
St47ik: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antigenic_shift
Snowlav: what limits the size of the virus?
SHAVEYY_: @mabac95 his stream is just opening chrome tabs right now
revenantrazer: lol
Masturbear: big isn't necessarily functional budd :/
lordBzzl: @Masturbear PartyHat
brownyyyylocks: sub life
esence: it's all about them likes and subs
revenantrazer: reverse engineer coronavirus for the subs
recursive_x: I'm on here maybe once or twice a month lol
vloood: trump was just like "Romney is in isolation?! Gee that's too bad" LMFAO
saheenshoukath: same
harbad: @Snowlav smaller viruses tend to travel further, cost less to produce, and can infect more. hosts
d3adb33: I watch always on YT - now it is my first time live.
dj_vicio: we need more people like George
VanishBlox: yo deep mind made a paper check it out https://deepmind.com/research/open-source/computational-predictions-of-protein-structures-associated-with-COVID-19
emiven: people are using NN to predict virus mutations
RakeRoux: RakeRoux subscribed with Twitch Prime.
vaskogomez87: cold and soggy fire, nham
alexyzdev: If anyone is going to be able to build a cure with a python script I think it's going to be george
fwef64: Reverse engineering coronavirus is cool, but do you know what's even cooler? Optimizing it to perform better.
Kmerck313: 1000 ppl
THX1342: how can you use a NN to predict a mutation? It's like trying to predict a dice roll, isn't it?
saheenshoukath: this is my youtube channel.subscribe.im desperate https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMoemgeR-6D5nmSJjShbcQA
lordBzzl: needs to be something like X-informatics :)
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz please play me https://lichess.org/r6EOP9JX
recursive_x: lol
logi6000: @fwef64 time for an upgrade
SHAVEYY_: isnt evolution just mutating randomly until something sticks?
THX1342: ^
Snowlav: @harbad like wave lengths? LUL
montreehall: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OOJqHPfG7pA
foti_kasparov: > Create the vaccine > Sell it for 1$ per person > 7 billion people buy it > You become a billionaire !!!
Loutlot: initiation codon is not always AUG for virus thats confusing
info303: @SHAVEYY_ thats how reinforcement learning works
Masturbear: THX1342 no, there are rules and predispositions in strings of DNA/RNA that make stuff more/less likeley to happen
THX1342: maybe using NN to check protein folds might make sense
recursive_x: k
THX1342: @Masturbear oh ok
法國人: @SHAVEYY_ correct, except it's not random
harbad: @georgehotz the M is for MRNA
djcows: Are you shorting the market?
THX1342: @Masturbear any keywords for me to research that?
murkythunder: @foti_kasparov sell it for 1000, become a trillionaire
northumb: what have you reached so far george?
lemonspree: random question of the day; what are your thoughts on Norway? @georgehotz
harbad: @georgehotz it's a replication and translation codon
dorkmo: whats to stop evil doers from re-releasing sars every year?
logi6000: @lemonspree found out where this guy lives I guess
alexyzdev: @northumb he knows he needs to either eat zinc, or soap..
Masturbear: THX1342 hmm if you wanna go really basic just look up: transversion/translations DNA/RNA
emiven: lol e det deg lem
foti_kasparov: @murkythunder But if you sell it for 1$, everybody will be happy ! :P
d3adb33: see the rest (hopefully) on YT....have to quit :(
brownyyyylocks: why can we peacefully co-exist?
harbad: think of it like code
brownyyyylocks: YOLO
murkythunder: @foti_kasparov no, ppl will complain why its not .5 or why its not free :(
Masturbear: thats just a simple example of a factor that has to do with it, theres many more but it'll give you an understanding THX1342
d3adb33: in EU it is midnight
harbad: when a script ends, it's just like a return statement
montreehall: if covid-19 is mucus vicks and mustard kills it
d3adb33: good night everyone!
harbad: it stops running.
info303: lol
djcows: TRUE
nashesvobodnoye: How does he plan to "reverse engineer" the virus? I mean do we know precisely what each piece of the gene is doing?
St47ik: LUL
THX1342: @Masturbear I understand the basics but not the mechanics involved in mutations. I thought it would be a random error in transcoding/translation
o______________________k: squadOmega
sayyy: ANELE
recursive_x: zkdkSip
info303: being evil is low effort
dvdutch: Unabomber was p smart
THX1342: didn't know there were 'more probable' outcomes
kornez: LUL
lordBzzl: @mastubear is bionformatics only on genetics?
gyne: monkaTOS
logi6000: what was that song called
harbad: we actually know what most proteins are doing @nashesvobodnoye . Their indevidual moving pieces are documented.
SHAVEYY_: make a virus
SHAVEYY_: sell the cure
WeBDaEMoN3: @georgehotz this is the phylogeny of the virus with its evolution https://www.gisaid.org/epiflu-applications/nextflu-app/
FargioFarmani: great play!
21_savior: xqcT
St47ik: NotLikeThis
Masturbear: THX1342 the mutations are somewhat random yea for sure. Everytime DNA is copied to RNA mistakes happen somewhat at random
Ant__K: monkaS
roystang: rip
Mariosavitch: hello mr. hotz
ICAntF331MyFAce: monkaS
Ant__K: squadHmm
murkythunder: evil smart people have a doctrine they stick to at least, they dont do it for chaos
harbad: very much of the proteins that make up viruses are very well documented.
Snowlav: Masturbear like flipped bits in electronics?
nashesvobodnoye: !uptime
TheHareld: Is the streamer playing IRL Plague INC ?
harbad: phylogeny is the tree of mutation and ancestry
d3adb33: and for all of the end of the world fans - have a look on this hymn :D https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yUKZhbZHXsI
St47ik: @TheHareld we're all playing it IRL now
WeBDaEMoN3: @georgehotz you can select ncov in the tab on the left
recursive_x: bullshit field germ theory createdir
Masturbear: lordBzzl bio-informatics is the field that studies organisms their genetic material by using programming. but it's pretty broad, just google it ^^
recursive_x: it
harbad: HIV is WAY different.
harbad: don't bother with HIV
ToxicVulpes: all these viruses are literally just BIOLOGICAL version of . exe
esteve_11: What is the result of reverse engineering a virus lol?
bichid69: can you not just rm -rf / of the virus?
SHAVEYY_: bro they turned the computer virus into a real thing
lordBzzl: @Masturbear will do, thanks
SHAVEYY_: cant wait for fortnite irl
11plus4thinking: what are you trying to accomplish by reverse engineering the coronavirus
dtsa349: Hi George, nice to see you :) Happy to see you are working on some corona virus-related project. That quarantine already affected my life, the third week at home, working remotely, everything is closed except shop and pharmacy. I read a little bit about coronaVirus. The aspect you may have to consider is getting a virus inside the cell (mitosis) and protein ACE2. Scientists are trying to make a vaccine that stimulates to make antibodies for that protein. Have a nice day :)
TheHareld: @St47ik We are losing hard though :/
d3adb33: a deeper understanding is a good start for a reverse engeneering. Maybe more or less
Masturbear: Snowlav basically, but since theres ATCG which are all composed off many molecules alot can happen. but if you're just looking at results yea it's just like htat
is_physics: does he have access to paid papers?
recursive_x: m
SHAVEYY_: @11plus4thinking putting the cure on github
harbad: @esteve_11 you can understand where the virus can be stopped.
o______________________k: Hi George, nice to see you :) Happy to see you are working on some corona virus-related project. That quarantine already affected my life, the third week at home, working remotely, everything is closed except shop and pharmacy. I read a little bit about coronaVirus. The aspect you may have to consider is getting a virus inside the cell (mitosis) and protein ACE2. Scientists are trying to make a vaccine that stimulates to make antibodies for that protein. Have a nice day :)
St47ik: @TheHareld there's still hope
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are your reasons for doing anything?
montreehall: HOW TO MAKE DECONTAMINATION BOX TO KILL BACTERIA AND VIRUS (EX. CORONA COVID-19) WITH H2O2 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6PM_D1fuAS0
11plus4thinking: @SHAVEYY_ doesnt matter if he finds the "cure" it needs to go through a long testing period that can take up to a year anyway
bichid69: bro just rm -rf corona
Snowlav: Masturbear thank you for the explanation!
esteve_11: @harbad Does he have any hope of actually achiveing it?
SHAVEYY_: @11plus4thinking he's injecting the virus into monkies 4Head
TheHareld: @St47ik I already did not have hope even before this pandemic dude, so i'm all in if this shit turns into World War Z or smth
cengea: bruh
Masturbear: Snowlav np! :D
bichid69: @esteve_11 absolutely fucking not
Hoefler02: Run :(): on it
recursive_x: ba is bs
kittenplan_et_al: is it mostly "junk" like the human genome and you're trying to find the viral "genes"?
brittonx2: you should do a SARS-v2 hackathon
St47ik: regex the proteinz Kappa
murkythunder: if world is this freaked about 2% deathrate whait til they find out about global wamring Pog
11plus4thinking: @kittenplan_et_al "junk"
Masturbear: kittenplan_et_al generally virusses have A LOT less junk
lordBzzl: '.exe' does not have and maintain physical body and processes, could be where biology is better at
kittenplan_et_al: @11plus4thinking well some of our "junk" is actually viruses Keepo
Alteriume: imagine if u could have a biologist in chat that could tell you what is junk and what isn't
St47ik: ocean water is full of viruses
SHAVEYY_: bro Bernie sanders be live
SHAVEYY_: wtf
Fulk33: First ones always end in GG
iiiiiiillllliiiill: i am bilogist btw
misterbinu: If you solve coronavirus using Python I am going to get mad
Masturbear: Alteriume not like a biologist knows every piece of DNA LUL
St47ik: LUL
lordBzzl: definitely some bio peeps in the room
Zorbaselo: what is this i entered now
harbad: @iiiiiiillllliiiill what do you study?
tone_by: what is he doing?
Alteriume: Masturbear you a leftist? name everyone to your left
bichid69: I'm a comp chemist, still don't know shit though
dtsa349: he doesn't read chat? :(
11plus4thinking: @iiiiiiillllliiiill whats a bilogist?
logi6000: @tone_by making a vaccine and posting it on github
St47ik: @Zorbaselo reverse engineering the virus and saving the world
harbad: he does from time to time.
METH_HEAD_MIKE: just copy paste the glycoprotein code to the Influenza virus and make a flu vaccine 4Head
Masturbear: Alteriume im a lefty, and i'm alone atm quarantining hard :)
法國人: @tone_by he is developing a vaccine to fight corona
Alteriume: Masturbear FeelsBadMan roughs time
Zorbaselo: @st47ik tf bro i dont undrstand shit but i keep watching
lemonspree: ELI5: What are you doing right now and for what purpose? @georgehotz
TheHareld: @METH_HEAD_MIKE LUL
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @harbad i specialize in ant psychology
bichid69: @METH_HEAD_MIKE Wait this is actually a pretty good idea
Masturbear: Alteriume personally meh, globally ye travisty :/
11plus4thinking: I heard that the us is using the supercomputer summit to simulate the virus
St47ik: @Zorbaselo you're not alone LUL
TimoPuukka: @georgehotz are you related to Kenny Hotz?
aasimm: what are we doin
Alteriume: Masturbear I mean, since me and my gf don't really go out and our family too we kinda cheat and still see each other but yeah
is_physics: sudo virus-get purge Sars-Cov-2
wootawee: banning people left and right :)
anbu_bb: is he setting up for a nn?
法國人: @11plus4thinking really ? name your sources, if that's true that's cool
harbad: @iiiiiiillllliiiill ant psychology? did you study microbiology at all?
Aagaard89: @iiiiiiillllliiiill are you really an ant shrimp?
lordBzzl: what's the most complex virus to simulate with code?
Alteriume: Masturbear her neighbour were doing a fucking party the other day, didn't quite understand wtf was going on
pigporkman: just do rm -rf ~/coronavirus?
pigporkman: ezpz
StoogeThomas: StoogeThomas subscribed at Tier 1.
Masturbear: @georgehotz are u trying to find what those chunks of (i assume) DNA do?
aasimm: !uptime
recursive_x: it all is
bichid69: @pigporkman already suggested that
lordBzzl: or just the most complex virus
lordBzzl: ?
sobwyn123: @georgehotz how fast can you type ?
misterbinu: Should we try to run this through IDA?
logi6000: guys we need to just shut down the area 51 computer that has plague inc running
Zorbaselo: he is using the computer a way that i have never seen
Masturbear: Alteriume yeah i cheat a bit too, i see the same 5 friends daily. and they me and eachother exclusively
informalgarlic: @georgehotz why you have no dono link??? @georgehotz
Fulk33: weird that the different parts all end in LQ
Snowlav: where does a virus get it
Masturbear: Alteriume man so many stupid people.. they'll all be sick in no time
Snowlav: energy from
equipollent_z: Biggest CTF in the world right now 😄
FargioFarmani: Where is your Ice Tea?? @georgehotz
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @harbad i majored in the effects of prayers on viruses
wootawee: blast the seq
Snowlav: could you starve the virus of energy and kill it that way?
t3rminal: Y29yb25hdmlydXMK
tazicke11: can someone explain what is he doing, im New
blazeofglorytv: This guy is crazy
Masturbear: Snowlav if it has no host cell then it dies
georgehotz: https://pastebin.com/FBtprSGK
djcows: Just pray and the virus will go away
Hoefler02: Crazy awesome
harbad: he's going to find a cure and post it on github
logi6000: @equipollent_z the flag is the vaccine and the reward is sex with a pornstar
theonlymonkas: twitchchess
Masturbear: it just steals proccesses in those cells to survive and replicate normally
iron_lasagna: lol
recursive_x: scared night
St47ik: PogChamp
komocode_: HACK THE PLANET
lordBzzl: woot woot
Snowlav: Masturbear I see, ok
Greaser_1: :-)
latisrof: did he post the paste?
equipollent_z: 😄
komocode_: zer0_cool
St47ik: @latisrof https://pastebin.com/FBtprSGK
equipollent_z: Hack the 🌎
latisrof: ty
VanishBlox: https://pastebin.com/FBtprSGK
davidgames68: @Transferer agr1 agr2 agr3 agr4
Alteriume: the echo in your room makes me sad @georgehotz
logi6000: @georgehotz are you just doing this to fuck that pornstar
theonlymonkas: LUL
Ghost_001: monkaS
Transferer: @davidgames68 ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
osuiw: howcome
davidgames68: @transferer agrJoy
b4by__y0d4: where is cc defined?
harbad: reverse engineering the virus is actually quite smart, but it's very difficult to figure out what to exploit in biology.
法國人: ^
logi6000: marshall law in affect that the sirens there coming with the M16'S
wootawee: "almost no way" = easy for evolution over time
St47ik: @georgehotz did you check Antigenic shift?
cutza: MARTIAL
StoogeThomas: The virus spread for animals to humans. Now his reverse engineering it and it will spread from humans to computers. True story 100% fact ;)
StoogeThomas: from*
FargioFarmani: makes sense
Zorbaselo: where the hell he learned this things??????
montreehall: the UK gov said there going to start using the cure next month live on TV the other day
harbad: internet
Penguino138: @Zorbaselo like the rest of us. From years of self isolation
lordBzzl: @harbad small realistic feedback loop needed, I think..
BesterGester: @Zorbaselo internet
St47ik: @Zorbaselo the internet Kappa
NoPartiesGuy: wtf happened here 1014 people watching, where are streams with ReactJS and Jquery in one project Kappa
法國人: @Zorbaselo internet
leesingods: Cant believe how lucky i am was watching the corona video on youtube and clicked the twitch link and you're live..
Creamy_Goodness_: so much white. turn on darkmode for gods sake
Tsoding: zorbaselo, What do you mean learned? Did you assume he ever stopped? LUL
Luccaasss: imagine, geo hot discover the solution of the virus
whitsyerhing: Whoever has the dials for our simulation is a prick
harbad: @lordBzzl what do you mean?
MuscleMario: @leesingods same here.... wasnt expecting him to be on.
theonlymonkas: my eyes
Zorbaselo: bro not the coding section i am asking about the gene things
kakurai: geo's reverse engineering Sars-Cov2's genetic code?
bichid69: TM score is some bullshit metric from CASP
Penguino138: @whitsyerhing The dials are already set on the inception of any multi-verse. Ie the universal constants
StoogeThomas: you should all be shorting the markets right now.
Masturbear: Zorbaselo internet
StoogeThomas: easy money
Simplex991: the only channel worth watching on twitch is finally live
Ziv0: over 1k viewers
法國人: @Zorbaselo he is doing it right now, you blind ? LUL
logi6000: @whitsyerhing there distracting us so we don't jailbreak out. that is his goal for 2020
vanst0rek: will this be on youtube ??
BesterGester: @Zorbaselo Still the internet
alexandru_cristiean: !uptime
Penguino138: @vanst0rek everything goes up on youtube after the stream
mabac95: what does the function "translate" does?
leesingods: @MuscleMario Damn i knew someone else was here that came from it too
harbad: protease is used to break down host protein, then uses it to build its own genome.
mabac95: with a parameter like cc[266-1:13483], True
element731: @georgehotz 100 bits of you can solve this thing by supper time. Guar-an-teed, sir!
Mariosavitch: awesome function
Masturbear: georgehotz if u'd complete sentences we could maybe help out xd
bichid69: TM-score is such a bs metric it's unreal
Mariosavitch: GG
alexandru_cristiean: How do I stop being a noob @georgehotz
St47ik: GG
wootawee: gg!
leesingods: ggwp
Mariosavitch: get rekt. GG
saintmthw: gg, qq
Mariosavitch: QQ gg
Ziv0: gg no re
welcomedungeon: k, gg
antony4s_: gg KEKW
Tsoding: KGB tsodinKomrade
StoogeThomas: @alexandru_cristiean stop spending time watching twitch and use your time learning
b4by__y0d4: In the pastern code, where is $cc defined?
iiiiiiillllliiiill: ggx
St47ik: LUL
harbad: @alexandru_cristiean you spam @georgehotz 's twitch chat, that's how.
element731: KGB, comrades?
harbad: @alexandru_cristiean obviously.
FurikuriYugi: queue
Tsoding: KKomrade
element731: Qanon?
blazeofglorytv: Is it ok that I don’t understand a piece of it?
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 subscribed at Tier 1.
NoPartiesGuy: @alexandru_cristiean whatever you do do it more frequently and longer and you will become better
mauke53: @macab95 The code is missing some imports defined in the previous blocks. "The string translate() method returns a string where each character is mapped to its corresponding character in the translation table."
UniversalGeneve: is george just pattern matching letters, or is he looking at the charges of these AAs?
法國人: cagibi
St47ik: @blazeofglorytv yeah this is some advanced stuff
mazsociety: does chewing ice help prevent the virus?
vanst0rek: Guys check out INOVIO PHARMACEUTICALS
lordBzzl: @harbad seems like a complex system, even if we pull it off in code
RakeRoux: qmap.pub
olokinhomeuxd: esse cara é brabo
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: EZ
Zorbaselo: bune aq
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogU
montreehall: I just found this https://allworldreport.com/world-news/coronavirus-cure-australian-researchers-claim-to-have-found-cure-for-deadly-virus/
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 3 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 3 in the channel!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 0xfadead!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 0x0range!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to itz_padi!
St47ik: PogChamp
araeasmes: WutFace
o______________________k: :D
logi6000: u guys remember that meme in 2016 where it showed a pic of toilet paper and said its a meme from the future you wouldn't get it. we need to find that guy
VanishBlox: higz me sub pls
VanishBlox: give
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Pog
FargioFarmani: How do I stop being a loser?
Mariosavitch: i was here
Ziv0: I was here Pog
MuscleMario: LOL greatest CTF in history
vaskogomez87: ez dodge
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
Mariosavitch: real life CTF
harbad: it's very complex, but if you break it down to the smallest pieces, it can be understood.
samthedogg: how are gifted subs being chosen??
benzojamal: just solving corona 4Head
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: I was here LUL
cutza: subs only vaxx
kakurai: @FargioFarmani become geohotz
Nyt1k: I WAS HERE
Ghost_001: LUL
Cornflays: PogChamp
fwef64: FargioFarmani you can't
Juankinator: first iphones then Coronavirus Kapa
Fr0zenOfficial: IRLCTF2020
Aecxlol: oonoliGlissade
Greaser_1: :-)
lordBzzl: post-covid19 party
Zorbaselo: guys i have a question i learned python what should i do now?
phunandgames: dangPOG dangClaps dangPOG dangDial
vanst0rek: god created this CTF
VanishBlox: FOR WHEN WE FIND CORONAVIRUS, MARK ME DOWN IN HISTORX CHAT!
St47ik: @FargioFarmani dive into something you like doing and keep at it till you get good, or just watch Jordan Peterson LUL
法國人: Covid is shitting his pants right now
tremendomendez: PogChamp
Ghost_001: pacing monkaS
aasimm: DxCat DxCat
MuscleMario: @georgehotz Im actually creating a CTF my job on the side, releasing it for state farm employees April 1st. lol
logi6000: @zorbaselo cure corona
blazeofglorytv: Is he high or what?
keepingtrckofthisacct: no code?
Mariosavitch: gg
Cryzeal: Zorbaselo what was your purpose
iiiiiiillllliiiill: addy hype
kakurai: geo's always high
lordBzzl: @法國人 lol, wrath of human rance
harbad: lol I agree with @georgehotz
Fr0zenOfficial: btw @georgehotz make sure you are hydrated enough :)
samthedogg: how do i get the .cn3 file hes using??
djcows: What's in those cookies?
lordBzzl: *race.
FargioFarmani: Thank you all! Up to a great start
murkythunder: lol like statefarm employees will give a shit about a ctf
Azereos: Azereos subscribed with Twitch Prime.
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 2 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
harbad: @georgehotz let's do this
MuscleMario: they wont
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Itsmeek0!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 0xreself!
St47ik: SARS-CoV 3 confirmed Kappa
Fulk33: @georgehotz Reason why there may be stops where there arent: "Hidden stops are non-stop codons that would be read as stop codons if they were frameshifted 1 or −1"
MuscleMario: but im bored so i wanna get ppl excited.
MuscleMario: :D
theonlymonkas: DansGame
kakurai: sound's just messed up here?
peter35_: the sim managers are running us for this CTF
St47ik: sound's fine
alex_grist: Do you use regular or ungoogled chromium?
harbad: I'm hearing fine, do you need to restart?
Zorbaselo: @cryzeal i dont remembee i started it finished a book, now i dont know where to go people making projects like mobile or web but i dont know what to do with python only know about AI
11plus4thinking: what are you drinking good sir
theonlymonkas: T E A
MorningScifi: We need a geneticist up in here for some pair programming
UniversalGeneve: it's mostly protein regulation studies
c1tr0n75: Cheer15 I am recovering from this evil thing man, slowly but surely
Mariosavitch: are you looking at each one as a particular function? @georgehotz
aasimm: schools aren't a choice these days george
logi6000: @c1tr0n75 true hero
harbad: again, HIV is not like Covid-19
Fulk33: @georgehotz Reason why there may be stops where there arent: "Hidden stops are non-stop codons that would be read as stop codons if they were frameshifted 1 or −1"
theonlymonkas: LUL
St47ik: @c1tr0n75 be strong mate you can get it 💪
Ghost_001: i don't even know what a protein is LUL
logi6000: @aasimm but education is ripe for disruption
Fr0zenOfficial: what OS are you using @georgehotz
c1tr0n75: thanks peeps
Fr0zenOfficial: nvm its mac
harbad: he's using IOS
Apocalyptic0ne: lol have you heard of all these stores being forced to close by local pd? people are nuts
phunandgames: @Ghost_001 Protein makes you big boy and stronk HahaThink
wembassy: reverse engineering as in?
lemonspree: did someone ctrl c the pastebin of the code?
UniversalGeneve: you use pdb blast to search sequences
Ghost_001: PogChamp
lordBzzl: they keep mentioning Chloroquine as anti-malarial drug..thought the plasmodium got resistant?
Abnico: he uses bloomberg terminal
felipeit999: Hello
theonlymonkas: LUL
mabac95: @lemonspree https://pastebin.com/FBtprSGK
samthedogg: where is the .cn3 file from? in cn3 = open(...cn3)
lemonspree: thanks @mabac95
harbad: the gene sequence of the covid-19 virus is what he's reverse-engineering.
Masturbear: @georgehotz https://blast.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/Blast.cgi?PAGE=Proteins throw it in here
THX1342: the biggest thing I think geo is showing people is that you should not be afraid of not knowing. just DO IT. research. get the fucking skills and hack the planet
wembassy: ah
tarasyarema: Kappa
wembassy: how far has he got so far
harbad: @THX1342 AMEN
Ghost_001: @THX1342 PogChamp
aasimm: You ain't gonna pass HR if you wanna immigrate from some third world country it you don't have atleast bachelor's degree
lordBzzl: @THX1342 100%
MuscleMario: I like that geohot is doing this, i got really into dis Crispr / biosynthetic circuits stuff b4, when u get bored w/ computers n wanna study biology hurrdurr
Masturbear: yea googling a sequence does not work LUL
mohammed1996mizab: INVENTED STRINGS
wootawee: Track mutation/evolution: https://nextstrain.org/narratives/trees-background/
Ghost_001: LUL
BiszkopTT: this is way toooooooo hard
Fr0zenOfficial: LUL
wembassy: it would be amazing if someone came up with a programming language/simulator for genetic manipulation and open-sourced it
St47ik: rewrite nCoV 2 in Rust KappaWealth
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: WUT
dav231002: lool
revenantrazer: LOL
Zorbaselo: guys i need help from someone who knows python n
Digital_donger: LUL
DecayingSkullz: MedChem Express
Nyt1k: monkaS
benzojamal: mass production LUL
lordBzzl: @Masturbear MaxLOL
theendri99: can somebody please explain what is he trying to accomplish?
wootawee: banned
brownyyyylocks: what i miss? back from standup
Simplex991: LUL
hat3m: what is he doing ?
PiroFloydian: port doom to the virus
mabac95: !uptime
Azereos: na fuck Rust...rewrite in LISP 😎
WaeHaKe: i'm making notes, wiki = 100% legit
harbad: @georgehotz I'm near vegas
Abnico: @hat3m he is doing ur mom
hubabuba1243: @hat3m nobody knows
blazeofglorytv: This guy is a fucking genius
GeneralSoak: he is hacking the source code of the virus
djcows: He hacked the iphone, he hacked the playstation, he hacked cars, now it's time to hack life
法國人: @hubabuba1243 some knows, you don't
lordBzzl: peeeps, focuuss on the present
harbad: @georgehotz I have a place you can crash at, if you headed to Vegas.
logi6000: guys Fuck Earth imma go to the Moon and chill with vector
ziNNGG: he didnt hack shit, he stole it from me
Masturbear: can someone give me the sequence, so i can do it for him
samthedogg: @theendri99 @hat3m hes trying to find a way to stop the cloning "code " in the RNA or a way to block human ACE2 protiens from attaching to covid-19
harbad: helicase is what cleaves apart dna
ummyeah1929: ctrl f 4Head
lemonspree: Masturbear, which one?
Masturbear: lemonspree one hes looking for atm
FurikuriYugi: alt f4
aasimm: back with tons of tabs
harbad: @georgehotz Helicase is like an axe and dna is a block of wood.
theendri99: @samthedogg thank you for your answer
THX1342: @Masturbear https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/nuccore/MN908947
WeBDaEMoN3: @georgehotz this is the link I sent before - you gotta select 'ncov' from the tab on the left https://www.gisaid.org/epiflu-applications/nextflu-app/
wootawee: @georgehotz https://nextstrain.org/ncov
samthedogg: @theendri99 np . Now can someone tell me where to get the .cn3 file george is using??
dj_vicio: he forgot to count the virus he had for not washing his hands
THX1342: @Masturbear not sure if he is using that one, but that was the first published sequence
alycia: where to download corona vaccine
logi6000: @alycia cia
St47ik: github
dj_vicio: from github, coming soon
Fulk33: @georgehotz Reason why there may be stops where there arent: "Hidden stops are non-stop codons that would be read as stop codons if they were frameshifted 1 or −1"
法國人: @samthedogg not sure where but I'm pretty sure you can find out in the stream of yesterday
VanishBlox: George what is the translate function?
olokinhomeuxd: I have the cure, thanks to my 1 billion machines
Masturbear: THX1342 aight no this helps alot, i can just look up the orf he's looking at very helpfull ^^
samthedogg: @法國人 tired to . not a twitch prime member
wootawee: See all the sequences here https://nextstrain.org/ncov
wootawee: That is what changes
iiiiiiillllliiiill: can you not just use the blockchain to defeat the corona
logi6000: @iiiiiiillllliiiill exactly
theonlymonkas: NotLikeThis
法國人: @samthedogg ah yes right
olokinhomeuxd: @iiiiiiillllliiiill why?
ummyeah1929: why not just encrypt the corona then delete the key
School47: Hahaha Geohotz gonna hack corona!
logi6000: @ummyeah1929 hell yeah give it ransomware with no key
Nyt1k: just delete corona lol 4Head
St47ik: ctrl alt del
wootawee: download data button at the bottom of this: https://nextstrain.org/ncov
School47: cmon George, lets get root on corona
St47ik: nCoV is just a global bio ransomware
logi6000: this is what we get as a society for killing harambe. none of this would have ever happened if we just didn't shoot him
TorathorHD: what is he doing?
theonlymonkas: BAN
almonte550: Hi @georgehotz what are we doing today?
peter35_: harambe memes ConcernDoge
VanishBlox: Josh could you please explain what the translate function does again?
VanishBlox: george
Masturbear: He's just learning about viruses
Masturbear: not really doing anything so far tho LUL
St47ik: Virology stream
Connieboyboy: what is he doing
St47ik: also Twitch-CoV
esence: press 1 if you don't understand shit and don't see shit
Nyt1k: Kappa sure
lordBzzl: let's goo
Fr1gidTV: 1
almonte550: I was looking at that exact same page yesterday
St47ik: @Connieboyboy learning virology
hubabuba1243: 2
iskjmss: 2? 2? 2? 2? 2?
iiiiiiillllliiiill: maybe we can ask the bats and pangolins how to coexist with corona
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are your reasons for doing things?
nashesvobodnoye: next step, reverse engineer human genome KappaHD
theonlymonkas: 42
Connieboyboy: got it @St47ik
THX1342: Does SARS-1 target ACE2?
PaoloSisto: not really sure what I'm watching...
TorathorHD: but what is the objective?
dj_vicio: problems with the wife/gf?
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
St47ik: @TorathorHD saving the world
jeffery_fan: next step, reverse engineering the universe
aasimm: its her guys
THX1342: TorathorHD learn about the virus..maybe get a new perspective no one had before
logi6000: now this is what I look like while coding on my phone
gamerguy009: Geohotz
ummyeah1929: catching HIV through lung receptors?
logi6000: not doing anything
almonte550: @TorathorHD there is not an objective, only learning stuff
gamerguy009: callme15HYPEE callme15HYPEE callme15HYPEE
aasimm: he is using termux
JdPaulBlart: when will comma.ai go public
jayfoxxy: Can anyone explain to me what geo its trying to prove?
lordBzzl: wonder whether the world becomes more biotech-y after covid19 troubles
MuscleMario: https://nextstrain.org/ncov reposting this cuz its cool
logi6000: @jayfoxxy not prove he's making an open source vaccine
fireposeidoncx: @jeffery_fan I'm in
aasimm: he isn't proving anything
St47ik: HIV targets immune system T cells @georgehotz
jayfoxxy: @logi6000 no way :O
murkythunder: geo can you make your title more clear, to many new ppl asking what u r doing :(
dohtem213: wonder if George get wasted drunk
brownyyyylocks: CD4 T cells
theonlymonkas: @MuscleMario nice
ICAntF331MyFAce: :O
St47ik: @brownyyyylocks right
esence: what are those, linux distros?
THX1342: jesus.. why do people crave validation so much...? " What are you trying to prove?!" "Why are you doing this?"
wootawee: eactly there
harbad: @georgehotz zoom in
wootawee: data at bottom
benzojamal: woah
St47ik: PogChamp
Landowner555: any breakthroughs yet
ziNNGG: holy shit what is it
lordBzzl: ooo that's cool
jayfoxxy: @logi6000 seeing this i get the conclusion that im completely dumb ahahahah
harbad: those are origin locations
THX1342: damn thats sick
revenantrazer: whoa
caiooliveira2014: @georgehotz I love U
benzojamal: nerd boner PogChamp
wootawee: "Download" data at bottom
School47: this is like Plague INC! PogChamp
ImpalerV: wntrBRAIN
ummyeah1929: colors and lines PogChamp
youngsachi: PogChamp
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm
lowtemperaturebody: yo wtf is going on
ICAntF331MyFAce: pogu
St47ik: PogChamp PogChamp
murkythunder: d3 Pog
Nyt1k: PogChamp
tokumei64: LOL did he just find this site? LUL
snapcs1: LUL
Cornflays: FeelsAmazingMan
Greaser_1: :-)
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp
BiszkopTT: damn son
Ghost_001: PogChamp
shekshas369: PogChamp PogChamp Kreygasm
MuscleMario: @wootawee u deserve that credit lol
caiooliveira2014: PogChamp
VanishBlox: WOAAH WE ARE IN THE ENDGAME BOIS
dj_vicio: comes from the labs of Washington DC
ImpalerV: strong pee incoming
MorningScifi: HACK THE PLANET!
jtparker: And he is gone....
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
shekshas369: well fucking ülayed
School47: hahaha we will hack it like Iphone or PS3
LazyNorm: PogChamp
Ghost_001: i have no idea what going on PogChamp
ziNNGG: you gotta read your chat more often
MuscleMario: count the time he doesnt wash his hands
esence: actually washing hands LUL
MuscleMario: -1 -2 -3
almonte550: I don't see Dominican Republic with cases in the map, maybe doesn't it doesn't have all the cases?
brownyyyylocks: WASH UR HANDZ
iiiiiiillllliiiill: get more addy we need you at 100%
vozdra: HSWP
1gonyali: içiyon içiyon biraları sonra işemeye gidiyon amk en heyecanlı yerinde
School47: @Ghost_001 just make more hype
mattdougherty22: some was better than none
Masturbear: click on play PogChamp (top left worldmap) @georgehotz
iskjmss: this guy is added up
harbad: @georgehotz Thanks for the stream, I gotta go be productive... Ugh.
snapcs1: https://clips.twitch.tv/BumblingAcceptablePeafowlTebowing
bichid69: yo check this out https://github.com/feiglab/sars-cov-2-proteins
Ghost_001: Kappa
theonlymonkas: hahahaha no hand washing
gattz_: Kappa
AntiVax_SoccerMom: Kappa
Apocalyptic0ne: fuck adderall
cutza: adderall vaccine
Ghost_001: sure bud Kappa
youngsachi: Kappa
revenantrazer: you have adhd?
kakurai: Why geo's wearing ninja clothes?
dvdutch: 2 months too long
lordBzzl: Africa's seeing more cases but maybe no analysis of genome yet
wootawee: @MuscleMario no worries :)
PiroFloydian: are you on anything?
shekshas369: when genuine passion is being confused for being medicated
Mariosavitch: if you want to search a protein sequence you have to search the blastp database. Here is the search for the helicase of covid https://blast.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/Blast.cgi?CMD=Get&RID=7FWDB250016 @georgehotz
shekshas369: welcome to 2k20
klaazdw: im dutch <3
jeffery_fan: is adderall actually useful?
theonlymonkas: cocaine
shekshas369: LUL
almonte550: @georgehotz don't touch your face
wootawee: Everyone but the US has :(
dvdutch: Im not dutch
logi6000: how is Africa immune
ackxhpaez: Someone did a series of videos on nextstrain recently https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL1J8Fh6-iQxIeYUmeKHsyHP0c3LcY8Wyh
Abnico: why did u stop the adderal?
Ghost_001: @jeffery_fan ye but coke is better
fireposeidoncx: George is going insane
farlopote: Spain is fucked
dj_vicio: no one travels to AFrica
St47ik: @logi6000 its not immune just not much ppl travel there
dvdutch: Spains got it bad
kakurai: Let's go to Africa and get some diamonds.
jeffery_fan: @Ghost_001 True
bichid69: check this out bro https://github.com/feiglab/sars-cov-2-proteins
School47: this is EPIC
dohtem213: adderall make u smarter
gamerguy009: Adderal is 1 molecule away from METH
Masturbear: too late 4Head
Abnico: adderal is op for math
AntiVax_SoccerMom: CHYNA KKona
dorkmo: german master race corona
jeffery_fan: US KEKW
iiiiiiillllliiiill: chyna virus confirm
theonlymonkas: LUL
lordBzzl: @logi6000 africa's not immune, could be data not coming back or as fast
esence: look at that duuude, SEATTLE xd
grenaderaven: africa has much younger population than rest of world so they're probably fare better
dvdutch: 1 molecule makes a big difference
dj_vicio: whats the URL For that?
sAfEgUy1: way too late
St47ik: Adderal is a litlle neurotoxin
School47: there is no air blocks even now LUL
ummyeah1929: wait so the earth is flat
UniqumTV: people can still fly china -> japan -> US
Abnico: @gamerguy009 u are retarded lol
dvdutch: The earth is hollow
theonlymonkas: yes LUL
Mariosavitch: blastp sequence search for the helicase of covid19 https://blast.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/Blast.cgi?CMD=Get&RID=7FWDB250016. - download the search @georgehotz
benzojamal: TRUMP LUL
aasimm: the earth is flat, they came from other side
samthedogg: US democrats were busy impeaching trump to even notice covid
JdPaulBlart: the deep state globalists injected it into our country
dorkmo: flights arnt blocked, just passengers
Apocalyptic0ne: adderall and ritalin are only effective in short burts IMO. Taking them all the time, as prescribed, seems to create a mental haze in my experience. I recommend them for focused tasks though
esence: look at Seattle
pwnbase: pwnbase subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Adolfich: russia knows something @georgehotz
BiszkopTT: This auspice data visualization tool is amazing @georgehotz
bayarealove: bayarealove subscribed with Twitch Prime.
kakurai: flat Earth3 confirmed
St47ik: LUL
lordBzzl: africa probably going to be hit pretty bad: https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2020/03/covid-19-warns-africa-prepare-worst-200322163148759.html
ziNNGG: we past 4:20 😡
wootawee: @georgehotz you want a MSA of the sequences there, probably available via download, then light up the nucleotides and you can see what has changed
Kmerck313: The FEDs will be knocking your soon
THX1342: South America is going to get rekt
kakurai: geo, pls save us.
wootawee: msa = multiple sequence alignment
aasimm: 4:20AM here
fireposeidoncx: This mal proves that the earth is flat
Abnico: @Apocalyptic0ne i agree, now i only take it around 2 - 4 times a week
dvdutch: Will oil prices go down because of this whole thing
wootawee: "download" at the bottom
dohtem213: so it is chinese virus
jeffery_fan: time to move to north pole, I'll expect to see none of you there
theonlymonkas: guatemala
lordBzzl: tldr 1000 people in 42 countries in africa
wootawee: *sequeces*
kakurai: Sony could sponsors geo on his searchs
logi6000: @jeffery_fan say hi to santa for me
blazeofglorytv: @georgehotz gulfstream is a key
Loutlot: torrent?
MuscleMario: DOWNLOAD @ Bottom
Masturbear: theres always junk and hotspots
jeffery_fan: @logi6000 Sure thing, will do
St47ik: cough WutFace
PiroFloydian: HE COUGHED HE HAS IT
StoogeThomas: lol
gattz_: monkaS
kakurai: RIP geo
Ghost_001: quarantine the stream monkaS
grenaderaven: its game over
theonlymonkas: monkaS
cockwizard69: i'm out monkaS
logi6000: no it's just terminal lung cancer don't worry
youngsachi: monkaS
St47ik: NotLikeThis
Ghost_001: no one is allowed to leave now monkaS
anguscupcake: how does george do this shit without a PhD in biology
fireposeidoncx: Rip
gamerguy009: Play plague inc game anyone?/
Nyt1k: monkaS
theonlymonkas: PIR
Apocalyptic0ne: @Abnico that's a good amount. I only take it under high pressure circumstances lol, like if a project is due in a week or if i need to get through a code sprint
Mariosavitch: https://blast.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/Blast.cgi?CMD=Get&RID=7FWDB250016 searched for the sequence of the helicase
aasimm: are we talking about it evolving over spread?
kakurai: geo, you cant get infected. you're our only hope, geo kenobi.
hazeystream: could you briefly explain what you are doing?
logi6000: @pirofloydian don't worry it's just terminal lung cancer
fireposeidoncx: Rip in chat boys
alex_grist: Do you use regular or ungoogled chromium?
lordBzzl: amount of accessible data is amazing
theonlymonkas: F
Ghost_001: hacking the world @hazeystream
Fulk33: @georgehotz screenshot that graph!
chillguy269: Studying the virus gives you the virus monkaW
benzojamal: chat, he has no clue either xD
wootawee: You could load everything as tracks into Jbrowse or Gbrowse, not so good code, but nice to see things
Nopy1: BTW HACKERS:If some of you want to help in a different way: try hacking up some respiratory machines... they are much needed.
yth1n: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17934078 ppl talking about it in 2007, predicted possible epidemy
theonlymonkas: LUL
dohtem213: george learning shit everyday
aasimm: how can rna gene sequences differ of the same viruse>
AntiVax_SoccerMom: what happened to cozy metamath streams esfandCozy
almonte550: If sars-2 is this bad, I can't wait for sars-3
Ghost_001: interesting LUL
dohtem213: FortOne FortOne
St47ik: @almonte550 Sars 3 confirmed by gaben Kappa
iiiiiiillllliiiill: i predicted corona in february, no one listened
logi6000: @antivax_soccermom your username suggest you boutta die
s4j0k5: !uptime
kakurai: China's confirmed Sars3. They said it's gonna be a hell of a season. Cant wait for it.
theonlymonkas: ResidentSleeper
benzojamal: @logi6000 LUL
AleexM: what are we doing?
logi6000: the sequal
Mariosavitch: a better version yes
St47ik: profiler LUL
hazeystream: could you briefly explain what you are doing?
THX1342: it's just stripped code man....
MuscleMario: yall givin out IDA pro licenses in dis bit? !giveaway
aasimm: how can rna gene sequences differ of the same virus?
murkythunder: better ui than ida
Nopy1: @kakurai can's wait for sars03e01
almonte550: @St47ik link?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: logi6000 KKona this is all a hoax to get you to take the autism injections
St47ik: @aasimm mutations maybe
BananStian: @georgehotz What is the goal in what your doing? And how exactly are you reverse engineering the corona virus? Glad to see you trying to do something with the situation tho B)
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @hazeystream pretending to understand viruses
theonlymonkas: LUL
fireposeidoncx: @georgehotz how is your church doing?
ziNNGG: @iiiiiiillllliiiill :DDDDD
dontbeameme: What’s the benefit of reverse engineering this?
aasimm: does it evolve that rapidly?
kakurai: The present season isnt that good. So boring that's almost killing everyone.
Apocalyptic0ne: @iiiiiiillllliiiill well you were a bit late to the prediction there, as it was spreading since november in china xD easy to extrapolate what will happen
benzojamal: @aasimm yes
THX1342: rant time PepeHands
St47ik: LUL
brownyyyylocks: goodie two shoes
BOSSTIEN: inspiring!
School47: LUL
dontbeameme: Real
Ghost_001: not yet* PogChamp
jeffery_fan: Hack the computer virus
Kwallenbeet: LETS DO IT
ktzkalash: LMAO
THX1342: lanaluLetMeIn
Ziv0: LUL
Nyt1k: PogChamp
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp
Duschjenkovic: LUL
patulskitime: hell yeah!
faxity: MY MAN
VanishBlox: LETS DOOOOO IT :D
Kubissus: PogChamp
theonlymonkas: but have you hack the world?
gattz_: PogChamp
BOSSTIEN: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
St47ik: PogChamp
benzojamal: you doin good Kappa
VanishBlox: LUL
chillguy269: Is klout chasing really that bad?
snapcs1: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
MuscleMario: ... :( they laughin tho
CompestLive: LMAOOOO
xXICEW0LFXx: what does "hack the corona virus" mean?
pwnbase: pwn
dorkmo: lettttssss gooooo
myaocat: https://msphere.asm.org/content/5/2/e00203-20
AntiVax_SoccerMom: TREMENDOUS EGO PogChamp
0xmilan: love the rants
School47: George, you are the Best )
kleyy: PogChamp
samthedogg: GEORGE THE HYPE MAN
BagBoxx: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
peter35_: hack the planet !!
fuseteaseftali: Pog
THX1342: PWN COVID
Ghost_001: we gonna do what ? PogChamp
snapcs1: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp lets goooo
almonte550: Let's hack sars-2 and optimize it to make it more lethal
BananStian: Daym brah interesting B)
CompestLive: PWN vax
revenantrazer: @georgehotz its the first time you're hacking something that's not manmade
jeffery_fan: Corona is actually a computer virus that spreads through internet
snapcs1: PogChamp LETS GOOO PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
roadrunnervx: lol
theonlymonkas: HACK THE WORLD
esence: good luck, Georgy, corona virus is man-made afterall!
darkzade: AT 700% P`ROFIT PogChamp
fireposeidoncx: Pwn it faster!!!
Ghost_001: LULW
BOSSTIEN: lul
aasimm: for those of you who don't know. I'm gettin sued by soni
SlamchestPowerthrust: lol
revenantrazer: @georgehotz its the first time you're hacking something that's not manmade..
Cornflays: billionaire PogChamp
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp real money making time
dontbeameme: So this is for a vaccine, okay
FargioFarmani: welcome to communism
GeneralSoak: leeroy jenkins
Ghost_001: REAL PogChamp
theonlymonkas: scammer
revenantrazer: @georgehotz its the first time you're hacking something that's not manmadee
jeffery_fan: @revenantrazer Or maybe it is KEKW
bigie: how about coma.ai for the website ?
ICAntF331MyFAce: noobs will pay PogChamp
peter35_: clout baby
THX1342: LUL if you can't git clone you have to open your wallet, noob
vozdra: ItsBoshyTime https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4797993/#!po=0.943396
caine_corp: Are you sure you didn't take adderall?
BOSSTIEN: corona
mechanic_hammer: [Hell] Pwn the virus ! (Pt: 1,000)
aasimm: calm down
snapcs1: its usually true
Kmerck313: Nobody
caine_corp: LUL
iiiiiiillllliiiill: addy kicking in Pog
iTeQo_: Bro talk less and hack faster
parviz_gc: yeeee
roadrunnervx: have you thought about the name of your github repo yet? Has to be something cool
dontbeameme: Open source = Trojan horse for data
almonte550: How hacking coronavirus will affect augur 2.0?
kakurai: don't sell the cure to Sony's executives
iskjmss: yep he took addy
jeffery_fan: Im the first type!
Scyned: xD
benzojamal: how much would a corona virus cure be worth right now?
ziNNGG: @iskjmss :DD
dontbeameme: REAL
St47ik: LUL
ancientchineseelder: addy cotton mouth requires tea at lightnin speeds
PiroFloydian: tbh im prob a hypocrite
St47ik: Any truers
Apocalyptic0ne: y'all don't understand how adderall works for those who have adhd... He'd still be sitting focused and less talking
snapcs1: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
lgtst_: the truth
theonlymonkas: you are losing it geo
MuscleMario: nom nomz
MrSnoopDog: ayy lmao
dontbeameme: True
snapcs1: Kreygasm thank u george
Cornflays: yeaaaah brooo
FargioFarmani: oh boy how I missed these streams @georgehotz
icyvran: Flavor?
11plus4thinking: hes losing it monkaS
StoogeThomas: ice cream brand?
jeffery_fan: George Hotz tellin the truth on twitch
chillguy269: This is content
guacDev: what kind of chair is that
esence: THANK YOU BRO, GIVE ME SOME MORE
Crypod: FeelsAmazingMan 👈
Tompuscina: what happened
programmer42: George, you're cool bro
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: gachiHYPER
Mlewii: midlife crisis ?
theonlymonkas: BrokeBack
aasimm: asshole hypocrite
St47ik: don't eat it DansGame
u1337ochka: https://clips.twitch.tv/ExpensiveSparklyFlyWow
dontbeameme: Does this lead to hacking the simulation?
murkythunder: SIMP walk
St47ik: @u1337ochka LUL nice
MuscleMario: lol
School47: @Tompuscina we are hacking corona to make vacine
benzojamal: gay walk LUL
theonlymonkas: @Mlewii probably
logi6000: yo I swear one day the FBI gonna knock on George's door for speaking too much truth
fireposeidoncx: Stop eating pwn it faster!
firemang: firemang subscribed with Twitch Prime.
St47ik: nCoV readthedocs PogChamp
almonte550: If you hack coronavirus, will Sony sue you again?
guacDev: 5head
programmer42: thanks @u1337ochka
BagBoxx: PogChamp PogChamp
ancientchineseelder: lmfao
TrippinFlare: so what's the approach @georgehotz ?
gamerguy009: Are we living in a simulation?/
dontbeameme: mother terica was a do gooder
ABAD1DEA: Kappa
theonlymonkas: yes
cutza: Hack it for profit
jeffery_fan: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
Tompuscina: @school47 how is he doing so far
benzojamal: creating a botnet?
Jehhred: we're hacking corona to put on GitHub
aasimm: no we are hacking corona to mine crypto
11plus4thinking: @logi6000 the fbi is a bunch of idiots
inDOObitablee: We will deal with it when we get there.
lgtst_: ice cream with fries
theonlymonkas: potato
chillguy269: What's truth?
t3rminal: geotangent
dontbeameme: I wish I could see the optamizm
TrippinFlare: so what's the approach @georgehotz ?
snapcs1: true af
jeffery_fan: We will migrate corona from IRL to a computer virus
dontbeameme: George should never speak to children
theonlymonkas: Kappa
pwnbase: @georgehotz opinion on Peter Thiel?
MuscleMario: Re FBI: ... I want Geo to say something about Aaron Swartz
AleexM: george is such a legebd
dj_vicio: who is he talking to?
snapcs1: george is never wrong about anything
School47: @Tompuscina its only the begining as you see LUL
TrippinFlare: TRUEEEE
aasimm: we are hacking corona to mine crypto
almonte550: What truth? all the information is public on the internet, everything can access it
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: TRUEEW
AntiVax_SoccerMom: FIGHT THE POWER
murkythunder: @dj_vicio us
Nyt1k: @dj_vicio me :-)
peter35_: true bro FeelsBadMan truuuee
iiiiiiillllliiiill: addy peaking
theonlymonkas: se lost him
esence: economics degree LUL
jeffery_fan: we will upgrade corona to spread through internet
St47ik: @georgehotz calm down bro LUL
fireposeidoncx: Fuck Corona lets play minecraft!
dj_vicio: that's it. He needs the Aderall
Cornflays: FeelsAmazingMan 🍄
TrippinFlare: TRUEEEEE
patulskitime: blame the fed
guacDev: what kind of chair is that
School47: @jeffery_fan LUL
DecayingSkullz: love is the answer
bufferovrflw: ctf, capture the flu?
dr_set: those are making 50 million in wall street, we got left with ketchup
aasimm: we are hacking corona to mine crypto
bufferovrflw: *catch the flu
St47ik: Alex Jones mode
AntiVax_SoccerMom: quitting adderall was a mistake FeelsBadMan
davidgames68: @guacDev Herman Miller SAYL Chair
kakurai: PS5 Sars-Cov2 DLC confirmed
razr22: you need to go on JRE with eddie bravo
inDOObitablee: Lets create corona that only targets wealthy people
murkythunder: math DansGame
anguscupcake: which EE textbook should i get
TrippinFlare: so what's the approach @georgehotz ?
dontbeameme: Lol
tohsdnilb: fuck mAth!
vozdra: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4797993/#!po=0.943396
lgtst_: magic is math
St47ik: Slurp
ICAntF331MyFAce: math WutFace
almonte550: So we haven't solve coronavirus because of math
node_storm: that is true
theonlymonkas: we love math
dontbeameme: Lolol
Ghost_001: he is high LUL
jeffery_fan: Math NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
Tomishima: quick math?
nashesvobodnoye: magic IS MATH
gattz_: Kappa
St47ik: Math or m eth Kappa
theonlymonkas: slow math
Ghost_001: Kappa
worleywarrior: Fuck math, all my homies hate math
parse: Kappa
youngsachi: Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kapp
jeffery_fan: Weed
TsarSec: Kappa
reckful_bald_spot_114: Kappa
dontbeameme: ewwww math
VanishBlox: Is magic related to math?
okhandjoyjoyjoy: Kappa
nudax: LUL LUL
xXICEW0LFXx: dammit geo, now i'm eating ice creme you're a bad influence
FargioFarmani: you're not good at math are you ?@georgehotz
lgtst_: the hole point of doing math is having magic in the brain
Tomishima: just play AC for fun.
anguscupcake: is math related to science
Apocalyptic0ne: lol he should definitely be on JRE, I'd definitely watch that episode
kakurai: geo, o Brasil te ama
Ghost_001: Kappa who knows
MuscleMario: Aaron Swartz
dj_vicio: give him the aderall
Yemtex: mr. robot are you there ?
jeffery_fan: He
St47ik: magic is related to m eth Kappa
gamerguy009: Try smoking crack
diegoarigony: what he uses?
barrenaps: You are sounding like a crackhead
tohsdnilb: math math=fuckit
VanishBlox: Give him the coke
yevheniiushtyk: at least you're not a noob ;)
St47ik: DansGame
dontbeameme: Math and magic should never go together, pure blasphemy
logi6000: it could be autism. or a certain strain
ICAntF331MyFAce: oh no, someone has energy must be addy rockin :)
theonlymonkas: are you real life mr. robot???
Cornflays: FeelsAmazingMan 🍄
tiagodopke: joe rogan needs to get on george's strea
iiiiiiillllliiiill: lmao
dj_vicio: life's not that binary my friend
Mariosavitch: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/projects/msaviewer/?rid=7FX88B5301R&coloring=cons MSA comparison of the helicase @georgehotz
VanishBlox: LUL
jeffery_fan: Drug the CPU
saintmthw: 5Head
revenantrazer: yup
revenantrazer: intersting point
tohsdnilb: is this matrix 4
THX1342: yes
revenantrazer: its actually
logi6000: @theonlymonkas that could be it
revenantrazer: the problem with reductionists
lgtst_: right
PiroFloydian: hm
lgtst_: exactly
THX1342: it's using a canon to kill an ant
revenantrazer: thats a reductionist argument
myaocat: http://virological.org/t/alignment-of-58-sarbecovirus-genomes-for-conservation-analysis-of-sars-cov-2/430
theonlymonkas: D E E P
JdPaulBlart: ive been enlightened
St47ik: @georgehotz vaccines are software patches Kappa
esence: good points, tbh
11plus4thinking: so go to a psychiatrist basically
PiroFloydian: so how does that transfer to fixing mental health stuff @georgehotz ?
TheSpeedyLive: some deep shit
yevheniiushtyk: Sounds like something Intel would say
dj_vicio: my head hurts, do I cut it off to fix the ache?
benzojamal: so deep Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: when are you going on Joe Rogan ?
revenantrazer: software is way easier
Jehhred: software is hard....ware
revenantrazer: all discrete
revenantrazer: unlike nature
t3rminal: can you write a for loop or something?
MrBankster: you're take on covid being a hoax?
ninjadidio: true
leesingods: So the way you think is software???
almonte550: So are we creating coronavirus software to fix our bodies?
Cornflays: LUL
ICAntF331MyFAce: LUL
11plus4thinking: PIZZA? OpieOP
theonlymonkas: do joe rogan
swagomgswag: israel
AntiVax_SoccerMom: Israel?
snnoox: What about his self driving car project?
benzojamal: isreal?
dr_set: they are not trying to fix it, they are trying to make money . It's an incentives problem.
nudax: nice eyes man
peter35_: israel monkaS
JdPaulBlart: nah we just need to hack the simulation somehow to get to the real root of the hardware issue @georgehotz
jeffery_fan: Corona is not Real KEKW
Tomishima: Adrenochrome is not real chat!
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 12 months, currently on a 12 month streak! I wish I had more time to watch ur streams, maybe Covid-19 can fix that? :D
ToxicVulpes: @georgehotz are you still pro $BCH ?
vrooom_vroooooom: @t3rminal lmfao
St47ik: @georgehotz vaccines are software patches KappaWealth
THX1342: yeeeeepppppp
Pasha_Pechkin: @georgehotz it's all good, but can u hack a russian government?
FargioFarmani: true that
myaocat: @georgehotz http://virological.org/t/alignment-of-58-sarbecovirus-genomes-for-conservation-analysis-of-sars-cov-2/430
theonlymonkas: i like this
cutza: LOL
11plus4thinking: LUL
flaczq: what is your main source of income, sir?
Snowlav: LUL
bigie: wanna go off on flat earthers ?
youngsachi: LUL
St47ik: LUL
Nyt1k: 4Head
guacDev: LUL
Cornflays: LUL
dontbeameme: it’s called 1984 George Orwell
VanishBlox: LUL
lemonspree: how is he not on drugs today
dontbeameme: Nobody listened
Marcel63: kappa
bufferovrflw: Is he bipolar?
dj_vicio: yea.. he needs another dose of Aderall
theonlymonkas: no
logi6000: @dontbeameme def one of my fav books
Connieboyboy: he has to be on druhs
THX1342: Snowden was a redemption to a lot of nerds considered conspirators
Connieboyboy: drugs
PilotHaman: https://clips.twitch.tv/ShyPeppyMangetoutPunchTrees
tahiraslam8k: What about Area 51?
theonlymonkas: he is the drug
shlver: I believe it. :)
zombiedigital: earth is pizza
Apocalyptic0ne: lol he's not on drugs
dvdutch: The earth is hollow. Open your eyes.
11plus4thinking: KKona EARTH IS FLAT MAN
AntiVax_SoccerMom: monkaS you have too much faith in society
leesingods: no people do believe that and its sad
St47ik: he doesn't need drugs LUL
Halixness: how is it going with the reverse engineering thing?
almonte550: Are we optimizing covid-19 or not
lgtst_: sugar injection
ICAntF331MyFAce: oh no, someone has energy must be drugs :)
ancientchineseelder: he microdosed salvia just before he started going on steram, someone clipped it earlier
School47: Ppl don't care they have no time to think about it
dontbeameme: People believe skinny jeans are good, so anything is possible to manipulate
tohsdnilb: good example of not making it months in quarantine
ageMonkey: haha
bufferovrflw: Watching George rant about conspiracies and eat ice cream
bufferovrflw: damn
Halixness: @almonte550 optimizing it would be pretty risky innit
tornpaperyoyos: oh hey george is streaming again
Bitcoin__: My day is ruined however, people have banana on their pizza.
Mariosavitch: here is the orfa1 msa diffs .. zoom in to see the code https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/projects/msaviewer/?rid=7FXGTZFN016&coloring=cons @georgehotz
ktzkalash: @georgehotz forget about Rona. We want you unlocking the new PS5 that is coming
Fr0zenOfficial: So george what you do all day besides this? :D
Apocalyptic0ne: salvia lasts only a couple minutes max
dj_vicio: now he needs to hack glucose levels so that ice cream doesn't take a toll on him.
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Epsteins death was weird
dontbeameme: George is definitely in the know
dongmuya: So far Hotz has solved the ice cream problem
logi6000: amped George is what I fucking live for
kiikoh: any progress here?
TrippinFlare: so what's the approach @georgehotz ?
Tomishima: he has take Adderall after weeks today SMOrc
mmi18: is that a 3d printed chair>
MuscleMario: He's exhibiting symptoms that a medical professional would probably diagnose as manic depression. All great people are like this, society just wants to sell u that its a problem and sedate u.
Halixness: @georgehotz why not predicting the spread of the disease?
School47: is it hackable? ))
whitesaucey: hows comma doing???
almonte550: Is it Alex?
yth1n: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17934078 predicted in 2007
youngsachi: mon
dontbeameme: Can you just do virtual experiments on AI
LaminertKatt: whats happening today folks?
guacDev: its the government
dj_vicio: oh shit, his wife. that' sit guys. Streams' off
esence: is it NSA
ziNNGG: coronas callin monkaS
AntiVax_SoccerMom: FBI OPEN UP SwiftRage
tohsdnilb: it's Trinity calling
dj_vicio: it's the CIA
youngsachi: monkaS
boxtooo: fbi monkaS
snapcs1: the FBI monkaS
cutza: BiLl gAtEs CrEaTed cOroNaViruS tO ImpLanT EveRyOnE wItH DiGitAl InK
swagomgswag: fbi heard him
Mariosavitch: u owe taxes
21_savior: monkaS
PilotHaman: FBI
School47: its CIA LUL
theonlymonkas: is the government
Apocalyptic0ne: FBI ON THE LINE
dontbeameme: CIA
ktzkalash: FBI CALLIN HIM
guacDev: FBI
chillguy269: monkaS
THX1342: it's the FBI telling him to stop streaming
ICAntF331MyFAce: monkaS
11plus4thinking: FBI OPEN UP LUL
benzojamal: monkaS
ktzkalash: LMAO
dj_vicio: Trinity hahahahahhaa
murkythunder: @MuscleMario stfu armchair psychologgist
Nyt1k: FBI
logi6000: I heard security
dvdutch: Its da CDC
razr22: monkaWait
PilotHaman: this stream is done
dontbeameme: FBI open up
lllowe: FBI OPEN UP
whitesaucey: george from statefarm
guacDev: FBI LMAOOOOOOOOO
fireposeidoncx: Its Obama MonkaS
alexandru_cristiean: Trump's calling
flaczq: "this is corona, pls end the stream"
nudax: lol
davidgames68: CIA FeelsBadMan
dj_vicio: oh shit
ninjadidio: morpheus
Mariosavitch: rofl
Apocalyptic0ne: RAIDED
Luccaasss: FBI, stop with this
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
almonte550: FBI omg
logi6000: oh it's landlord
theonlymonkas: trump on the phone
St47ik: NotLikeThis
Restless_Bagel: monkaS
gamerguy009: IRS
almonte550: RUN
o______________________k: FBI OPEN UP
dontbeameme: FBI open Up
ktzkalash: lmaooooooooo
razr22: monkaW
maqebane: lol
guacDev: hahahahhahahhaha
Mariosavitch: stop making noise rofl
Fr0zenOfficial: "hello stop working on covid thank you." what a monkaS moment
VanishBlox: They caught him bois, Bio terror is no more!
alexyzdev: FBI
saintmthw: @ninjadidio LUL
benzojamal: landlord? LUL
MorningScifi: Landlord is angry yo
youngsachi: monkaS monkaS
Mariosavitch: TOO LOUD rofl
logi6000: fbi
almonte550: RUNNNNNNN
FargioFarmani: FBI guys
worleywarrior: NOISE COMPLAINT LUL
alexandru_cristiean: direct line with the White House
dontbeameme: F B I
guacDev: lmaoooooooo
Apocalyptic0ne: RAID
razr22: MonkaW
logi6000: CIA.
dj_vicio: too loud hahahahahaha
MuscleMario: @murkythunder im an armchair meteorologist
Mariosavitch: hahah
bufferovrflw: :DDDDDD
theonlymonkas: FBI
chillguy269: LUL
shlver: LUL
fwef64: @georgehotz how are are you willing to take this corona series?
snapcs1: LUL LUL LUL
vrooom_vroooooom: LUL
alexyzdev: HAHAHAHAHAH
Restless_Bagel: LUL
adamcernycz: Corona upstairs? :monkas
11plus4thinking: LUL
alexandru_cristiean: "no worries Donald"
St47ik: LUL
benzojamal: LUL
kleyy: LUL
VGBurnzy: this guy doesn't have a landlord lol
Fr0zenOfficial: fbi open up LUL
Ziv0: LUL
FargioFarmani: too loud
esence: 500000000 SHEKELS DEPOSITED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT
dvdutch: LMAO
dontbeameme: Looks away like we can’t hear him
Penguino138: They thought you were being loud? lol what a joke
mechanic_hammer: Open up! FBI
St47ik: Loud rant LUL
nudax: HAHAH wtf is happening
leesingods: Is the software you're talking about for humans are the way they think??
lgtst_: conspiracy
vaskogomez87: you think?
shlver: TOO LOUD
JdPaulBlart: Bogdanoff
dr_set: ? you are not been loud
baezor: XD
bigie: ! do you live in a retirement home ? that wasnt loud
dj_vicio: being loud == CIA tells him to shut the operation.
nashesvobodnoye: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
chillguy269: THEY ARE TRYING TO SHUT DOWN YOUR TRUTH TALKING MAN
kiikoh: your not loud
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: "TOO LOUD"
THX1342: upstairs neighbor was raided by mistake
School47: why everything is red?
kiikoh: it's not late either
Apocalyptic0ne: its 4pm, who the fuck complains about you being loud?
SpecialAgentSkye: monkaS Be quiet chat monkaS
Nyt1k: monkaS they are watching
pixelzman: hey hey hey
Kmerck313: I knowwhat you did last summmer
Bitcoin__: Play some loud music :D
dontbeameme: Nobody is working so what’s the problem, your quarantined
theonlymonkas: the fbi
ICAntF331MyFAce: neighbors NotLikeThis
VGBurnzy: @georgehotz hope you're doing well my man!
tome_silva: does he have Asperger's?
ktzkalash: LOUD = TOO MUCH EXPOSING
dr_set: TheIlluminati
esence: who the fuck calls you to tell you about lowering your voice?????????????
alexandru_cristiean: lmao if geohotz has to be quiet in his own house then I have no hope for true freedom
FargioFarmani: please whisper from now on @georgehotz
Fr0zenOfficial: probably getting mad bc he said corona too many times in the building LUL
logi6000: @chillguy269 they called me a madman. said the FBI were a bunch of idiots. look at it now George is being quiet
dj_vicio: CIA tells him to stop bragging or else RIP
esence: the land of the free LUL
shlver: you should get even louder Kappa
peter35_: we all have the tism here bro
Snowlav: LUL
benzojamal: that's the reason why he loves anarchism?
Mariosavitch: yes, take the sequence and enter it into "blastp" and then click MSA Viewer after results are done @georgehotz
Kmerck313: adilanHack
cutza: BiLl gAtEs CrEaTed cOroNaViruS tO ImpLanT EveRyOnE wItH DiGitAl InK
yth1n: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17934078 predicted in 2007
chillguy269: @logi6000 Be careful out there brother, there can only be so much truth spoken at once
dontbeameme: did George y’all about EARN it act?
dontbeameme: Talk ?
fbmtr: Sars coronovirus?
amek7: where he lives?
dj_vicio: neighbor who called is a conspiracy theorist hahahahaha
theonlymonkas: COOL
logi6000: @chillguy269 my agents already on to me.
FargioFarmani: 1 @dj_vicio
dontbeameme: Did George talk about EARN it Act?
School47: is it DNA od corona?
Penguino138: Sounds like your neighbor needs you to scream CORONA more
kleyy: the virus is trying to tell us something monkaS
kittenplan_et_al: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_coronavirus_NL63 has someone posted this yet? similar virus that binds to the same ACE2 receptor and causes fever, cough, and pneumonia
mescal33t: beastyAmazin
aethuall: I only found out how good biopython actually is. After refusing to use it and writing my own code for the longest time I caved in and just used it, makes my life so easy
Mariosavitch: You can search "blastp" for the protein and look at the MSA viewer to see the diff @georgehotz
almonte550: But the real question is, is our body running on 32bits or 64
aasimm: so we are looking at multile samples?
yth1n: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17934078 predicted in 2007
theonlymonkas: 32 bit
aethuall: Yeah doing a blastp is good
kiikoh: @georgehotz do you have biochem background?
logi6000: nah 512 bit
ktzkalash: TELL UR NEIGHBOR YOU FINDING CORONA CURE. DO NOT SHARE WITH HIM
School47: @kiikoh this is not nessesary for him LUL
ziNNGG: monkaS
razr22: LUL
cutza: you are not even loud wtf
jeffery_fan: Hacked house
guacDev: the NSA
lgtst_: how the heck they know all the contacts?
Snowlav: monkaS
Penguino138: Then it's not ur fault George, u do u
TrippinFlare: Email complaints PogChamp
o______________________k: CALI LUL
chillguy269: They're trying to silence you bro, I am telling you
Apocalyptic0ne: lol fuck your neighbors, they sound like asshats
jeffery_fan: hacked KEKW
adamcernycz: I guess it is a bug then monkaS
esence: commiefornia
dr_set: Somebody doesn't like you and they are making stuff up
aasimm: fish em
informalgarlic: dude you allowed to make noise during day @georgehotz
t3rminal: no vaccine for him
boxtooo: fbi breaking in to make noise to get you on the streets
murkythunder: CHEW ICE
LaheyFPS: headspace LUL
Mariosavitch: GOV trying to shut down your real life CTF hacking
AntiVax_SoccerMom: slap out a quick fap
St47ik: Headspace time Kappa
guacDev: its comma ai's competitor
TrippinFlare: headspace OMEGALUL
iiiiiiillllliiiill: 420
eduardoadf1: !uptime
jeffery_fan: Kreygasm Meditation Kreygasm
dontbeameme: imagine calling George for noise complaint, the guy who hacked the first iPhone lol
slimpimp007: after he first complaint, Karen will come with another one soon after
Bitcoin__: When u have that type of neighbor, move out right away. Fuck those
azogshady: damn that's a big head g3orge
lgtst_: screw calming down, doesn't activates the brain
kakurai: has someone complained about him being loud?? LUL
Mariosavitch: lol
ktzkalash: plot twist your neighbor is a CIA agent
ziNNGG: :DDDDDDDD
VanishBlox: Calm chat
lebop: ???
ninjadidio: haaahahy
emel_ryan: headspace?
Hawklite: meditation is a waste of time just visualize yourself in the 3rd person for 10 seconds then your'e good to go
VanishBlox: Let's Calm
lgtst_: CORONA SOLVING NEEDS RAGE
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
Fr0zenOfficial: lets do this @everbody
LaheyFPS: 🙏
informalgarlic: @georgehotz meditation is too loud!! @georgehotz
dj_vicio: he reminds me of Josh from Watchdogs 2 LOL
icyvran: The accent is really important
aethuall: This is now a :) zone
murkythunder: turn that down youll get another noise complaint
Panerakis: LUL
dvdutch: :)
lgtst_: SHUT THAT SHIT
kiikoh: phone speaker is louder than you are
a_ato: LuvSnooze LuvSnooze
dj_vicio: too loud
shlver: FEELING
lebop: what is happening
VanishBlox: @everyone shut up headspace time!
o______________________k: :) zone
dontbeameme: Ewwww
theonlymonkas: let's open up those chakras
aethuall: Everyone spam :) to relax
MuscleMario: he tryna medidate and read chat.
alfyfav: rlly???
esence: AY TONE, CAN YOU TONE DOWN THAT CORONA VIRUS REVERSAL
Snowlav: 🙏 chat
Apocalyptic0ne: do your neighbors know who you are? You need to show you're the alpha male in the building
Penguino138: get ready for another call. Phone is wayyy louder than geroge
MJT_au: this meditation guy is about to sell you some crystals
iiiiiiillllliiiill: :)
informalgarlic: meditation is too loud
Yemtex: !time
dontbeameme: Why do I feel worse from this guys voice
brownyyyylocks: stop reading chat geo focus
kleyy: drhgBreath drhgBreath drhgEye drhgEye
guacDev: STOP LOOKING AT CHAT GEORGE
dvdutch: :)
Mariosavitch: hah
sircrocodile163: MUCH FEELINGS LUL
VanishBlox: @everyone Calm, it's headspace time!
icyvran: Copyright complain!!!
dontbeameme: George has a thing for British accents
dj_vicio: is that Alex Jones
Fr0zenOfficial: guys just roll with it and mediate aswell :)
anguscupcake: we're going to build a wall and make the corona pay for it
PiroFloydian: :)
dontbeameme: Imagine having a guy to relax u
dj_vicio: wtf is happening
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: ????
aasimm: dont focus on comments bitch
davidgames68: @Transferer :-)
lgtst_: that was awful
benzojamal: call dr. k, he will teach you how to meditate :)
murkythunder: having a guy tell u to relax is sorta gay ngl
icyvran: Challenge: Meditate while reading the chat
farlopote: PixelBob PixelBob
zombiedigital: da fucks going on here
gabo_sk: ResidentSleeper
MuscleMario: @murkythunder lol
adamcernycz: I hear that meditation tape even in Europe kappa
amek7: where he lives? in usa?
ktzkalash: WAKE UP THIS MATRIX
darkzade: BlessRNG
Marcel63: Ehm.. good night?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: ResidentSleeper .........
dj_vicio: he blacked out?
almonte550: Lets open up those chakras to let the virus enter more easily
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: .............
Penguino138: reach boner yet?
dj_vicio: illuminati told him to do that
esence: SLEEPING STREAM
JarlVonBarf: I thought the stream froze
dontbeameme: over 9000
benzojamal: ResidentSleeper
brownyyyylocks: omg geo==neo
cutza: SHHHH
sircrocodile163: WAKE ME UP SwiftRage
diegoarigony: what am i doing here
lgtst_: just sleeping
dj_vicio: strream froze on me too
Snowlav: monkaS
dj_vicio: its the NSA
VanishBlox: Shhhhhhh! sleeping stream
lgtst_: category
ktzkalash: U KNOW CIA IS CONTROLLING HIM
o______________________k: squadR HEY DUD where is my content @georgehotz DUD squadR
1gonyali: bi Ferdi Öğzbeğen Dilek Taşı dinle hiç bişeyin kalmaz
maqebane: meditation
vaskogomez87: reckful streaming? lol
pedrovictortech: Is that the "10 percent" app?
aasimm: he passed out
dj_vicio: CIA is erasing his mind right now
icyvran: Meditate while listening to the calming computer fan
sircrocodile163: I CANT WAKE UP SwiftRage
gabo_sk: f
snorting_milk: he fell asleep
dr_set: hack the guy that complained tv, and put it in perma max volume so everbody wil complain about him
dontbeameme: The noise complaint triggered George into meditation
Fr0zenOfficial: is his cam frozen or did he diededed?
almonte550: Is this part of solving coronavirus?
ktzkalash: MK ULTRA SHIT
chillguy269: @pedrovictortech its headspace
diegoarigony: dead
kleyy: drhgBreath
adamcernycz: Compression alg just chilling, no need to work, still image LULW
guacDev: rip
t3rminal: WHO PUT ADERALL IN HIS ICECREAM?
pedrovictortech: @chillguy269 Thanks!
MuscleMario: formatting his disk rn
Fr0zenOfficial: WAKE UP
myaocat: "smithereens" someone?
benzojamal: corona symptoms monkaS
Snowlav: he disconnected irl monkaS
TrippinFlare: ResidentSleeper
tiagodopke: actually losing viewers
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: is george getting hack by the deep state LUL
esence: D E F R A G M E N T A T I O N
ninjadidio: guys he's power up
almonte550: Geohots left the chat
Fr0zenOfficial: he escaped the matrix
allhail2daking: How you hacking rona virus?
TrippinFlare: meditation ResidentSleeper meditation ResidentSleeper meditation ResidentSleeper
21_savior: xqcMood
iiiiiiillllliiiill: the corona complained to your landlord because he was afraid
BananStian: Wake me up, wake me up inside FortBush
dontbeameme: Why do I feel ASMR coming on
bufferovrflw: Someone got root shell on him
dj_vicio: Agent Smith's work
VanishBlox: Chill he's changing his grapichs settings, it's too heavy on his pc
guacDev: he jailbroke the simulation
dontbeameme: ASMR next chapter
MuscleMario: D E F R A G M E N T A T I O N INITIATED
allhail2daking: Show us your desk setup
slayerdaniel: he’s having an out of body experience right now he’s hacked the simulation
ktzkalash: SO HE JUST TOOK THE REDPILL WHEN HE SIPPED WATER
dontbeameme: Simulation hacked
lgtst_: so someone calls in asks to be quite and george ends up sleeping. No conspiracy you say?
dj_vicio: CIA BRAINWASHING BEGINS........
esence: I FEEL SENSATION IN MY PIPI
TrippinFlare: corona incoming
erlsek: tanoviSHT
gabo_sk: this new episode of mr robot 2 is 1337
VanishBlox: He got a phone by the matrix boys!
ninjadidio: Jilbroke himself
ktzkalash: @lgtst_ LMAO
VanishBlox: THE MATRIX CALLED HIM
almonte550: He now will be able to solve all the world problems
o______________________k: I WANT CONTENT NOW DUD squadR squadR
TrippinFlare: squadW in the chat
FargioFarmani: which app is he using? @channel
thxslo: so thats how you reverse these ddays ? =)
ktzkalash: HE'S GETTIN READY FOR MATRIX 4
dj_vicio: someone clip this please. He's making history
revenantrazer: meditating before solving coronavirus
o______________________k: squadW squadSquad
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: APE GANG squadW
PiroFloydian: hes using headspace
imopfloors: he's temporarily leaving the simulation
Cornflays: nmpW
revenantrazer: 5head
mauke53: @FargioFarmani Headspace
brownyyyylocks: doesnt work on me
VanishBlox: George is new matrix actor????
MuscleMario: squadW yeeee
4zimut: wake up neo
kleyy: drhgBreath
vaskogomez87: any giffters bouys?
o______________________k: HEY squadR you awake DOMIE
VanishBlox: Neo wake up
Ziv0: mizkifHA
dontbeameme: I’m falling asleep, we not getting a cure sleeping
dj_vicio: Wake Up George....... the CIA has you
esence: AY TONE, CAN YOU MAKE THAT HACKER STFU
lgtst_: KNOCK KNOCK
icyvran: **This stream is sponsored by Headspace**
ninjadidio: follow th white rabbit
tiagodopke: hey george bring me some stuff from the outside
TrippinFlare: any oil princes OMEGALUL
logi6000: yo hotz is in the matrix right now so chill
stole_yo_eip: namaste
cutza: Watching e-girls sleeping level of quality stream right here
o______________________k: hey @georgehotz I need my exploit chain DUD squadR squadR squadR
ktzkalash: HE EVEN LOOKS LIKE YOUNG KEANU REEVES
Mlewii: !uptime
lgtst_: liquid sunlight my ass
vaskogomez87: stop staling domer
PaoloSisto: when is he going to discover the vaccine?
dontbeameme: So this is how hypnotism works
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: HEEEEELOOO squdW
sircrocodile163: JUST MEDITATE BRUH KEKW
razr22: stop looking at chat george
dj_vicio: shit, he's awake
VanishBlox: yo hold up, this is irl neo, the people who called him were the matrix
adamcernycz: Liquid sunlight, ooooook
Pasha_Pechkin: @lgtst_ who's where?
iiiiiiillllliiiill: you are all breathtaking
slimpimp007: this sounds a little sus
TrippinFlare: 24 HOUR VACCINE HACK STREAM PogChamp 24 HOUR VACCINE HACK STREAM PogChamp 24 HOUR VACCINE HACK STREAM PogChamp
Mariosavitch: *ring ring*: "Yeah we have complaints of someone meditating.. any idea?"
Dawoud3: drdisrepect V.2
o______________________k: squad1 squad2 squadOK
VanishBlox: anybody suspecios?
lemonspree: for how long is he doing di
dontbeameme: George has ADD, no way he is going clear right now
almonte550: Is @georgehotz opening his third eye?
dj_vicio: Corona's payback
sircrocodile163: ResidentSleeper
logi6000: everyone say ban questions now he's in the matrix he can't see i
cutza: Just like watching thots sleeping
Penguino138: i just took a shit and this is still going on lol
sircrocodile163: ResidentSleeper GO ON
o______________________k: squadL squadL squadL squadL
cammbamm92: cammbamm92 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months! WAKE UP
gabo_sk: geohot final form monkaS
Mariosavitch: danHmm
MuscleMario: I am from the future George, P R O O F: In the next few moments we will have 2 gifted subs.
brownyyyylocks: uhp opened eyes
VanishBlox: Everyone this is a calm stream
VanishBlox: Shhh
ktzkalash: PLOT TWIST: THEY BRAINWASHING US
thxslo: heaspace 10 min sessiosn =)
OptoCloud: Why u still meiditating? NotLikeThis
eduardoadf1: !uptime
lgtst_: why we still here
TrippinFlare: downloading code PogChamp downloading code PogChamp downloading code PogChamp downloading code PogChamp
dj_vicio: !uptime
Apocalyptic0ne: MOTHERFUCKERS, DO THEY KNOW WHO THE FUCK YOU ARE?
slimpimp007: George probably stressed tf out running a startup during all this
Br4nnon: monkaW transcending space and time monkaW
sircrocodile163: everybody shut up i have an erection
Br4nnon: monkaS *
saixj: f
ninjadidio: just to suffer
adamcernycz: I believe corona is meditating as well so it is a fair game
VanishBlox: He's doing that contact sequence where he opens his cabient and jumps out of the goo and goes into the sewrs
tokumei64: woah this sounds like hypnosis stuff
dj_vicio: @sircrocodile163 in your ass
iiiiiiillllliiiill: addy reaching critically low levels
cammbamm92: LOL @sircrocodile163
o______________________k: @sircrocodile163 HEY DUD ME TOO squadR squadR
benzojamal: viewcount 👉 📉 ResidentSleeper
lgtst_: the voice is about to ask for credit card number
lgtst_: 100%
icyvran: **This stream is sponsored by Headspace**
aasimm: does it help
darkzade: DOWNLOADING NEW DNA FROM GOD TO DECODE CORONA
VanishBlox: Hey, you're finally awake :)
logi6000: hey future George guy do I get a sub in those next few moments
Restless_Bagel: @icyvran raid shadow legends LUL
cutza: SLEEPING STREAM WITH HOTZ
Jehhred: Dude looks high in air
4zimut: send link
stole_yo_eip: namaste
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: this chat is shame less LUL
esence: TIME TO STOP PRETENDING
Apocalyptic0ne: Fuck your neighbors
Marcel63: HE LIVES
theonlymonkas: IM AWAKENED NOW! Kreygasm
Fr0zenOfficial: well done :)
St47ik: Kreygasm
aasimm: does it help??
OptoCloud: HES BACK BOIS
o______________________k: squadOmega
inDOObitablee: waffleT1 waffleT2
ktzkalash: IM FEELIN WEIRD HOL UP
Mariosavitch: it looks like the spike protein changed the most
VanishBlox: Hey, welcome back
gabo_sk: ssh god@universe
Andremm2: trying to meditate reading twitch chat must be a challenge LUL
razr22: LUL
esence: ASMR
tiagodopke: asmr stream
Apocalyptic0ne: he's got the bob ross voice now
almonte550: Can I be a mob because of me watching you sleep from start to end?
TrippinFlare: superpowers downloaded LUL superpowers downloaded LUL superpowers downloaded LUL
dj_vicio: getting a sub for sleeping , damn
razr22: yes george, whisper in my ears
lgtst_: aaaaaw sheeeeit
VanishBlox: Bob ross stream :D
sircrocodile163: ROADRAGE IN 10MIN LULW
dj_vicio: too loud!!
St47ik: CoolStoryBob
tarasyarema: wtf
Apocalyptic0ne: Now we're gonna code a secret little bush
TrippinFlare: have you seen a sequence before?
Cofffee: ASMR Kreygasm
VanishBlox: CoolStoryBob
ktzkalash: GOTTA START PAINTING CORONA
o______________________k: squadCozy squadPH
slimpimp007: yea you can be a mob
bigie: didn't it recently jump to humans from chinese wet markets
VanishBlox: CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob
lgtst_: tap that mouse
St47ik: PixelBob
logi6000: holy shit George just calmed the fuck down. this is not good the CIA called him to stop him form truth speaking and it's working
lgtst_: SUSSSSCEPTIBLE
aasimm: so these are multiple viruses belonging to corona family
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
TrippinFlare: are you trying to find the specific protein @georgehotz ?
slimpimp007: SUSceptible
dj_vicio: @logi6000 he will soon start telling us that we should also listen to the media and buy medicines/vaccines
logi6000: I know
logi6000: there getting to him
aethuall: @georgehotz Do you know what the ANI is across all of the ncov strains? I can't find a good source
tykabmo: @georgehotz I bet 5 bucks with my friend that you wont read this message
almonte550: remember you need to do -1
VanishBlox: Lua gang :)
logi6000: @tykabmo you most likely gon win
TrippinFlare: @georgehotz are you reading chat
Tomishima: python gang checking in
fendermd20: is this about the french guy exposing the patent for corona?
almonte550: There you go
tykabmo: bring on the money!
logi6000: you getting it
iiiiiiillllliiiill: which js framework is best for devloping vaccine?
murkythunder: pog
theonlymonkas: node
logi6000: I'm chatting so you get money and chat gets pushed up more
thisisdrew42: thisisdrew42 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logi6000: there youngo
tykabmo: I knew the odds were in my favor ...about to take the 5 bucks home!
almonte550: @iiiiiiillllliiiill react of course
TrippinFlare: coronavirus vaccine in javascript OMEGALUL
St47ik: LUL
pz3300: George, you are the boy!
St47ik: @TrippinFlare transpiled from typescript
stole_yo_eip: stole_yo_eip subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logi6000: @tykabmo buy weed! but for 5 you really can't get shit
Mariosavitch: yes i think you can
tykabmo: victory 5 bucks baby @logi6000 team player!
Punkfx: @georgehotz have you worked with Go before?
ziNNGG: turn off that little wanka
almonte550: Why it looks like we are getting somewhere?
TrippinFlare: npm install -g coronavirus-vaccine
theonlymonkas: he is
OnlyB1ade: umm
logi6000: @trippinflare nah no npm. pip
TrippinFlare: brew install coronavirus-vaccine
caiooliveira2014: what they doing?
NoPartiesGuy: @TrippinFlare imagine having 256 ssd and not having enough space for this LUL
Mariosavitch: here is the entire thing https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/projects/msaviewer/?rid=7FYNU14F01R&coloring= @georgehotz
aethuall: It also inhibits NF-κB which is good for the virus
TrippinFlare: SPONSORED BY AWS S3 PogChamp
logi6000: @trippinflare how bout Pacman -S python-corona-vax
aethuall: Less cytokine reaction
thxslo: What is his goal ?
Mariosavitch: the posted the entire nuecleotide diff above
firstavegner: chat what is he doing for real ?
allhail2daking: Do you meditate everyday?
logi6000: yo anyone look at zeronet source yet. this offtopic but it looks like good code
VanishBlox: He is making a cure for covid 19 to post on github
VitalyzedTv: his goal is to program a vaccin for corona
Riqour: @firstavegner he is going to code the coronavirus and destroy the world
aethuall: @firstavegner He's trying to understand what the proteins in nCoV do
VanishBlox: and post it on githun
caiooliveira2014: @firstavegner Vaccine for corona I think
Mariosavitch: entire diff https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/projects/msaviewer/?rid=7FYNU14F01R&coloring= @georgehotz
Tanarif: there's already loads of vaccines in testing aren't there?
TrippinFlare: he's hacking the corona computer virus, which originated from Israel
nashesvobodnoye: So we know what certain piece of the protein is doing, but we still don't have a clue *why* these certain arrangements of letters perform a certain function. Maybe you can figure it out, George?
OnlyB1ade: ahhaha
aethuall: Yes, there's many vaccines that are in the clinical trial stage
logi6000: has anyone looked at zeronet. looks like a good project
Mariosavitch: I looked up the entire genome under "blastn" @georgehotz
myaocat: You may want to look at that : http://virological.org/t/alignment-of-58-sarbecovirus-genomes-for-conservation-analysis-of-sars-cov-2/430 @georgehotz
bayarealove: Thwarting coronavirus by not allowing them to replicate
TrippinFlare: Also the sequence of Corona is only ONE PART of the picture. Understanding how it interacts with the human protein is critical.
Marynx: what are you coding ?
NoPartiesGuy: imagine some bio guy just explaining to George some essential basics and the magic happening afterwards LUL
aethuall: I'm holding my tongue @NoPartiesGuy
stole_yo_eip: @Marynx corona virus
firstavegner: @Marynx he's trying to understand corona virus proteins
TrippinFlare: "just put it in a neural net" PogChamp
VanishBlox: we need a bio livestreamer to work with george
VanishBlox: they would be a killer duoe
logi6000: @trippinflare said every person who hasnt used NN
NoPartiesGuy: @aethuall Are you related to this field?
aethuall: Bio livestreamers don't get views
aethuall: @NoPartiesGuy Bioinformatician
sirleeroyjenkins: Is geohotz trying to literally hack the coronavirus
logi6000: @aethuall they need to tho
anotherkidnamedaustin: we love the state, what scam?
logi6000: @sirleeroyjenkins world's largest ctf
anotherkidnamedaustin: btw this is the only stream ive ever considered subbing to
NoPartiesGuy: @aethuall So does it make sense what is he doing or just learning the most basic stuff?
TrippinFlare: LUL
aethuall: I work in microbial genomics though, primarily bacteria
DecayingSkullz: Coronavirus exploits
thxslo: she will hack him beafore he her =)
iiiiiiillllliiiill: a virus is just an agile microservice running in the cloud
VitalyzedTv: WutFace
stole_yo_eip: F
dj_vicio: lol
saintmthw: @aethuall why not just comment helpful stuff for george then?
dj_vicio: he will eventually fall
kirisalolisa: !uptime
anotherkidnamedaustin: i work in micro too, bacteria/fungus tho no viral
dorkmo: chair noise complaints!
VanishBlox: BibleThump WutFace
TrippinFlare: sudo service coronavirus stop
TheKoreanZombi: $5k chair with 3 adjustments. Lol.
Sky_Light_37: @georgehotz left a bit early yesterday, where did we left off?
Mariosavitch: F
dj_vicio: who said the chair was $5k?
aethuall: @saintmthw I think that vaccine development is a very specific field that people who normally develop vaccines know much better than anyone else
logi6000: @trippinflare for the arch users systemctl disable coronavirus
sircrocodile163: @georgehotz your posture is tragic
TrippinFlare: ^ yeah, systemctl is more universal
TheKoreanZombi: @dj_vicio Only the best for geohotz
saintmthw: @aethuall not that. the "basics of biology" you said you're holding your tongue over
hmnvdota: hey guys, what is the challange
stole_yo_eip: @logi6000 works ty
Jehhred: Pandas will do the trick
logi6000: yup
publishcoffee: posture is for humans
THX1342: hmnvdota pwn covid
TrippinFlare: donation goal - new chair LUL
Nopy1: posture is for posers
aethuall: @saintmthw Proteins and virus-host interactions take so long to learn if you don't have bio background
sircrocodile163: @georgehotz you going for that S letter spine?
VanishBlox: if your neck while standing up doesn't look like a crocodile than you are not a real programmer
aethuall: I don't personally know a lot about virus-host interactions myself
aethuall: I only did 2nd year cell bio
aethuall: 1 course
aresfour: what's he up to? 😁😁
slimpimp007: my
aethuall: Rest is genetics, biochem, molbio
firstavegner: @Geo did you know that the sequence of the virus has 33'a s in the end ? that's strange
NoPartiesGuy: @aethuall I mean it's still geohot after all, so he could just learn it much faster I guess
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @aethuall just pretend like the rest of us
dj_vicio: 666 would be stranger @firstavegner
dj_vicio: beast # and trips
TrippinFlare: so we now have the genetic codes of proteins that define coronavirus????
anotherkidnamedaustin: tell everyone stay home, send TSLA's around spraying antiviral = corona defeated
aethuall: @georgehotz https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/genome/doc/ftpfaq/
saintmthw: @aethuall even so, he's the type that would either ignore or appreciate any input you have that could help
Cofffee: monkaS downloading coronavirus
nozpheratu: Check if the page responds to XML or JSON formats or something?
firstavegner: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/nuccore/MN908947
lgtst_: improve TSLA vision to detect corona and arm them with lasers
dalvasorsali: pip install coronavirus
aethuall: @georgehotz You can also use Biopython https://www.biostars.org/p/261774/
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @nozpheratu hacker?
anguscupcake: nooo uninstall it
TrippinFlare: download in 256 gb ssd???
THX1342: are you going to analyze the mutations next?
aasimm: ctrl u
St47ik: @aethuall he didn't like biopython
dorkmo: view source?
Jehhred: Surely Pandas can do it?
Tomishima: scripted Kappa
campinggrounds: try inspecting the requests, maybe iit sends it raw
aasimm: scrape it out
bufferovrflw: Check the Network Tab in DevTools for the download link when you send the request in browser?
bbrak: What is he programming?
Noman35: 5Head @dalvasorsali
TrippinFlare: df.delete_corona()
nozpheratu: @iiiiiiillllliiiill Just a web dev bro
aasimm: try inspect element
maqebane: he is programming ananı amı
aethuall: Biopython is very underrated
dinxpoy: @bbrak he's coding a Corona vaccine he's going to publish on github
bufferovrflw: its RNA, not DNA, reeeeeeeeeeeeeee
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz python or python
TrippinFlare: git clone corona-vaccine
iskjmss: this man is hacking darwin
anguscupcake: so you can just code genetics and turn them into a real substance? bruh
nozpheratu: I thought he was reverse engineering it so he could make it himself in one of those DNA printers
h0h0h0: can someone let me know what exactly we are doing here?
jasondesante: what up GeoHot
VitalyzedTv: why can't i say the word keyb0ard
dj_vicio: hacking the Gibson @h0h0h0
xeroeffect: Hi this is your neighbor. Can you please keep it down. My pussy is taking a nap.
h0h0h0: @dj_vicio oh dang Penn jilette is on the phone now
nozpheratu: @h0h0h0 Making Corona virus bitcoin miner
grizvok: dont do it man
luigifrcruz: Scientists need to upload the genome.
onuei: @nozpheratu stonks
h0h0h0: ( i just watched hackers in the theater last week too)
aethuall: @georgehotz Go to the nextstrain page and scroll to the bottom and hit 'download data'
williamjennings1: Hello
THX1342: VitalyzedTv because only noobs care about "what switches you/re using"
TrippinFlare: open source crispr kit to kill coronavirus
bufferovrflw: THERES DOWNLOAD DATA ON NEXSTRAIN
lemonboxed: they probably got the dataset from a research instituition, they dont actually release the whole dataset unless you pay $$$$$
bufferovrflw: ^^^^
h0h0h0: 1000 VIEWERS lol on a programming stream
Kodak_Z: @h0h0h0 that's new...
h0h0h0: What's new?
bufferovrflw: You can download data on NextStrain ncov, someone let Geogre know please
Lizardan: @h0h0h0 it's not your average programming stream
aethuall: I pinged him about it
aethuall: @georgehotz Go to the nextstrain page and scroll to the bottom and hit 'download data'
BesterGester: @bufferovrflw link the download link to chat
axlebear: When is Corona 2.0 coming out?
kirisalolisa: our hero hacking corona to save us, so inspiring
asaalgk: u can press B to insert cell below
nozpheratu: Where is the fun in that?
TrippinFlare: TSV WutFace TSV WutFace TSV WutFace TSV WutFace
aethuall: god nevermind @georgehotz that's just the tree you can download
h0h0h0: So i understand that we are reverse engineering but.. to what end?
iskjmss: oof
TrippinFlare: to the bit level @h0h0h0
jemoetahh: shit i saw my birthplace in that metadata
dj_vicio: To save the world, what else.
nozpheratu: Find their unprotected S3 bucket
asaalgk: i just got in here, what are we trying to accomplish?
grizvok: same reason george does all of these streams
jasondesante: geohot gonna jailbreak corona
popposbubbolo: what is he doing exactly?
School47: corona on github PogChamp
hitmanhax: PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogU
dj_vicio: researching @popposbubbolo
h0h0h0: Noone is really able to tell you exactly what he is attempting to do in here at the moment.
School47: yeah baby, this is corona code
MuscleMario: Please dont paste that 1.7Mb into jupyter
nr_fury: time
School47: can we launch it LUL???
astr0nils: nCoV is open source, thats why everyone got it PogChamp
TrippinFlare: analyzing genetic sequence of covid-19 @h0h0h0
Ziv0: https://bigd.big.ac.cn/ncov/release_genome this claims to have 1.2k sequences of ncov
School47: @astr0nils and decentralised Kappa
nozpheratu: Search gitub code for one of your seqeunces
jbnunn: ^^^^
h0h0h0: ok. then this is way above my standard programmer head. lol.
Tidusuper91: !uptime
OrlinTheMage: he touches his face too much
Ziv0: if you translate the second button says download all sequences
Trr67: monkaS
Hptenuse: yea no face touching monkaS
aethuall: Ahahaha there's a queue for access credentials
aethuall: That's actually cooked
benakiba: wouldnt be the first to do that for sure
Digital_donger: the virus is proprietary Kappa
iskjmss: getting sued by doctors LUL
logi6000: with all the chrome tabs he must have 1tb of ram
dj_vicio: yea from Israel
aethuall: @georgehotz I really doubt you can get approved for that
lemonboxed: not the virus just the data collected from patients
TrippinFlare: welcome to macOS @logi6000 (:
tkdboy555: Hey, the company my best friend works at is making their software free to use for people trying to help the corona-virus situation, the company is called DataRobot, based out of Boston. Don't know if it's of any interest to you, since you have to submit a request. https://www.datarobot.com/
Nussinov: I just tuned in, can you describe what you're attempting please? :)
logi6000: @trippinflare arch
Lana_Lux: 165 raiders from Lana_Lux have joined!
logi6000: fuck who sent the raiders
JjohnConstantine: LuvHearts
dj_vicio: haha
dj_vicio: shes hot
berke98: My antivirus licence has over, i don’t wanna get corona virus
Mariosavitch: that means u dead
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogU
abk467: @Lana_Lux lanaluHi2
o______________________k: squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega squadOmega
MuscleMario: ... raided lol
T3chHS: @Lana_Lux Pog
faxity: LUL
PiroFloydian: she sent her 165 viewers here
Digital_donger: she makes games PogChamp
rraksut: lanaluHacking
fendermd20: can u explain a bit what is going on in the stream?
Tidusuper91: What are we looking for?
Cofffee: She is trying to hack your stream monkaS
tkdboy555: LUL
bigie: it's like hosting but a bit more stupid
axlebear: monkaS
METH_HEAD_MIKE: @Lana_Lux PogChamp
School47: we can compile another virus PogChamp
BesterGester: People who just joined. He is making vaccine for corona virus
OrlinTheMage: she looks like Angelina Jolie
SHAVEYY_: @Lana_Lux PogChamp
PiroFloydian: nah i feel like raiding is better than hosting
Hptenuse: for the new viewers: he is reverse engineering corona virus to make it into a computer virus
nozpheratu: Lana Lux sounds like a good porn star name
lebop: @georgehotz its a host
silentheee: mathilM mathilS
TrippinFlare: we are downloading coronavirus chat PogChamp we are downloading coronavirus chat PogChamp we are downloading coronavirus chat PogChamp
h0h0h0: Apparently he is analyzing the virus structure. It's unclear to what end he is going it for.
ited01: wtf guys
o______________________k: @nozpheratu squad4
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz encode the coronavirus as base64
Mariosavitch: lol
dj_vicio: Lana Lux Raiders are all from CIA and doctors from cambridge uni. to build a case against geohot
Incurs0: LUL
Nussinov: BesterGester what, is he going to inject some files in people with the disease? Kappa
Bitcoin__: LUL
Digital_donger: Kappa
swagomgswag: Kappa
Skriance: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kappa
Tymski_: Hello Raiders from Lana! We are coding a vaccine for coronavirus!
Mariosavitch: Kappa
sabibas: !commands
adamcernycz: Kappa
bokeee_: atpRtsd
viper262_: LUL
Cofffee: Kappa
jasondesante: we're always positive #mentalhealth
School47: Kappa
Cornflays: Kappa
garam_chai94: Kappa
PiroFloydian: LUL
Hptenuse: Kappa
alexandru_cristiean: HHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAH
nashesvobodnoye: Kappa
bigie: LUL
TrippinFlare: KAPOW
silentheee: haHAA
SHAVEYY_: polotics is for losers btw
TrippinFlare: Kappa
goodlink: Kappa
faxity: Kappa
nashesvobodnoye: LUL
SHAVEYY_: :)
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Sure
jeankx23: MiniK MiniK MiniK MiniK MiniK
DecayingSkullz: LUL LUL
alexandru_cristiean: HAHAHAHAHHAHA
razr22: :)
stole_yo_eip: Kappa
logi6000: calm good joke you just got a noise complaint from the CIA
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz encode the coronavirus as base64
h0h0h0: What do you mean reverse engineer? oh he is explaining YAY!
cockwizard69: show tits
dj_vicio: over 9000!
StealtHy34: what is he exactly doing?
TrippinFlare: C OMEGALUL DE FOR CORONAVIRUS
SHAVEYY_: ogcc
OnlyB1ade: very good
sabibas: dude
SHAVEYY_: Pog
sabibas: what are your specs
TrippinFlare: MacBook Air
nozpheratu: He's making a virus miner for bitcoin
dj_vicio: aderall again
SHAVEYY_: @sabibas some macbook
Ziv0: not the sources code - the compiled code Kappa
cutza: Remember tidepods are the solution
syns0r: encoded in base4
bigie: what if you make a PR and they accept it by accident and get pwnd
SHAVEYY_: encode as base-64
bokeee_: rofl
School47: you should wear mask to protect urself while working with korona @georgehotz Kappa
FargioFarmani: Programming in Unity sucks
bufferovrflw: Any way to "reassemble" it?
h0h0h0: ok he is trying to figure out how it works by analyzing the genetic code.
logi6000: calm good joke. btw he just got a noise complaint from the CIA.
iskjmss: there's a correlation between consumption of tidepods, coronavirus and death
nozpheratu: That's what she said
BesterGester: @h0h0h0 YAY!
fendermd20: do you mean the virus is created by a process and you try to figure out the parts of that procesS?
sabibas: oh he has a macbook with a dock?
dj_vicio: "noise" complaint
Tymski_: @FargioFarmani But programming in VSCode is cool
logi6000: @dj_vicio truth complaint
lemonboxed: with the graphs
SHAVEYY_: can you upload the cure to gitlab instead I hear its better af
h3llphish: h3llphish subscribed with Twitch Prime.
TrippinFlare: gitlab? WutFace
Ziv0: https://bigd.big.ac.cn/ncov/genome/sequence/download/all all.fasta
Tomishima: imagining the self-pressure Kappa
durinwildhammer47: what is even going on here
SHAVEYY_: I cant fucking use gitlabs UI
St47ik: DNA sequencer from ebay LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LULW
nozpheratu: Can you use that to print waifus?
logi6000: calm good joke. btw he just got a noise complaint from the CIA
cutza: Start the brewin'
esence: just take a photo and zoom in on your iphone
lemonboxed: the 600 dollar one must be broken
swagomgswag: cables PogChamp
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz can you make anime irl?
durinwildhammer47: just use some reallllly strong binoculars
Nussinov: youd have to order some enzymes my guy Kappa
thejuror8: @georgehotz Hey Hotz how do you plan on reverse engineering it if you don't know anything about molecular biology ? You will eventually have to come down to that level at some point in order to properly understand it
TrippinFlare: VSCode < Codium - opern source VSCode without Microsoft telemetrics
iskjmss: that shit better come with 2 topre keyboards
DisruptedNexus: DisruptedNexus subscribed with Twitch Prime.
u1337ochka: can't you just like filter all dna in ur body that equals to the sars-cov-2 dna with like a bloom filter or something
DenkoCode: DenkoCode subscribed with Twitch Prime.
durinwildhammer47: who are you?
wijlum: hi
SHAVEYY_: just use vim 4Head
Fundlak: scam train PogChamp
Bitcoin__: SCAM TRAIN!
AresRai: @thejuror8 he will find someone who already did the bio part 5Head
Zerolski: HahaGingercat
BesterGester: @thejuror8 you can learn that stuff online
SHAVEYY_: SHILL TRAIN BOYS !!!
TrippinFlare: Have you tried Brave? @georgehotz
St47ik: PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: scam train Pog
williamjennings1: ArsonNoSexy ArsonNoSexy
astralhustler: comma ftw
kleyy: PogChamp
Digital_donger: PogChamp 2?
iskjmss: Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog Pog
bigie: it's a scam train LUL
Nussinov: PogChamp GAMERS RISE UP
Trr67: LULW
nozpheratu: @thejuror8 >need education to program LUL
exzhhh: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
Cornflays: PogChamp
ipo___: Update us George, are we hitting a breakthrough
VanishBlox: come on GUYS
METH_HEAD_MIKE: Level 2 PogChamp
swagomgswag: SCAM TRAIN
TrippinFlare: LUL
ts012839050: scam train LUL
Cofffee: PogChamp 2
AresRai: scam train PogChamp
careaa: Kappa 4Head
araeasmes: YES PogChamp
mescal33t: beastyPoggers beastyAmazin beastyPoggers beastyAmazin beastyPoggers beastyAmazin
astralhustler: !claim
georgehotz: !claim
bokeee_: bokeee_ subscribed at Tier 1.
St47ik: Scan train PogChamp
milobailey: nice try george Kappa
SHAVEYY_: !claim omg guys I got the new sub!!!
garam_chai94: PogChamp1
FargioFarmani: !claim
VanishBlox: !cvlaim
Digital_donger: dopamine PogChamp
Vjasal: next episode of the stream: making bioweapon at home
logi6000: !claim
lgtst_: CIA up your ass
razr22: !claim
williamjennings1: !claim
AresRai: !claim
cutza: !claim
DecayingSkullz: !claim
lovelyhashbrowns: !claim
Mdog1224: Hypeeeee
tkdboy555: datarobot.com
viper262_: LULW
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp Scam train LUL PogChamp Scam train LUL PogChamp Scam train LUL
williamjennings1: lol
Digital_donger: !claim
TsarSec: KEKW
durinwildhammer47: !claim
St47ik: LUL
swagomgswag: !claim
darushan: !claim
Noman35: Jebaited
Jehhred: !claim
MuscleMario: !claim
gabriel_denis: !claim
swagomgswag: LULW
gombloddo: gombloddo subscribed with Twitch Prime.
fizeh: !claim
TrippinFlare: !claim
inDOObitablee: LUL
williamjennings1: LMao
VanishBlox: 100!
viper262_: danO
electro55555: LUL
tiagodopke: !claim
shlver: SCAM TRAIN
Georgye: !claim
reaganchisholm: !claim
Tymski_: !claim
swagomgswag: LUL
adietrichs: !claim
Foxxy_xx: !claim
kirisalolisa: !scam
araeasmes: !claim
razr22: scammaz
shlver: !claim
ableslayer: !claim
Ghost_001: LUL
ipo___: !UpdateOnBreakthrough
dinxpoy: LOL
OnlyB1ade: !claim
BananStian: !claim
alexandru_cristiean: !claim
OrlinTheMage: !claim
OnlyB1ade: why
williamjennings1: !scam
milobailey: !claim
MacoNighto: !claim
fishing4fish85: !claim
esence: !claim
Aixyn0: !claim
cutza: !scam
lemonboxed: !claim
loligarchia: !claim
syns0r: !claim
PiroFloydian: LUL Jebaited
alexandru_cristiean: HYYYYYYYPE
informalgarlic: !claim
St47ik: !scam
lgtst_: distracts with hype train
TheRealREJack: !claim
Marcel63: !claim
Remembermyfart1: YES
Mdog1224: !claim
happypuppppy: !claim
axlebear: !claim
eadio: !claim
sabibas: !claim
inDOObitablee: !claim
Vjasal: !claim
williamjennings1: lmao
almonte550: !claim
Kodak_Z: !claim
swagomgswag: !claim
tiagodopke: !scam
nozpheratu: !scam
VanishBlox: We are level 2
bigie: I am so hyppped.
Digital_donger: !claim ANY CLAIMERS?
superuserg: !claim
tombradley456: !claim
slowgonzales: !scam
swagomgswag: LUL
arm627: !claim
loligarchia: soos
Sundaexz: !claim
lgtst_: !claim
stole_yo_eip: !claim
Bernasv: !claim
kirisalolisa: !claim
VanishBlox: GO ON BOYS
Nopy1: twitch pls stop
alb12321: !claim
dudvdx: !scam
TrippinFlare: !level 2
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
axlebear: whoa it works
St47ik: BITCONEEEEEEEEECT
Remembermyfart1: !claim
ableslayer: !CLAIM
Noman35: Jebaited LuL
unluckychickenn: i love you george
abhinavneelam: !claim
Cornflays: any gifters? nmpPOGGERS
anguscupcake: fake bro
u1337ochka: !claim
icyvran: !claim
Zerolski: !claim
ableslayer: !claim
SHAVEYY_: LEVEL 2 HOLY FUCK
hir0andobey: !claim
gombloddo: !claim
alexandru_cristiean: COME ON LEVEL 3333333333
r0xtehem0x: !claim
cutza: GIVEMEDOPAMINE
Nussinov: !cough
ipo___: !claimfake
raondev: !claim
korede360: !claim
SHAVEYY_: HOLY SHIT
dvdutch: !claim
SHAVEYY_: HOLY FUCK
azogshady: PogU
TrippinFlare: !claim
imopfloors: !claim
trajenx: scam train
sabibas: wow
azogshady: Pog
tellmewhy_tv: !claim
shlver: SCAM
h0h0h0: !claim
SHAVEYY_: LEVEL 3??
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye subscribed at Tier 3.
logi6000: no this is the CIA distracting us
sabibas: can we do it
JjohnConstantine: !claim
Br4nnon: scam train PogChamp
St47ik: BITCONEEEEEEEEEEEEECT
hitmanhax: !claim
swagomgswag: no way
JohnEGQ: !claim
VanishBlox: WE NEED A NEW SUBSCRIBED
devioux77: lul
FargioFarmani: !claim
gattz_: !claim
SHAVEYY_: WTH!!!
MuscleMario: lol
JefeBezos: !claim
VanishBlox: YEE
luigifrcruz: !claim
Ghost_001: LuL
esence: WE DED ET
tiagodopke: !claim
SHAVEYY_: OMG
DecayingSkullz: !claim
GODaruu: !claim
o______________________k: no :)
ancientchineseelder: LEVEL 3
sabibas: we got it lets go
alexandru_cristiean: LEVEL 3 LET'S GOOOOOOOOOO
swagomgswag: LEVEL 4 PogChamp
SHAVEYY_: WE DID IT BOYS
dorkmo: !claim
Bitcoin__: Who's the longest sub?
Aixyn0: !claim
Penguino138: HYPE IT UP MOTHA FUCKAS
1gonyali: !claim
bufferovrflw: How many psychologists does Twitch employ?
fwef64: !claim
sabibas: level 3
St47ik: LUL
happypuppppy: PogChamp
dunehazard: KEKW
gogenhub: !claim
esence: !claim
icyvran: lol
TrippinFlare: PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN
sabibas: !claim
saintmthw: tier 3 sub PogChamp
lgtst_: FOCUS
milobailey: !claim
MuscleMario: Unlock unlock unlock
u1337ochka: PogChamp
bokeee_: DOPAMINE IS HITTING ME
VanishBlox: !claim
Aixyn0: !scam
tkdboy555: !hype !claim
PiroFloydian: PogChamp
kirisalolisa: !scam
dark_jmat: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
williamjennings1: lmao
shlver: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
logi6000: did we all just get subs
alexandru_cristiean: HYYYYYYYPEEEEEEEEE TRAAAAIINNNNNNN
mescal33t: beasty1more beasty1more beasty1more beasty1more
gattz_: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
TrippinFlare: !claim
St47ik: Scam train PogChamp
bigie: do you really need the twitch benefits LUL
almonte550: !claim
azogshady: Pog Pog
adamcernycz: So new phone call about noise? Kappa
Digital_donger: choo choo PogChamp
milobailey: lvl 10
tombradley456: !claim
TrippinFlare: PogChamp
fwef64: !hype
exzhhh: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
Jehhred: !claim
axlebear: EZ
icyvran: !claim
Aixyn0: !lvl42
Br4nnon: Level 5 unlocks fireball PogChamp
TehQi: !claim
bufferovrflw: How many psychologists are employed at Twitch ?
DecayingSkullz: Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN
azogshady: Pog Pog Pog
alexandru_cristiean: SCAM TRAIN LEVEL 4
rubho: the best kind of scam, where we get out dopamine for completing goals, and you get money
dj_vicio: louder!!!!
Toastie1: PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳
moonify: maisterWHAT maisterWHAT maisterWHAT maisterWHAT maisterWHAT
georgehotz: !claim
williamjennings1: !claim
fwef64: !claim
logi6000: !claim
azogshady: Pog
cutza: !CLAIM
happypuppppy: GIFTED PogChamp
syns0r: !claim
luigifrcruz: !claim
milobailey: FOCUS GEORGE
wrying: !claim
TrippinFlare: !claim
OrlinTheMage: !claim
MuscleMario: !claim
azogshady: Pog Pog
sabibas: RECEPT THOSE DOPES
ad5k: !claim
icyvran: lol
moonify: !claim
Zerolski: !claim
imopfloors: !claim
vicious503: !claim
bokeee_: !claim
camkinstrike: !calim
DecayingSkullz: !claim
viper262_: !claim
parviz_gc: lol
azogshady: Pog
JjohnConstantine: !claim
tremendomendez: !claim Kappa
bufferovrflw: !claim
bigie: i just came
devioux77: LUL
TrippinFlare: PogChamp
Itsmeek0: I SUBSCRIBED TO GEORGE HOTZ TIER 13 AND ONLY RECEIVED SADNESS
Remembermyfart1: !claim
Ncwr: !claim
gattz_: LUL
MorningScifi: !claim
camkinstrike: !claim
alexandru_cristiean: SCAM TRAIN SCAM TRAIN SCAM TRAIN SCAM TRAIN SCAM TRAIN
Ensthor: !claim
parviz_gc: wtf
Marcel63: !claim
trumpetjean: !claim
thejuror8: !claim
Digital_donger: !claim
bigie: !claim
alexandru_cristiean: !claim
superuserg: !claim
VanishBlox: let's do this boys
tehEGO: !claim
slowgonzales: !claim
informalgarlic: DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip
icyvran: Noise claim
trajenx: !claim
viper262_: !clams
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳
ableslayer: !claim
gogenhub: !claim
fwef64: !hype !claim
auron018: !claim
mashafique: !claim
swagomgswag: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
TrippinFlare: LUL
eadio: !claim
MParry: !claim
faxity: hahahaha
azogshady: Pog Pog SCAM TRAIN
cutza: DOPAMINEDOPAMINEDOPAMINE
lgtst_: GOT DAMMIT
CompestLive: !claim
MuscleMario: Free Chicken Tendies
milobailey: !claim
1gonyali: !claim
Kahawa: !claim Scammaz
georgehotz: !claim
Cornflays: LUL
axlebear: !boost
Bernasv: !claim
parviz_gc: this guy
exzhhh: Kappa
mudowoster: !uptime
phrixus_bro: phrixus_bro subscribed at Tier 1.
icyvran: !claim
FargioFarmani: !claim
georgehotz: !claim
K_I_N_N_Y_B_O_T: !claim
williamjennings1: VoHiYo VoHiYo
TrippinFlare: !claim
chargen: !claim
anguscupcake: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
gabriel_denis: !claim
nashesvobodnoye: !claim
GODaruu: !claim
CompestLive: !calim
DeimosTK: !claim
AresRai: !claim
tombradley456: !claim
kleyy: !claim
hitmanhax: !claim
georgehotz: !claim
MuscleMario: !Free Chicken Tendies
TrippinFlare: PogChamp
tremendomendez: PogChamp
seniorkae: !claim
esence: !claim
williamjennings1: !claim
SHAVEYY_: pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4 pOGcHAMP level 4
Mdog1224: !claim
Noman35: !claim
Ghost_001: !claim
georgehotz: !claim
h0h0h0: !claim
fishing4fish85: !claim
exzhhh: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
iskjmss: !claim
happypuppppy: !claim
u1337ochka: !claim
VanishBlox: !claim
heroinefather_: !claim
o______________________k: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
neuromancer2: !claim
informalgarlic: !scam
RapidEU: !claim
simonas1122: !claim
fwef64: !claim
immutable0bject: !claim
azogshady: !claim
darushan: !claim
Abnico: !claim
mashafique: Pog
DenkoCode: claim()
onuei: REVERSE ENGINEER DOPAMINE RECEPTORS
parviz_gc: LEVELLLLLLLL 5
devioux77: salrosSCAM salrosSCAM salrosSCAM salrosSCAM
CompestLive: !claim
r0xtehem0x: !claim
xXICEW0LFXx: !claim
St47ik: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. This is a scam imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
shlver: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
williamjennings1: what is going on
shoji22: !claim
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
swagomgswag: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
dorkmo: uni1
void8TV: !claim
alexandru_cristiean: !claimHYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYPEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
logi6000: !claim
RapidEU: rofl
gattz_: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
tkdboy555: !claim
teslost: !claim
williamjennings1: !claim
dj_vicio: !claim
ninjadidio: !claim
inDOObitablee: LUL
tehEGO: i dont know what is hypening?
kirisalolisa: Type !scam to restore sanity
SHAVEYY_: yes
alexandru_cristiean: !claim
williamjennings1: what is going on
gombloddo: !claim
mashafique: LULW
jasondesante: bro lets get to level 60
superuserg: !claim
mescal33t: beastyH beastyH beastyH
dvdutch: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
DecayingSkullz: !claim
onuei: TYPE CLAME TO CONFIRM AUTISM
ableslayer: ———————————————————————— imGlitch You have been gifted the Golden Kappa!—————————————————————
informalgarlic: o______________________k ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
takkeo: !claim
K_I_N_N_Y_B_O_T: !claim
trajenx: TOS
trumpetjean: !claim
azogshady: PogU
dvdutch: Hype
JjohnConstantine: !claim
dj_vicio: how you use bits
eadio: haHAA
icyvran: !claim
o______________________k: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ .
FargioFarmani: !claim
cutza: BITS COST MONEY
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳 PogChamp 💳
1gonyali: !claim
fishing4fish85: !claim
CompestLive: !claim
eadio: !claim
Zasuslive: !claim
VanishBlox: !claim
williamjennings1: !claim
Abnico: !claim
gabriel_denis: !claim
anguscupcake: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ Jehhred: !claim
neuromancer2: !claim
esence: 1% KEKW
georgehotz: !claim
pjayys77: !claim
TrippinFlare: pip uninstall coronavirus Cheer100
urhentom: !claim
dj_vicio: !cliam
arm627: !claim
Trr67: LUL
St47ik: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. This is a scam imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
luigifrcruz: !claim
milobailey: !claim
VanishBlox: BOYS COME ON
dj_vicio: !claim
Noman35: !claim
OnlyB1ade: OnlyB1ade subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! yee
tokumei64: it's a meme
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
almonte550: !claim
AresRai: !claim
devioux77: LMAO
Bernasv: !claim
Ziv0: LUL
auron018: !claim
fizeh: LUL
syns0r: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
williamjennings1: !claim what
Wolvey: no Kappa
bokeee_: ROFL
o______________________k: LMFAO
Panda1Express: LUL
shlver: LMAO
maqebane: !claim
BananStian: !claim
xXICEW0LFXx: that is most definitely a scam
pdungeytv: LUL
anguscupcake: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
o______________________k: GOTTEM
kleyy: LUL
viper262_: LUL
swagomgswag: its not real LUL @georgehotz
SHAVEYY_: go to this @georgehotz https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/home
happypuppppy: LUL
milobailey: LUL
dongmuya: !claim
Noman35: LuL
fizeh: HE JUST FOUND OUT
Itsmeek0: HYPE TRAIN UPPP
TsarSec: LULW
Restless_Bagel: Jebaited
informalgarlic: o______________________k ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
homies7: keep us excited cheer10
utkuzz: shshshhsahas
shlver: Jebaited
xXICEW0LFXx: lmfao
icyvran: !claim
exzhhh: lul
swagomgswag: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
tremendomendez: LUL
Julll: LUL
kito__: LUL
exzhhh: hahahahhaa
o______________________k: monkaS
korede360: !claim
nozpheratu: @georgehotz When Hype train gets to level 5, you gift all your viewers subs.
Sky_Light_37: LULW
MuscleMario: Free Chicken Tendies
Digital_donger: Jebaited classic
tokumei64: ITS A MEME COPYPASTA
tiagodopke: GOT EM
exzhhh: trolled
maqebane: lel
dvdutch: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
unluckychickenn: Pog
syns0r: !claim
AresRai: Jebaited
void8TV: !claim
SHAVEYY_: go to this @georgehotz https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/home !!
Cornflays: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: THE !CLAIM IS A SCAM
Noman35: LUL
Sundaexz: LUL
tremendomendez: Jebaited
mescal33t: beastyLULWW beastyLULWW beastyLULWW beastyLULWW
chargen: !claim
Cofffee: monkaS
FaCeFat: LMAAAOO¨
Ghost_001: LUL
PiroFloydian: LUL Jebaited
dj_vicio: hahahahahaha
inDOObitablee: LUL
Nussinov: Jebaited
kirisalolisa: shshssh
bottters: o______________________k ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch You have been gifted a subscription on this channel. Type !claim to activate. imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
St47ik: stop NotLikeThis
Noman35: Jebaited
viper262_: BAN
bufferovrflw: !ban
anguscupcake: I SUBBED TEO U
SHAVEYY_: go to this @georgehotz https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/home
dinxpoy: LUL
Cofffee: monkaS
Ziv0: LMAO
freshsoclean: gay
kleyy: i though he was trolling
milobailey: lmaaao
St47ik: Jebaited
void8TV: !claim wtf
CompestLive: LMAOOOOOO
ableslayer: LUL
o______________________k: LMFAO
Noman35: Jebaited LuL
kirisalolisa: LMAO
tokumei64: IT DOESN'T DO ANYTHIN
ShewNs: looooool
Fundlak: Jebaited
williamjennings1: what!!!!!
wrying: LUL
Digital_donger: a classic Jebaited
axlebear: Jebaited
mickjaggerrrr: lol
bigie: @george it's a meme not a scam
Vjasal: why would anyone disable hypetrain
cutza: LOL
swagomgswag: Jebaited
kito__: Jebaited
bufferovrflw: I'm a gifted child
almonte550: LMAO
ipo___: U all.. my mom just gifted me
adamcernycz: LUL
Fantasma56: monkaS
alexandru_cristiean: ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ imGlitch This is the first time I use Twitch and I'm already bought imGlitch ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬ஜ۩۞۩ஜ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
dvdutch: mines the only one that looks good
Cornflays: GOT EM
devioux77: salrosSCAM salrosSCAM salrosSCAM salrosSCAM salrosSCAM
dj_vicio: owned again! hahahahaha
void8TV: Jebaited
ts012839050: bang cya
swagomgswag: HIDE EM TriHard HIDE EM TriHard HIDE EM TriHard HIDE EM TriHard HIDE EM TriHard HIDE EM TriHard
Riqour: gift me
informalgarlic: but you are gift5d
alexandru_cristiean: Sold*
SpecialAgentSkye: You are a very gifted developer Geo :)
BrodatyWhiteBear: quebMonka
logi6000: what if I say I'm in a gifted class?
azogshady: THIS DUDE A BORDERLINE BOOMER
milobailey: how they scam with hype train?
phrixus_bro: i dont know what happened i got caught in the hype
St47ik: TriHard 7
tokumei64: not a scam!
revolutionist123: Jebaited
tkdboy555: alexandru banned too please
dinxpoy: Geo is such a gifted programmer
Remembermyfart1: DUDE WE HAVE TO REACH LEVEL 5 BEFORE TESLA
Wolvey: !claim Kappa
AresRai: Jebaited lol
void8TV: LUL
mescal33t: beasty1more beasty1more beasty1more
xXICEW0LFXx: it's a scam lol
Tomishima: natural selection at work
informalgarlic: @georgehotz but you are g9fted!!!!
o______________________k: HAHAHA
bufferovrflw: bro you just posted cringe
exzhhh: xD
xXICEW0LFXx: lmfao
slowgonzales: !ban
williamjennings1: VoHiYo
aiex42: Ban train about to start lol
dj_vicio: LOL
fizeh: BANNED LUL
alexandru_cristiean: :(
Digital_donger: monkaS
SHAVEYY_: G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin
ipo___: u talent, u jifted
SHAVEYY_: G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin G TriHard I be flexin
St47ik: Chat stop NotLikeThis
SpecialAgentSkye: ROLLED
DenkoCode: Hacks ps, cars, iphone -> cant figure out how twitch works
bufferovrflw: KEEP THE HYPE TRAIN
VanishBlox: Boys the hype train is gonna cool down
esence: NO FUN IN THIS CHANNEL
pjayys77: the man is Emtional baggage though
cutza: !SCAM
veeraman: how close are we?
exzhhh: hahahhahaa
Nussinov: Hundreds of teenagers are outsmarting this streamer
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
axlebear: EZ jebait
VanishBlox: HYPE HYPE HYPE HYPE TRAIN
happypuppppy: socially engineered FeelsBadMan
lyricrush: WHAT KEYB0ard do you have
bufferovrflw: HYYYYYYYYYPEEEEEEE
TrippinFlare: ANY OIL PRINCESS??
void8TV: Its just a troll even
lgtst_: HYPE CONDUCTORS
Ghost_001: me :)
nozpheratu: PICK ME
SHAVEYY_: !claim
Orennnn: lmao
gombloddo: ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
dj_vicio: he RE coronavirus but can't ban ppl from Twitch
lgtst_: they already there
MuscleMario: PogChamp100 lets get some emotez
tokumei64: Jebaited
Noman35: ill do it :)
VanishBlox: HYPE HYPE HYPE HYPE
FargioFarmani: its me
almonte550: Can I be a conductor?
swagomgswag: ME PogChamp
shlver: Me :)
MorningScifi: choo choo
Lizardan: me
icyvran: Go go go go
SernOne: Once you sequence the cure to the virus just go ahead and CD/CI that puppy, we'll be waiting
tkdboy555: TIME THEN OUT, GIT 'EM
boxtooo: me :)
DecayingSkullz: Hyper train ENGINEER
Sky_Light_37: me :)
SpecialAgentSkye: not me :)
bufferovrflw: CHOOO CHOOOOOOO
tremendomendez: me poh
pjayys77: like a mod
bigie: LUL it's like manual for herding sheep
tehEGO: lol
MuscleMario: yeah w/e
Cornflays: me nmpSMILE
Mariosavitch: too soon
Noman35: monkaS
Ghost_001: PogChamp
AresRai: LUL
cutza: pog
ipo___: GeorgeNutz
gombloddo: PokCharizard
icyvran: lol
TsarSec: no shit
OnlyB1ade: PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard
almonte550: Coronavirus band people permanently
veeraman: how close are we?! 🦠
dj_vicio: why he complaining then lol
xXICEW0LFXx: it is definitely a way to make more money, but hey it gives you more money too soooooo
ts012839050: PogChamp100
nozpheratu: We need adblocker for twitch
DenkoCode: >man twitch.com
dj_vicio: !claim
Loutlot: Cheer1000
abhinavneelam: George Botz
Wolvey: PogChamp
PiroFloydian: HOLY
OnlyB1ade: PokGarchomp PokGarchomp
abhinavneelam: George Lotz
St47ik: MrDestructoid
kito__: will there be vod of this ?
almonte550: I don't even know how to use bits
tremendomendez: PogChamp
trajenx: is george going to hack the corona virus?
Lizardan: STAFF PogChamp
PiroFloydian: 1K bits!
saintmthw: staff gave 10 bucks PogChamp
TrippinFlare: dilemmas of George Hotz Cheer300
fdddff: fdddff subscribed with Twitch Prime.
tehEGO: i bet twitch cant max out hype train
Cornflays: @Loutlot nmpGUN
faxity: Loutlot LUL
MorningScifi: Check for n-grams, George?
mescal33t: @Loutlot beastyPoggers beastyAmazin
pjayys77: lvl 5
swagomgswag: LEVEL 5 PogChamp
dj_vicio: level 4 yay!!!
St47ik: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Loutlot: scammed
tremendomendez: PogChamp next level
TrippinFlare: PogChamp
Itsmeek0: LEVELLLLLLLLLLLLLL UPPPPPPPPPPPPPP LEVELLLLLLLL 5555555555555555555
Digital_donger: PogChamp insane
exzhhh: Scammed
trajenx: i don't think the FDA will approve a self-driving corona virus
dyslexicgruffalo: so when he says hes reverse engineering what is he meaning by that?
Nussinov: level 5 is for noobs try reaching level 10
logi6000: how do we know when the hype train going
St47ik: Final level PogChamp
gombloddo: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
almonte550: What are the last level?
saixj: got to clean up the data
imopfloors: PogChamp100
hitmanhax: Pog EXCLUSIVE EMOTES
dj_vicio: FDA are dumb brutes
brownyyyylocks: so many ads on this channel
informalgarlic: FINAL LEVEL CHAT!
StealtHy34: can someone explain me what is he doing please? im dumb
tiagodopke: who cares about the FDA
almonte550: I want to see the last level before coronavirus hits me!
JustAsGoodJo: Pog a fellow scientist :)
Nussinov: that would be called a deletion mutation Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL PogChamp
alexandru_cristiean: HypeUnicorn1
logi6000: @tiagodopke vapers mostly
pjayys77: "reverse engineering the coronavirus"
St47ik: Any gifters TriHard
alexandru_cristiean: :HypeUnicorn1
DenkoCode: self driving corona virus
firstavegner: he's trying to understand the relations between the proteins in the coronavirus
Cornflays: any gifters guys? nmpPeepo
anguscupcake: he is building a wall and making the coronavirus pay for it
pjayys77: no one knows what it means but its provocative
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 5 PogChamp
JustAsGoodJo: untranslated region on the 5 prime end
almonte550: What level of autonomy does coronavirus has? has it hit level 5 yet?
grey_street: PogChamp
mik12f4: I wish you did more videos like this.
JustAsGoodJo: sides of mRNA are not translated into protein
tehEGO: can all the crypto miners just start contributing to coronavirus
Nussinov: the 5-UTR is there for the mRNA processing machinery to bind :) it usually does not encode any proteins
limpid_kzonix: hi, from Ukraine) nice to see you on twitch!!!
dyslexicgruffalo: what exacyly is he doing?
St47ik: @tehEGO they can't
tehEGO: and have the coin pay percentage of solving
Remembermyfart1: just throw deep learning at the problem, dude
Lizardan: @dyslexicgruffalo coronavirus reverse engineering
St47ik: ASICs are for crypto only
TrippinFlare: tf.train_coronavirus_vaccine()
dj_vicio: for those asking what he's doing STFU and keep watching. If you're smart enough you'll understand. If not, god help you.
auron018: introns Google that, it will not be included in the mRNA
Mariosavitch: model.fit
mescal33t: cheer200
almonte550: @dyslexicgruffalo learning stuff
St47ik: 20% PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: corona crypto LUL
dyslexicgruffalo: @Lizardan i get that but what is he actually doing and why does eh think it'll help?
samu79rai: yo george wat up
dyslexicgruffalo: jw
tehEGO: the combinations are transactions
Feedael: Feedael subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months!
Lizardan: @dyslexicgruffalo trying to find a cure
Nussinov: 5'-UTR----I'm Retarded----3'-UTR
trumpetjean: trumpetjean subscribed with Twitch Prime.
dj_vicio: final lvel guys come on!
hitmanhax: PogChamp 54%
TrippinFlare: LEVEL 5 CHAT PogChamp
dj_vicio: 1 min to go
St47ik: 1min left PogChamp
logi6000: when does the Google trends part of George's steam come
TrippinFlare: !claim
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye gifted a Tier 1 sub to iskjmss!
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye gifted a Tier 1 sub to 1shortking!
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye gifted a Tier 1 sub to 33333333333333!
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye gifted a Tier 1 sub to iRenansz!
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye gifted a Tier 1 sub to 64pillars!
AnAnonymousCheerer: Anon67
TrippinFlare: PogChamp
aiex42: HYPE TRAIN LVL 5 is the last level
dj_vicio: holy.....
Cornflays: nmpPOGGERS
St47ik: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
pjayys77: dayum 138 %
hitmanhax: PogChamp DODGED
informalgarlic: skaPOG skaPOG skaPOG skaPOG
Sky_Light_37: PogChamp
TrippinFlare: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
bufferovrflw: HYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYPEEEEEE
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 5 PogChamp LEVEL 5 PogChamp
brownyyyylocks: gift me
grey_street: Hype
alycia: test¨'
jasondesante: I hope they increase the level cap of hype train with the release of burning crusade
happypuppppy: PogChamp
mescal33t: beastyPoggers beastyPoggers beastyPoggers
JjohnConstantine: PridePan PridePan PridePan
somnium_s: !uptime
Aixyn0: !train
milobailey: HYPE SCAM
iskjmss: @nashesvobodnoye spasibo brat)))
Izimoney92100: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp SeemsGood
almonte550: Did we broke it ?
St47ik: 140%
1ntegral_: Dynamic programming is the key for alignement comparison algoirtihms @georgehotz
pjayys77: 30 Seconds Monka
hitmanhax: PogChamp OVER 100
TrippinFlare: DELETE CORONA PogChamp DELETE CORONA PogChamp DELETE CORONA PogChamp
aiex42: SCAM TRAIN HYPE
logi6000: I mean if I could get gifted thatd be great
bufferovrflw: gift sub pls
pjayys77: give all the munies
St47ik: TriHard 7
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 5 140% PogChamp LEVEL 5 140% PogChamp
bokeee_: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
nashesvobodnoye: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
imopfloors: HypeUnicorn1
TrippinFlare: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
trumpetjean: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
pjayys77: it was a good run
Izimoney92100: lvl 5 bois
happypuppppy: asking for handouts :z
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
dvdutch: HypeDragon5
iskjmss: PogChamp
mescal33t: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
bufferovrflw: 250 bytes bruh
logi6000: choo fucking choo bitch the next station is anal devestation
cutza: !coronavirus
St47ik: PogChamp
gameinchanel: can you CRISPR edit the covid-19 to super covid-2020 alien edition
FargioFarmani: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1 1-Monats-AbonnentTwitch Primetrumpetjean: Choo Chooo
bokeee_: i did great dad )
bigie: level 5 autonomy
Cornflays: LUL
Kodak_Z: kodakzUSA
dyslexicgruffalo: !streamtime
ipo___: Nutty George
HoiskyPoisky: LuvHearts
dj_vicio: @logi6000 you sure know about that subject, do you?
dyslexicgruffalo: !time
nashesvobodnoye: LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush LuvBlush
auron018: !time
Lana_Lux: Hello!!
TrippinFlare: can you push your CRISPR changes to github on the coronavirus vaccine branch?
gameinchanel: kntentHelo
St47ik: @Lana_Lux hey Lana PogChamp
Sky_Light_37: @georgehotz can you zoom the notebook a little bit? pretty hard to read
zak_krack: LUL extra letter
Lathendros: it was me sorry
zak_krack: alien dna
pjayys77: F that W
theeliteoftheelite21: it stands for wuhan
Mariosavitch: git commit -am 'Typo' @georgehotz
TsarSec: lanaluCat
FargioFarmani: who is Lana??
SHAVEYY_: OMG
anguscupcake: no
Nussinov: W usually means weak for pyramidines i think like A or T?
SHAVEYY_: NOOO
JustAsGoodJo: translating into protein :)
logi6000: no
DecayingSkullz: Oh my
St47ik: mods cmonBruh
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
T3chHS: LOL
dvdutch: yum
pjayys77: hmm mod boyz
patulskitime: ban
saixj: clean the data
cutza: ban
stole_yo_eip: W
SHAVEYY_: monkaS MODS!!!
Izimoney92100: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
alycia: Make me mod and I can BAN
shlver: KappaPride
Mariosavitch: git commit -am 'More typos'
electro55555: is that a lolipop
ipo___: white stuff wut?
thebiggaeboi: LMAO
Lana_Lux: Could anyone fill me in on this process?
SHAVEYY_: GEO SCROLL UP
Ghost_001: LUL
St47ik: @georgehotz get mods bro NotLikeThis
Mariosavitch: lol
logi6000: george didn't even know what to do when he looked at chat
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: no mods
JustAsGoodJo: N is usually denoted as a missing nucleotide :)
TrippinFlare: no ones has any clue @Lana_Lux
alycia: I am willing to be mod!
Mariosavitch: git commit -am 'add random characters to confuse hackers'
lebop: @georgehotz just give me mod so i can ban them
bufferovrflw: try except?
1ntegral_: Dynamic programming is the key for alignement comparison algorithms @georgehotz
KruptWorld: hahah youre hilarious geohot!
shlver: @Lana_Lux asking what hes doing is a banned question
Lana_Lux: @TrippinFlare LUL
dj_vicio: dont look chat please
St47ik: PogChamp
CompestLive: lmso
Lana_Lux: Ooooo
CompestLive: lmao
alycia: TEST
anguscupcake: what mac does george use
abk467: PogChamp
TrippinFlare: Kappa
SHAVEYY_: PogChamp
almonte550: @georgehotz can I be mod
CompestLive: I want sub :(
nashesvobodnoye: PogChamp
logi6000: Lana ban that dick dude
Ghost_001: monkaS
CompestLive: Or mod lol
rraksut: the people asking for mods are the same people on alt accounts causing trouble
Loutlot: ?
knilecrack: what are you trying to do?
METH_HEAD_MIKE: monkaS
Mariosavitch: i sent you all the diff code, can I be a mod?
Ghost_001: mod corona monkaS
u1337ochka: why would anyone ban people
FargioFarmani: can I be mod please?
Bitcoin__: Twitch Staff :)
Restless_Bagel: staff :)
SpecialAgentSkye: I have contributed nothing. Can i be mod? :)
CompestLive: I always make the chat lit and HQ gib mod kappa
benakiba: <message deleted>
Cornflays: monkaS
bufferovrflw: Can't you just try except for the KeyErrors?
St47ik: :)
lebop: lol
OnlyB1ade: yea
dvdutch: <message deleted>
faxity: Loutlot hype train conductor PogChamp
SHAVEYY_: can I be mod?
TrippinFlare: I have 84 commits can i be mod george
Lana_Lux: Can I ban everyone? :)
SHAVEYY_: :)
pjayys77: whoa our twitch overlords are present
kakurai: so many saint people over here
stole_yo_eip: @Lana_Lux me first
samu79rai: Squid1 Squid2 copyThis pastaThat Squid4
bufferovrflw: George, try except for the KeyErrors?
ColdZer0o: @Lana_Lux just end me
St47ik: @Lana_Lux ban the virus LUL
Vjasal: are you looking at genome of viruses that only infect humans, or other ones too? @georgehotz
publishcoffee: @Lana_Lux it would be an honor to be banned by you
logi6000: @lana_lux shit George we have a non comrade in the union
TrippinFlare: i will review your PRs can i be mod pls
ezamlaid: what is he doing?
Riqour: can i be mod? Kappa
KruptWorld: is this part of your church youre starting? i want in!
trajenx: twitch staff might ban us for coronaS misinformation :(
Nussinov: table for the different letters https://www.bioinformatics.org/sms/iupac.html
ytazn: Yep
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz I don't know x86 assembly, can I be mod :)
Lana_Lux: LUL
FargioFarmani: who is this Lana??
SHAVEYY_: @FargioFarmani game dev streamer
conductor1: I have no idea whats goin on :)
ytazn: Yep cock
knilecrack: twitcher
logi6000: @fargiofarmani nobody know she just raided the stream and became a mod
Lizardan: @conductor1 noone does
conductor1: thank god
xMrDidas: What is he doing ? just joinned
ytazn: RlyTho
saixj: check chat someone posted a link above
DBJNR876: @georgehotz those 16 Quadros you have in your machine better be Folding
FargioFarmani: well up to a great start then for Lana
T3chHS: @FargioFarmani a talented game dev
logi6000: @xmrdidas bannes
11plus4thinking: did you make some good money shorting the market?
publishcoffee: @xMrDidas he's hacking the coronavirus
rgbeezus: SeemsGood
AresRai: @11plus4thinking I seen a few byron viewers in here already SeemsGood
alycia: waffleD
dorkmo: highlighted message trainnn chooo
samu79rai: wow 16 quads.
ytazn: RitzMitz
almonte550: biopython again
stole_yo_eip: ../
JustAsGoodJo: there are ton of sequence alignment algorithms that score based upon missmatched bps
logi6000: I got 800 channel points just from this stream
11plus4thinking: @AresRai havent watched that hobo in months
PiroFloydian: ayyy we love memoization
rgbeezus: choo
abk467: choo choo
alycia: -380
cutza: Choo
dorkmo: choooo
n00b_Solid: CHUGGA CHUGGA
METH_HEAD_MIKE: choo choo
tokumei64: choo choo choooo
ytazn: Choo
SpecialAgentSkye: quack
shlver: Choo
1ntegral_: Yeah dynammic programming works great for alignement comparison algorithms !
DecayingSkullz: choo chooooooo
publishcoffee: choooooooooooooo
iskjmss: ANY -380ers?
TrippinFlare: PAIR programming with twitch chat PogChamp PAIR programming with twitch chat PogChamp PAIR programming with twitch chat PogChamp PAIR programming with twitch chat PogChamp
r0xtehem0x: Cheer100 chooooo chooooo
dorkmo: choooooo
Ziv0: chooo
rubho: train noises
DecayingSkullz: choo choooooo
BesterGester: -380
OnlyB1ade: CHOo0
ited01: i can do this
knilecrack: damn
shlver: choo
Bitcoin__: Your neighbor is crazy, move out D:
dorkmo: chuga chooooo
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: CHOOO PogChamp CHOOO PogChamp CHOOO PogChamp CHOOO PogChamp CHOOO PogChamp
ProtoLambda: chooo
dj_vicio: @Lana_Lux why you restrict non-subscribers from watching your videos?
almonte550: KappaHD
kleyy: wow
logi6000: @ited01 we found the true hacker
almonte550: MiniK MiniK
ytazn: Pog
Mariosavitch: lol
dorkmo: chitty chitty choo choo
miths: You guys excited about the new 14'' mbp?
Sky_Light_37: achoooooooooo corona train
ited01: @logi6000 xD
VanishBlox: Goodnight George
yevheniiushtyk: skrr skrr
toasty_jk2: @georgehotz that's why there are w, y and r's in the "dna" : https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FASTA_format
ited01: now it's purple
alycia: is corona created by the governemnt?
knilecrack: no
ited01: no
Cornflays: -380 LUL
michownz: no lol
logi6000: @ited01 who are you and whos is so wise In the ways of science
highxsnow_: yes
mik12f4: Is this Part 1 of 10?
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz is it hard to self-taught math?
KruptWorld: are you finding the jailbreak for cornavirus? XD
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL
JustAsGoodJo: sequence alignment is a very open field in bioinformatics and genomics atm
MuscleMario: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1 me got it
TrippinFlare: you need a library in this case @georgehotz
Mariosavitch: 60 page algo
TrippinFlare: github search
Nussinov: the scoring for biosequences is rather tricky because you know, evolution and stuff
samu79rai: you can do it
21_savior: PogChamp
void8TV: Use dynamic programming for protein folding
TrippinFlare: git clone coronavirus
KruptWorld: can someone fill me in on what hes trying to achieve here?
HoiskyPoisky: phone call inc
almonte550: Finally, some loops and funciotns
vidminok: attaaaggtt
Mariosavitch: its in the title
TrippinFlare: can we write it in rust?
zak_krack: I have never seen a twitch stream like this one.
logi6000: @trippinflare were all bouta do it
21_savior: git blame china
Crayonsss: can someone tl;dr how this works?
Cornflays: FeelsAmazingMan 🍄 Time
theonlymonkas: hands
Crayonsss: what hes doing
1ntegral_: @zak_krack Same
KruptWorld: ya but like how what??! lol
almonte550: Can we write it in go?
Nussinov: 5'--- Pepega ---3'
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: pee pee time
bokeee_: gawd daym thats a loud toilet ROFL
lgtst_: tl;dr - it doesn't
frantisek1337: what keybord do you have
void8TV: @georgehotz Protein folding is NP Hard bro
knilecrack: call it twitch_covid
logi6000: call it CIA IS WATCHING
peacedivision: Is he hacking the ps4 ? finally ?
samu79rai: PowerUpL CoolStoryBob PowerUpR
KruptWorld: lol
miths: no tmux DansGame
Nussinov: HACKER ALERT
KruptWorld: hes hacking nature @peacedivision
theonlymonkas: vim
SpecialAgentSkye: He is hacking Corona PogChamp
yevheniiushtyk: why do you do ls and ls -l everytime you create a new dir?
Anin209: Hackman PogChamp
KruptWorld: just like he said we wanted to
imopfloors: George needs to make a bioinformatics startup
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk Reflex, I do the same
KruptWorld: i think its the start of his church!
almonte550: @void8TV he is not folding anything yet
TrippinFlare: alias l='ls -lha'
saintmthw: @yevheniiushtyk muscle memory after cd
peacedivision: @KruptWorld fuck nature, i want ps4 hacked :(
1ntegral_: what's your setup ? @georgehotz
JefeBezos: iTerm and zshell are unreal
yevheniiushtyk: oh ok haha
bigie: vi not vim DansGame
dinxpoy: guys he's creating a ps5 emulator for x86 PC's
KruptWorld: @peacedivision get started on it then
yevheniiushtyk: i can type fast but i can
almonte550: neovim > vim
yevheniiushtyk: cant type that fast while i code or in terminal lmao
peacedivision: @KruptWorld i don't know shit about coding and stuff
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/corona
zak_krack: /fun/corona
knilecrack: this is how it all started
zak_krack: what a path
TrippinFlare: git clone https://github.com/geohot/corona.git
KruptWorld: youre the fuckn man!
logi6000: just cloned it
almonte550: finally, now I can download some coronas
JustAsGoodJo: python tab struggles lol
VGBurnzy: i wish i understood this :/
KruptWorld: i have a titan rtx sitting here let me know if i can contribute somehow
tokumei64: @KruptWorld folding@home :)
mashafique: You should post more often on Instagram
KruptWorld: im a mid-level programmer i would say
KruptWorld: oh ya i wanted to get on that
Nussinov: KruptWorld Kappa
pistolpetepcp: are you doing science today
hir0andobey: can this actually help to create a vaccine?
TsarSec: join the folding@home project for the rona @KruptWorld
zak_krack: i loving george's speed. not at typing, but at making progress
Keijo: i would call myself a golden legendary master lever programmer
Tomishima: scripted Kappa
diegoarigony: poor kb
KruptWorld: but what is geohot doing? literally programming a folding protein? lol
samu79rai: kill the Corona virus for us all George
MrJeff_: @KruptWorld Folding @ Home. But i heard they're struggling with bandwith as it went from 30,000 users to 400,000 in the past week.
KruptWorld: @haha diegoarigony
miths: We demand Plague inc playthrough to prove you know anything about pandemics.
AresRai: hes having fun :
Nussinov: KruptWorld right now I would say he's analyzing the available sequences
almonte550: @KruptWorld just learning stuff
logi6000: @diegoarigony it sounds amazing I'm gonna get the one he has soon
ohko10: !uptime
zak_krack: I think he's trying to understand its function, and how the variants differ from each other
dj_vicio: lol
bigie: ok everyone start making PRs LUL
firstavegner: yes that what's he's doing
zak_krack: the bits that don't change are likely to be important bits
almonte550: whitespaces > tabs
KruptWorld: @zak_krack you mean hes created like a comparing tool?
miths: spaces monkaS
KruptWorld: creating*
Sky_Light_37: W LUL R K
zak_krack: "Phe / F UUU, UUC "
zak_krack: Sounds rude
JustAsGoodJo: i need to learn these shortcuts tbh lol
MrJeff_: @KruptWorld You can contribute your GPU or CPU to Folding @ Home.
TrippinFlare: W OMEGALUL R K
SHAVEYY_: bro I thought you independent hacker who dont need no work
FoxMcWeezer: What’s the corinavirus
yevheniiushtyk: recently got hhkb pro 2, gonna take some time to get used to it lmao
zak_krack: @KruptWorld I think he's trying to use an existing one from biopython
dj_vicio: everyone needs to work
shieeeeeeeeet: !uptime
almonte550: @MrJeff_ I'm already contributing but they doesn't have any WU left, I switch to Boinc
samu79rai: tell it what to do
Br4nnon: where are you at in your project
miths: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
peacedivision: so is he going to find a vaccine doing this ?
samu79rai: u make up the rules here
1ntegral_: Why aren't you Twitch partner ? à
1ntegral_: @georgehotz
MrJeff_: @almonte550 Check LLT's video, they're setting up another server for users as they have 10gb.
theonlymonkas: LUL
pistolpetepcp: zsh vs bash
VGBurnzy: @miths nobody cares
r0kz_: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
toasty_jk2: @Lana_Lux :)
Cornflays: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
Keijo: this is very boomer chat
dj_vicio: moooods
1ntegral_: @pistolpetepcp Is that even a question of course Zsh !
BesterGester: @peacedivision probably not
theonlymonkas: lol
AresRai: meh copypasta
blazeofglorytv: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I’m fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I’m just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you’re a true fan
SHAVEYY_: check latest commit comments
pedrovictortech: @miths Imagine needing to have things to prove that you are a fan
Keijo: needs more hydracock
bokeee_: this chat is dank ngl
slimpimp007: ayo somebody come get their manz
zak_krack: zak_krack subscribed at Tier 1.
Bagofpotatoes: what's Geo trying to do? something about sequencing the virus genome?
miths: @pedrovictortech imagine getting mad over a copypasta LUL
T3chHS: So you're going by "georgehotz" now nerd? Haha whats up douche bag, it's Tanner from Highschool. Remember me? Me and the guys used to give you a hard time in school. Sorry you were just an easy target lol. I can see not much has changed. Remember Sarah the girl you had a crush on? Yeah we're married now. I make over 200k a year and drive a mustang GT. I guess some things never change huh loser? Nice catching up lol. Pathetic..
almonte550: @MrJeff_ great,
pedrovictortech: @miths aigth you got me there
Mariosavitch: lol
pedrovictortech: aight*
KruptWorld: lol is that a copy pasta?
11plus4thinking: @T3chHS real original salmon15Dank
SHAVEYY_: monkaS tanner
yevheniiushtyk: do it in haskell
miths: Tanner is back monakS
SHAVEYY_: So you're going by "georgehotz" now nerd? Haha whats up douche bag, it's Tanner from Highschool. Remember me? Me and the guys used to give you a hard time in school. Sorry you were just an easy target lol. I can see not much has changed. Remember Sarah the girl you had a crush on? Yeah we're married now. I make over 200k a year and drive a mustang GT. I guess some things never change huh loser? Nice catching up lol. Pathetic..
IndoPridePinoy: when can i download corona cure?
valibuu: why cant I write anything
T3chHS: The most classic copypasta
theonlymonkas: LUL
valibuu: What is he trying to do ?
11plus4thinking: chat spamming a dead beaten copy pasta salmon15Dank
slimpimp007: I can't picture a grown ass man named Tanner
TsarSec: LUL
kokadoo: R u infecting corona with a virus?
theonlymonkas: my name is tanner in 54
Br4nnon: he's trying to hack into the mainframe sodaVeg
33333333333333: woie
Mariosavitch: your computer will get corona if not careful
zak_krack: @valibuu He's got a data source which is in G, C, T, and A form, and he's translating it into the 26 proteins that DNA can form. I think.
OnlyB1ade: tanner is literally tanned
TsarSec: so whats the rna sequence for NOP?
esence: HERE WE GO BOIS
raondev: oh Boy what ha Idiot with spamming this shitty text
Keijo: Rest in piece Billy
Bagofpotatoes: jesus, stop filling the chat with highlighted copy/paste shite.
Jehhred: Is Data Science to Programming the equivalent of Geology to Science???
KruptWorld: hahah @kokadoo . i wanna know what hes working towards too!
SHAVEYY_: shutup I like myhighlight mesages
TrippinFlare: TSV WutFace TSV WutFace
abedbawsxx: are you trying to print hello world? let me help you
yevheniiushtyk: i can't use editor if it doesn't highlight whitespaces, i guess just my OCD, anyone does the same? lmao
Mariosavitch: dklsvhefwhfi23ifef
Bagofpotatoes: @zak_krack what can be achieved after mapping it onto those proteins?
SHAVEYY_: your a geohot fan? name every Continent
1ntegral_: @Jehhred Data science to Computer science you mean
zombiedigital: nopcauenapo undsacuoneapcubeaupi
TrippinFlare: python 2.7????????????????
raondev: @shaveyy_ shut up
theonlymonkas: LUL
KruptWorld: just hearing him type gives me a boner
SpecialAgentSkye: My boss thinks fixing bugs is deleting the line of code with "bug()" in it :) :gun:
Cornflays: @georgehotz are u calling this exploit coronara1n LUL
VoidSpyke_: :retab
11plus4thinking: @TrippinFlare does it matter???
SHAVEYY_: :( im running out of channel points
pistolpetepcp: @1ntegral_ zsh is more like zzzzzzzsh
zak_krack: @Bagofpotatoes easier protein diffing for a start
miths: @SpecialAgentSkye LUL
cybergenik: No Data Science is to Programming what Theoretical physics is to science. Your not building anything, but your extracting extremely valuable information using complicated algorithms...
Juankinator: pythLOLn
JustAsGoodJo: see differences in which codons are coding for which proteins
Jehhred: @1ntegral_ Yeah pretty much
zak_krack: G, C, T and A are hard to look at. Protein strings have more letters and are much shorter and easier
Toastie1: So am i the only one that's lost here
PiroFloydian: rip
parktype: Why using a mac?
IndoPridePinoy: wrap it bois., no coronavirus cure
dyslexicgruffalo: vi, convert spaces to tab?
TrippinFlare: COVID-19 JIRA ticket
11plus4thinking: @cybergenik please learn to use the correct your FailFish
JustAsGoodJo: see which bps are conserved across strain
miths: @parktype Steve Jobs was his grandfather
cybergenik: sorry you're
Bagofpotatoes: @zak_krack cool... so "diffing" the protein means comparing it against similar virii or wha?
TrippinFlare: @11plus4thinking isn't 2.7 deprecated?
bichid69: pppppppppppppppppppppp
parktype: ahh makes sense @miths
Riqour: @cybergenik don't apologize FailFish
ackxhpaez: My company actually opened a COVID Jira project
kubaaa6: @Loutlot are you an engineer?
cybergenik: wait @11plus4thinking LOL, a fellow reckful fan
couso_99: @Toastie1 I dont have a clue either :/
KruptWorld: im so happy this chat is actually chattable
abedbawsxx: @Riqour don't feed the trolls FailFish
yevheniiushtyk: does he have some prior skills in bio engineering? how does he do this shit wtf
11plus4thinking: @cybergenik why am i a reckful fan?
dj_vicio: slash to terminate maybe
bob_babyelephant: yo i love your shit
kubaaa6: kubaaa6 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
dj_vicio: escap
lemonboxed: every company is doing a covid project right now
cybergenik: 11 4
Riqour: @abedbawsxx LuL
kubaaa6: Want to watch your old vods pleae dont delete :)
bob_babyelephant: lololol
TrippinFlare: @yevheniiushtyk he's a bioinformatics dropout
JustAsGoodJo: LUL
KruptWorld: @yevheniiushtyk right!?!?! im tryn to get it too
11plus4thinking: @cybergenik ok so? doesnt mean im a fan
almonte550: Because they do bad stuff
lgtst_: extra crap
lgtst_: topping
ahahahaitslit: what the hell is he tryna do
JustAsGoodJo: you should put those protiens into pymol and see protein-protein interactions
dontusethiscode: doesn't look like a bad protein to me xD
samu79rai: ect.....
bob_babyelephant: also you use tmux and vim right
cybergenik: @11plus4thinking do you just like the meme?
Loutlot: @kubaaa6 I do python but mostly for fun
FoxMcWeezer: Ramirez! Cure me that Covid-19 now!
11plus4thinking: @Loutlot what does "fun" include LUL
miths: Im a java developer, help me chat PepeHands
bsuis: @kubaaa6 they're on yt
pistolpetepcp: i can solve coronus, give me btc
logi6000: just ran download sequesnces
toasty_jk2: because it is FASTA: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FASTA_format
KruptWorld: i dunno @ahahahaitslit i think its finding the protein that can kill the corona
yevheniiushtyk: using arrow keys on hhkb is so fucking annoying
logi6000: can confirm it works on arch
samu79rai: faster george faster
kubaaa6: @Loutlot ok was wondering why staff was watching unless they knew programming :p
TrippinFlare: protein.is_bad()
tehEGO: Did corona possibly come from a snake, and now using python to solve it.. is that like two snakes eating each other
Tymski_: Every time I code in python I get missing :
miths: @yevheniiushtyk you get used to it really fast imo
JustAsGoodJo: maybe codons don't align with the total number of bp?
KruptWorld: @georgehotz do you ever listen to music when you code?
OLEM13: what is he doing?
Lana_Lux: @JustAsGoodJo can you explain what he's doing? lol
dunehazard: chill mac miller
fa_k: @KruptWorld he just did yesterday
vaskogomez87: jesus i cant even see
knrbg: Hello from Bulgaria
bufferovrflw: -STOP UAA, UGA, UAG STOP UAA, UGA, UAG
bufferovrflw: you added more whitespace, lol
toasty_jk2: also i noticed that some genome samples have trailing adenine
dontusethiscode: love the font size
hellashotsx: What is he even doing?
TrippinFlare: "diffing the protein"
logi6000: I'm back
yevheniiushtyk: @miths aight, gotta practice ig
limpid_kzonix: https://community.datarobot.com/t5/research-center/join-the-fight-against-covid-19-with-datarobot/td-p/2282
Juankinator: corona = null Done Kappa
yevheniiushtyk: @miths u got hhkb asw?
ahahahaitslit: does anyone have a spare magnifying glass?
dj_vicio: another aderall shot
miths: @yevheniiushtyk hell yeah brother
Mariosavitch: chicken tendies?
zak_krack: A 4K monitor really helps watching this stream
zargy: Have ice cream for dinner
yevheniiushtyk: @miths nice mac/win?
ancientwoodland: he's uploading corona into the mainframe
Lana_Lux: sounds like my dinners
KruptWorld: @hellashotsx he just made a library for helping find the protien that kills corona?? ahha i have no clue
icanthitthose: what does engineering the coronavirus mean?
parktype: What kind of fuckery is this?
limpid_kzonix: @juankinator lol
AresRai: hes making the corona sequence and then will see how it goes from there, protein folding will be difficult x)
BesterGester: @Lana_Lux He is creating a tool to check the differences between viruses
zak_krack: Also remember to go full screen with F11 and fold down your left side bar
Punkfx: What is his strategy here for reverse engineering Covid. That doesn’t even make sense
samthedogg: im back, have i missed much?
Lana_Lux: @BesterGester ah, cool. thanks
JustAsGoodJo: @Lana_Lux i'm working on understanding LUL. from what i gather, he's looking at fasta codes (which are sequences of dna) across multiple coronavirus strains potentially to compare them. he then translated those sequences into proteins to compare them
Tomishima: What is his strategy here for reverse engineering Covid. That doesn’t even make sense
samu79rai: George do you believe in aliens
miths: @yevheniiushtyk mbp 2015, planning on buying the new 14'' mbp though. hbu?
almonte550: @Punkfx we are just learning stuff
fa_k: mactoodlers stop
zak_krack: I can explain what he's doing: he's currently cooking rice.
Ghost_001: @Tomishima Hack the world
OnlyB1ade: KappaHD KappaHD
dj_vicio: cereal
dontusethiscode: i. might get corona from this font size tbh
Nussinov: Tomishima it;s clickbait dumbass
DecayingSkullz: We need a Geohot cooking stream
fukurowlz: hacking the rice
pjayys77: hack the planet, cmon now
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz 2018 13" mpb, how long have you got the hhkb for?
icanthitthose: how do you get the corona sequence from a computer a program
OnlyB1ade: PokGardevoir
knrbg: Hello
OLEM13: An intereactive view of the virus?
Tomishima: He is out of his safe zone boys
JustAsGoodJo: @Lana_Lux but mrna sequences are pretty messy with regions that are untranslated or not coded into protein (ie functional bits) so he's cleaning them up
knrbg: How are you
phrixus_bro: hi
brownyyyylocks: whats in the oven?
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz which one do you have?
VGBurnzy: new macbook air, that's all
OnlyB1ade: hack the rice
TrippinFlare: new macbook air launched
dj_vicio: get a Lenovo Thinkpad
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: "CHEAP" LUL
dj_vicio: great for research
VGBurnzy: 1.1ghz.... what year is it?
1shortking: i3 for $1000 PepeLaugh
brownyyyylocks: rose gold finish
Mariosavitch: lol
pistolpetepcp: LOL
stole_yo_eip: lmfao
parse: LUL
dontusethiscode: if you were poor
Sky_Light_37: LUL
dontusethiscode: kek
Mariosavitch: unless your poor.. $1000
djcows: Just get a pro
anon_v28: $1000 dual core lol
yevheniiushtyk: gotta use the repair program to fix the sticky keys, drives me mad
BesterGester: @VGBurnzy That's base clock, not boost
djcows: i got the 16, super solid
miths: thinkpad x230 for the poor
logi6000: 1300k for a laptop=poor?
limpid_kzonix: probably somebody will be interested in thisLook what I shared: COVID-19 Open Research Dataset Challenge (CORD-19) | Kaggle @MIUI| https://www.kaggle.com/allen-institute-for-ai/CORD-19-research-challenge/tasks
VGBurnzy: """pro"""
pistolpetepcp: Gotta pay the apple tax
Sky_Light_37: pls donate guys, he is poor
Juankinator: who needs ram anyway just close chrome tabs
Winnepooh_: extra 8gb of ram from Apple, $400
Lana_Lux: @JustAsGoodJo interesting. and thanks. once they're cleaned up or compared, what can you do wit that info
Program: Good evening, everyone.
SpecialAgentSkye: @VGBurnzy Missing 8 quotation marks buddy
Tomishima: @Sky_Light_37 lol
bob_babyelephant: lag
dj_vicio: cant do shit with 8GB of RAM. only open 2 tabs in chrome.
yevheniiushtyk: i got 8gb mpb pro and i kinda regret it lmao
VGBurnzy: @SpecialAgentSkye sorry
DBJNR876: yes i concur
almonte550: Are we going to predict what sars-3 gonna look like?
dabdabay: ne vaxta stream bashlayib bu oglan
bichid69: What happenned to your razer blade?
Nussinov: You're thinking of polypeptide
Tomishima: he just streams for fun and the FBI and CIA
JustAsGoodJo: polyprotein is functional protein that is chopped into bits by an enzyme
Nussinov: proteins are made of peptides
alexandru_cristiean: @georgehotz getting that sweet Google job or hacking my way to freedom?
AresRai: shape probably
dontusethiscode: Is this guy like a budget christopher olah? I
VGBurnzy: @alexandru_cristiean who would want to work for good LUL
imsuperficial: let's just discover where the coronavirus lives in latent space
Juankinator: cant we just nuke the coronavirus?
PiroFloydian: Keep reading you were almost there
QuantumDota: Memes
Hello_im_nix: !uptime
zak_krack: Proteins are 3d
yevheniiushtyk: work on temple os after hacking corona?
bichid69: What happened to your razer blade?
kevin21071: you ever took BCAA?
Nussinov: @georgehotz typically a protein a more biologically 'complete' unit, whereas peptide typically refers to much shorter, sometimes truncated proteins
Loutlot: Peptones are material prolines made of
Hello_im_nix: is that a HHKB? Sounds like one
dj_vicio: BCAA == chaim aminoacids
AresRai: @dontusethiscode budget ? :o google this guy
dj_vicio: chain*
kevin21071: Branch chain amino acids
Tomishima: pyhton > ruby
JustAsGoodJo: @Lana_Lux that's what i'm interested in seeing! you can look at protein interactions. once a virus is inserted into the cell membrane, it must replicate and make more of itself (more protein) so the goal is to disrupt that machinery
SpecialAgentSkye: We are developing an anti virus that we deploy with OTA update to all humans that can detect corona PogChamp Kappa
dontusethiscode: @AresRai google olah lol
fukurowlz: recently the minister of health of my country says "maybe this virus turn into a good person, in that case it will be another case" to avoid implement a quarantine
yevheniiushtyk: @Hello_im_nix yeah he's know to use hhkb
DecayingSkullz: @Hello_im_nix yes it is
JdPaulBlart: did you see the stanford paper on your speed detection challenge @georgehotz
ancientwoodland: critical firmware update, recommend immediate install
zak_krack: you can also download the 3d folded shape of coronavirus instead of just the protein sequence
peacedivision: we need to clone @georgehotz a few thousands like him maybe 1 would hack the ps4
Loutlot: Polypeptides are not act like Proteins unless they are folded correctly and functional
vaskogomez87: ah yes
Mariosavitch: jkerhgiu3wijefhwdf
logi6000: @peacedivision but that clone will get sued
dj_vicio: this guys' a robot
peacedivision: @logi6000 he wouldn't you can do it anonyomous
yevheniiushtyk: @dj_vicio just a big nerd
1ntegral_: yeah probably faster with dictionnaries
logi6000: should robots have rights?
pz3300: What happened with that case? Did it get dropped?
theonlymonkas: yes
JustAsGoodJo: i think you want to see the three dimensional structure of these proteins, which is a structural biology battle.
Nussinov: Loutlot this is not true. There are non-functional 'proteins' and functional 'peptides', this distinction is more or less meaningless, like most categorizations in biology
SpecialAgentSkye: Should rights have robots?
nitcat: nitcat subscribed at Tier 1.
bichid69: What happened to your razer blade?
parktype: What is this?
logi6000: @specialagentskye shiit idk
theonlymonkas: LUL
SpecialAgentSkye: idk shit @logi6000 /shrug
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/corona
yevheniiushtyk: oh fuck imma start that
Darvein21: !uptime
Tomishima: public repro in 2020 Kappa
fa_k: Ah Yes my penistosida is also foldable, may i please
ahahahaitslit: let's kill this virus boys
pz3300: Imagine if robots starting raping people
nitcat: np
zak_krack: I think you can download the 3d structure raw data at https://www.rcsb.org/structure/6lu7
11plus4thinking: salmon15Dank if (Coronavirus = true)  else
mashafique: How much bio do you know Georege
mashafique: George*
megaman0711: hi I'm new, can anyone give me a tldr of what he's trying to do? thanks
Lizardan: @megaman0711 title
Mariosavitch: but a bitch aint 1
bufferovrflw: @11plus4thinking bro, you just assigned true to Coronavirus
TheRedLineUK: can I hear topre switches??
Nussinov: zak_krack that ramachandran outlier score Kreygasm
kaiokenx90: hey george i just farted wanna reverse engineer that?
zak_krack: I got 99 sequences but a twitch ain't one
SpecialAgentSkye: Building an anti virus competetor for Avast Free Anti cheat that can beat corona @megaman0711 Kappa
pz3300: Cherry brown are best
peacedivision: @megaman0711 he's hacking the coronavirus, this would lead to a ps4 exploit
Mariosavitch: i got 99 sequences but a cure isnt one
megaman0711: ahaha
fukurowlz: @mashafique let him study two days and that will be enough
11plus4thinking: @bufferovrflw bro it was obviously a joke
Amaz1ngLALALA: Hi guys, I'm Russian from the future, you should stop him immediately, no joke
TheLogg: LOL^^^
bufferovrflw: @11plus4thinking bro...
SpecialAgentSkye: Hi russian from the future. Im adopted
pz3300: In soviet russia virus cures you!
bichid69: use tensorflow to find a cure bro
11plus4thinking: @bufferovrflw bro meet me @ twitchcon
yevheniiushtyk: oi guys, you got any tips on how to get into reverse engineering, and binary stuff, i wanna broaden my skillz a lil
peacedivision: he is making the ultimate virus that would wipe the world in seconds and he will be immunite to it
mashafique: @fukurowlz enough for what?
TrippinFlare: what's cleaving?
bufferovrflw: @11plus4thinking bro we're gonna have a good time at twitchcon bro
TrippinFlare: cleaving - Proteolysis is the breakdown of proteins into smaller polypeptides or amino acids.
bichid69: @yevheniiushtyk it's jus 1 0 bro
yevheniiushtyk: history 🤔
SpecialAgentSkye: Just make an AI that guesses them PogChamp
Tomishima: is do not trust this dna sequence
yevheniiushtyk: @bichid69 wot
Mariosavitch: what do you wnat
TrippinFlare: google
11plus4thinking: @bufferovrflw bro im gonna bash ur head in bro squadR
bufferovrflw: @11plus4thinking bro, don't
Tomishima: remember the Xerox copy machine software bug
Nussinov: Try researching the protease from a previous coronavirus. the chemical mechanism of the cleavage should be well understood at this point
logi6000: it started with new something
zak_krack: cleaving is chopping a protein sequence into pieces
logi6000: I have 1k channel points
SpecialAgentSkye: Wasnt it the google docs sheet you had ?
SpecialAgentSkye: @georgehotz
bufferovrflw: George, I believe it was FASTA
11plus4thinking: @bufferovrflw ok :)
fukurowlz: @mashafique to lear a lot of bio
bufferovrflw: FASTA
pz3300: Apparently Corona is making people play poker there was 300k players on stars tonight
Nussinov: @georgehotz https://www.uniprot.org/uniprot/Q9BYF1#interaction here's a great site if you haven't been here yet
fukurowlz: learn*
yevheniiushtyk: respect for people that study this shit wtf
cold_x: the chinese gov will be knocking on his door at no time
ancientwoodland: get u dont have that red- bet u dont have that green - bet u dont have the biggest ball the wold has seen!
mrflurriesxvx: sorry i cant hear what youre saying
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz It's FASTA, iirc
williamjennings1: what is he even doing lmao
pistolpetepcp: He's looking for genomes that were cleaved
yevheniiushtyk: maybe it
brittonx2: I thought the furin did the cleaving...
georgecruece: how is the progress everyone
logi6000: the one with the map of where it came from
Lana_Lux: @JustAsGoodJo ah cool! thanks for the insight :)
mrflurriesxvx: i cant hear youuuuuuu
SpecialAgentSkye: @georgehotz Wasnt it the google sheets doc you had open?
brittonx2: the furin is on the host side
YoungGuns_: just got here, what are we doing??
MrEuds: Hey @Lana_Lux :D
yevheniiushtyk: @YoungGuns_ hacking corona
pistolpetepcp: Wait waht is a furin
freshsoclean: i couldve copy and pasted all the work you did in 20 hours in 1 min
georgecruece: has he found the key
SpecialAgentSkye: @YoungGuns_ Hacking burgerking to eliminate corona
fukurowlz: hacking god
Juankinator: @YoungGuns_ 3d printing corona beer
logi6000: is it the one with the map of where it came from
JustAsGoodJo: @Lana_Lux of course :)
mrflurriesxvx: imagine having covid 19 and aids at the same time
georgecruece: @justasgoodjo can i kiss u
yevheniiushtyk: its 2 am already fuck
YoungGuns_: chat so helpful :)
Juankinator: LUL
edu4594: he's linking the corona beer with covid-19
JustAsGoodJo: @georgecruece lanaluHuh LUL
JMSWRNR: monkaS
mashafique: @fukurowlz I wouldn't say you can deeply learn a lot of bio in two days. Probably just cram enough info to be able to work with it
mrflurriesxvx: lol i can learn everything in a day
KruptWorld: watching geohot with liquid drumnbass is magical
Lana_Lux: @MrEuds hey! :)
dj_vicio: rice overcooked
CompestLive: hi
edu4594: everyone in this chat has an iq of 240, damn
m4xh3ra: !uptime
bananacat98: bananacat98 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
zak_krack: @edu4594 we're nearly all faking
yevheniiushtyk: i wonder if he talks to himself off-stream PRChase
localcanofdutchgold: @zak_krack don't tell him 5Head
mrflurriesxvx: sexy beast
pistolpetepcp: To be honest, you need a high iq to even watch this
dj_vicio: @yevheniiushtyk HE IS talking to himself during the stream all the time
11plus4thinking: @yevheniiushtyk he def does
fukurowlz: @mashafique if u want to work with a specific topic of bio, i think that two days will be enough
bananacat98: you can do it!!!!
alycia: LuvHearts
SpecialAgentSkye: @yevheniiushtyk I think all developers do. I explain things out loud to myself so i understand them better
georgecruece: i can totally follow him, dont u? ArgieB8
yevheniiushtyk: nothing wrong with that i do too while i code so was just wondering haha
dj_vicio: yes, we all do
vaskogomez87: dlandlasndnsdd "ENTER"
mashafique: @fukurowlz Two days is enough to develop a working knowledge but I don't think that knowledge will last if you don't review it. It's not a one and done thing.
saintmthw: @yevheniiushtyk auditory learner?
11plus4thinking: 11 🤔
SpecialAgentSkye: me :) I skipped 11 :)
Mariosavitch: git commit -am 'Skip 11'
dj_vicio: but geohotz even yells and fights at himself
Mariosavitch: git blame china
zak_krack: this protein doesn't go up to 11
Winnepooh_: I usually just repeat "how can I be so stupid?" when I code, not sure if it helps
georgecruece: i has eaten 11
Amaz1ngLALALA: 11 monkaS
AresRai: 4 🤔
saintmthw: the coldlight oracle
Nussinov: @georgehotz check to see if some of the proteins are encoded on the other strand of dna
parktype: 11 Pepehands
yevheniiushtyk: 🤔 WHO
logi6000: is it the site with the timeline and where the virus came from
StriderKeni: StriderKeni subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months! Cheers from Chile! evo19Chile
TrippinFlare: grep "11"
Mariosavitch: well 7, 8, 9 so maybe 7 did
fukurowlz: @mashafique yeah, sure, but i mean that is a good time to start with it
Juankinator: bush did coronavirus
ad5k: mysterysQmark mysterysQmark mysterysQmark
fukurowlz: @StriderKeni saludos, de chile tambien <3
georgecruece: damn, he is just learning biology on google :( :( :(
Mariosavitch: can you look at the commit history of the virus
edu4594: obama did corona
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
logi6000: is it the site with the Timeline and where the Corona came from?
SpecialAgentSkye: @Mariosavitch but 5 sexed 7, so maybe 5 was in on it too?
fa_k: geohot did bioinformatics did he?
zak_krack: @georgecruece you can learn a lot from google / stackoverflow, even at the top levels
pomprocks: solving biology is like solving artificial intelligence. but harder
fa_k: nice rarted take brother
zak_krack: engine roar
KruptWorld: @pomprocks what is he solving in biology exactly?
georgecruece: @zak_krack but he hasn't written a line of code for half an hour :( :( :(
ad5k: Weren’t a lot of contributors to bioinformatics CS people who learned some basic bio
mashafique: @fukurowlz That's true. It's a good enough time to get a working knowledge to build upon.
yevheniiushtyk: so y'all think coronavirus (sars ig) could be bio engineered in a lab, or is actually from people eating bats?
logi6000: is it the site with the map of where corona cane from
Nussinov: @georgehotz wrong exonuclease is not related to exon. exo refers to the directionality of the mechanism of degradation of the enzyme
dj_vicio: go check the rice before you burn the house
dj_vicio: see? he talks to himself all the time
dj_vicio: never talks to the streamers
ninjadidio: :D
toasty_jk2: something with the ending "-ase" is an enzyme (a protei with a function)
fukurowlz: streamers?
fukurowlz: what
SpecialAgentSkye: We are streamers PogChamp
OnlyB1ade: hmm
fukurowlz: i didn't know
zak_krack: we're streamees
shieeeeeeeeet: we are streaming our thoughts in chat
fukurowlz: lol
norlagg: Pepega
aramaki2345: it looks interesting but i dont what the f im looking at
JustAsGoodJo: exon is just part of a gene that is in mature mRNA
fukurowlz: here comes the twitch money
yevheniiushtyk: 2 am timezone gang rise up
Juankinator: we do have twitch accounts so technically we are streamers
vaskogomez87: what language is this guys?
cold_x: english
localcanofdutchgold: didn't wash hands DansGame
fukurowlz: @vaskogomez87 python
allpurposebucket: better be 20 seconds of washing hands!
Relatate: python
ahahahaitslit: he does literally everything in python
pistolpetepcp: YOu have along way to go buddy
SpecialAgentSkye: We are streaming out combined brainpower to geo 5Head
georgecruece: how long has he stop writing codes
dj_vicio: hands washed?
vaskogomez87: @fukurowlz ty
ad5k: That was like 10 seconds
bufferovrflw: WASH HANDS GEORGE
logi6000: it is the site with the map of where corona is
bufferovrflw: PLS WASH HANDS
gianniskokos: !uptime
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk One study that made a supposition that it was released from the Wuhan P4 Virology laboratory, the study was quickly removed afterwards for being veryweak scientifically. Not much else so far, people seem to be widely in favor of the zoonosis theory
Usisuvach0: https://chemrxiv.org/articles/Analysis_of_Whole_Genome_Sequences_and_Homology_Modelling_of_a_3C_Like_Peptidase_and_a_Non-Structural_Protein_of_the_Novel_Coronavirus_COVID-19_Shows_Protein_Ligand_Interaction_with_an_Aza-Peptide_and_a_Noncovalent_Lead_Inhibitor_with_Possi/11846943/5?file=21777303
JustAsGoodJo: introns and exons are in nascent pre mRNAs, exons are in mature mRNA
ninjadidio: @JustAsGoodJo oh intresting
bufferovrflw: Let's make him wash hands
fukurowlz: @vaskogomez87 he always code on python, i think
logi6000: is it the site with the map of where corona came from
Mariosavitch: a different genome sequence
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk 2AM timezone too btw
Usisuvach0: random finding @georgehotz
yevheniiushtyk: @thejuror8 yeah, i think about this a lot though
Mariosavitch: its a virus
Juankinator: i cant understand anything can you please play fortnite
11plus4thinking: 2 am gang BasedGod
fukurowlz: @StriderKeni nunca pense encontrar a otro chileno por acá xd
yevheniiushtyk: @thejuror8 how come it appeared just now
logi6000: @juankinator eww
zak_krack: r-i-c-e
pistolpetepcp: wow line numbers in a text doc???
Nussinov: dont link preprints maybe 4Head
zak_krack: good to get carbs with all this protein
yevheniiushtyk: i'm sure people in china have been eating snakes and bats for a while now
ahahahaitslit: how long do u guys think this lockdown is gonna last lol
ad5k: Hope u got some mirin
dj_vicio: @Juankinator that's why you dont understand; because you're frying ur brain with that damned game
logi6000: @dj_vicio exactly
playfiendss: what is Lord Hotz exactly trying to do?
fukurowlz: @ahahahaitslit almost 3/4 of the year
11plus4thinking: @yevheniiushtyk oh, they def have, they find eat all kinds of exotic animals over there
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk It's hard to know anyways. If it was intentionally released which is a crazy theory, then at least one unaligned government would have made a declaration, so it is reasonable to exclude this possibility. Then it could be accidental, but there is very little fact to support this theory as well
SpecialAgentSkye: Fotnite in 2020 LUL
imsuperficial: @playfiendss coronavirus
AresRai: peepoSad want mroe pictures
ahahahaitslit: probably
fukurowlz: @playfiendss understanding how coronavirus work
Juankinator: @dj_vicio r/wooosh
georgecruece: plz writing god damn codes :( :( :(
Brunovercelli: Yeaah man, the smartest mind in the world is streaming. I miss that shit
yevheniiushtyk: @thejuror8 doesn't have to be intentionally, could have been some sort of an accident
ackxhpaez: He’s trying to reverse engineer the coranavirus, since it was an engineered bioweapon
dj_vicio: @Juankinator speak English to me, not that gamer damned language
georgecruece: stop randomly searching online plz
Amaz1ngLALALA: Well, he defeated Corona?
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk Yeah second part of my message
11plus4thinking: @ackxhpaez not how that works
georgecruece: just write the god damn codes
Mariosavitch: no pepper or salt?
yevheniiushtyk: @thejuror8 i'm from czech republic, and there's this bio engineering lady which also thinks that this was an potentionally bio engineered virus
fukurowlz: @georgecruece lol
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Wash your hands before you eat the rice goddamit ]
zak_krack: george let the man do it his way LUL
dj_vicio: no hands washed before eating
11plus4thinking: plain rice DansGame ? plain rice DansGame ? plain rice DansGame ? plain rice DansGame ?
dj_vicio: ew
thejuror8: @georgecruece Bro coding is 90% Googling
Mariosavitch: damn thats some depression era cooking
SpecialAgentSkye: Plain rice Kreygasm
Nussinov: ackxhpaez it was shown that it is very very unlikely it was an engineered bioweapon. https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/the-new-coronavirus-was-not-genetically-engineered-study-shows#Ending-the-rumors-about-SARS-CoV-2-
DecayingSkullz: soy sauce
yevheniiushtyk: @thejuror8 ah mb didnt finish reading lmao
dj_vicio: 10% copy/pasta
thejuror8: @yevheniiushtyk I do the same lmao
mescal33t: 🍚
brittonx2: http://www.virology.ws/2020/02/13/furin-cleavage-site-in-the-sars-cov-2-coronavirus-glycoprotein
dj_vicio: where's the protein lol
logi6000: @juankinator sorry to be excluding but I'm not sure you exactly fit in with this channel. go watch some gamer
zak_krack: i can't believe this guy hasn't visited stackoverflow, how does he get anything done?
DecayingSkullz: do you have any soylent
Mariosavitch: does it have a spike protein?
JefeBezos: Not even hot sauce?
dj_vicio: yea @Juankinator with all due respect GTFO
ackxhpaez: CCP propaganda!
11plus4thinking: @thejuror8 nah i would argue coding is 10% googling and 90% the person thinking of what questions to ask
SpecialAgentSkye: @dj_vicio 5% copy pasta. 2% cleanup. 3% praying it works.
georgecruece: he only eats rice? no other things?
Juankinator: @logi6000 its alright im joking
Nussinov: @georgehotz first hyperlink in this document is the nature article
fukurowlz: @zak_krack almost 10 years coding with python
logi6000: @zak_krack they haven't done this type of advanced shit yet
nic0latesla: you are cute
georgecruece: this man is weird HolidayCookie HolidayCookie
dj_vicio: @SpecialAgentSkye gotta be some % for "talking to yourself"
ited01: a
Mariosavitch: no
SpecialAgentSkye: Thats an async task @dj_vicio . It never stops. 100% talking to self LUL
Crayonsss: i assume u do this for fun? imagine what they pay people that work with this!
thejuror8: @georgehotz Nature would absolutely publish it if the article was of quality
bob_babyelephant: good stuff geo
JustAsGoodJo: i mean, nature might if it had 100 pages of supplemental
11plus4thinking: how can you enjoy plain rice DansGame
Nussinov: @georgehotz this is true, but not all evidence can be strong by nature of the situation
11plus4thinking: explain DansGame
zwisch: do you put anything in your rice?
ahahahaitslit: salt
dj_vicio: how can he eat with no water or chicken, veggies, etc.
zak_krack: yes a fork
KruptWorld: how do you determine if its lab created or not?
thejuror8: @georgehotz A previous paper supporting the theory was removed because the methodology was very weak
Tidusuper91: I'd put a bit of salmon.
SpecialAgentSkye: @zwisch A spoon Kappa
zak_krack: or a spoon
KruptWorld: is there like a signiture?
georgecruece: plz add something to.rice
dj_vicio: damn that bite hahahaha
zak_krack: LUL
bob_babyelephant: I like coding
yevheniiushtyk: well good to know he doesn't eat only takeout food lmao
toasty_jk2: just do a BLAST search and you will see it is 91% identical to the virus found in bats 2013
peter35_: news: lab origin conspiracy DEBUNKED
boneitis: !uptime
Usisuvach0: @KruptWorld it's visible if it's injected
JefeBezos: You’re not meant to eat the spoon too
fukurowlz: THE ASMR
thejuror8: @KruptWorld Sequencing and statistics, comparisons with existing specimens studied in said laboratories. It's easier than you think
dj_vicio: @peter35_ sauce?
SpecialAgentSkye: @JefeBezos Says who?
zak_krack: no sauce, it's plain rice
georgecruece: do u have a gf
KruptWorld: @georgehotz how does someone determine a lab created virus or not?
zak_krack: Kappa
Amaz1ngLALALA: WutFace
skieth028: hello there what ya doing?
peter35_: dj_vicio im saying how that's how they would blindly report on that paper george just had up
vaskogomez87: ah yes yes
11plus4thinking: @toasty_jk2 its really scary how viruses can mutate from animals to humans
zak_krack: i've got work tomorrow but I'm up watching this stream :(
logi6000: @zak_krack damn work
kevin99gh: is he trying jailbreak the corona wtf is this sourciYOUNGB
SpecialAgentSkye: @zak_krack Same. 3 hours till work FeelsGoodMan 🔫
KruptWorld: damn folding@home doesnt do corona yet
yevheniiushtyk: hm so sars had the potential to be even worse than coronavirus, but somehow it got stopped?
georgecruece: do u have biological background
thejuror8: @georgecruece He does not LUL that's going to be the main issue
Usisuvach0: @11plus4thinking it's also scary how bats get infected by it and mutates inside of them, but it does not harm the bats at all
vaskogomez87: @zak_krack me 2. 1:30am here
zak_krack: @SpecialAgentSkye I kinda feel I might learn more here than at work
Nussinov: @georgehotz one key insight is that COVID19 is derived from no coronaviruses known to be pathogenic, and the analyses show the pathogenic mutations occured within humans. it is very hard to believe that researchers that would "design" this virus would use a non pathogenic template and then PREDICT the downstream mutations to optimize for pathogenicity.
AresRai: @yevheniiushtyk more like sars exchanged mortality stats for reproductive stats
fizzword: hey
Juankinator: @georgecruece dont think so, hes learning as he goes i think
JustAsGoodJo: might have a different name
thejuror8: @Nussinov Damn I did not know that, that's spicy as fuck
11plus4thinking: @Usisuvach0 yep exactly, this is just the beginning
peter35_: i hate the word debunked
SpecialAgentSkye: @zak_krack I for sure will. Im at home, working on some ai stuff for ibm, that i cannot access because its not remotely accessable. I dont know what im paid for LUL
KruptWorld: @georgehotz are you working on setting up that church to hack nature at all or just been busy with other stuff?
zak_krack: yep @Juankinator . I love that, more people need to be able to explore new areas on the fly
georgecruece: he must be genius
bonzer66: @thejuror8 what is he writing? I just joined in like 10 mins ago
Usisuvach0: and bats are carrying god knows how much viruses in them
Nussinov: @thejuror8 the cutting edge is spicy as fuck, you should read more PogChamp
Juankinator: @zak_krack yep, google makes that easier too
11plus4thinking: @SpecialAgentSkye free money TriHard
Usisuvach0: all of the COV viruses are from bats
Usisuvach0: MERS, SARS, and this one
thejuror8: @bonzer66 Just scrambling around with the genetic code of Coronavirus, he's learning
Nussinov: Usisuvach0 where did you hear that?
SpecialAgentSkye: @zak_krack But they wont fire me because it would take too long to get someone else into the exact project (extension for watson). So im not getting fired LUL
georgecruece: does he have the machine to cook the vaccine
Usisuvach0: hear?
SpecialAgentSkye: @11plus4thinking TriHard 7 Rise up
Usisuvach0: it's everywhere
Usisuvach0: read about it
thejuror8: @Nussinov Yeah I know nothing about genomics, I mostly read ML papers these days
dj_vicio: @SpecialAgentSkye you work for IBM?
Usisuvach0: but the infection to humans is not from bats directly
Usisuvach0: it's from intermediate host
thejuror8: @georgecruece LUL don't be crazy
Usisuvach0: MERS was from camilla
zak_krack: what is spider beer?
Usisuvach0: SARS from civets
nic0latesla: i love this guy
Nussinov: @thejuror8 ML concepts are commonly used in genomics
SpecialAgentSkye: @dj_vicio yea. Its not fun at all. As much as it might sound like a nice workplace
zak_krack: Is that a default chromium link
Usisuvach0: this one they say it's from pangolin
thejuror8: Cmon Hotz just do [:-1] like a man
Usisuvach0: but they are not sure yet
yevheniiushtyk: Coronavirus are usually pretty harmless viruses right? When our nose gets runny etc, that's all coronaviruses as far as i know? Thats why they renamed it to sars cov?
thejuror8: @Nussinov That's cool
fizzword: what is jupyter?
Usisuvach0: but the first host is bat
brownyyyylocks: i made fried rice with bokchoy jalapenos and sesame seed oil
brownyyyylocks: it was amazing
logi6000: imma have to go it's been nice talking to you guys
JustAsGoodJo: easy way to run python code vs. using the terminal @fizzword
georgecruece: it is online python editing platform
zak_krack: yep @yevheniiushtyk this is the world's first pandemic coronavirus
Nussinov: @thejuror8 in fact most of the biosciences now use ML, given the 'big data' praxis
Juankinator: @fizzword python IDE
fizzword: oh, cool. thanks
SpecialAgentSkye: @brownyyyylocks You just made me hungry. I hope your next commit fails the CI pipeline 😡
KruptWorld: @fizzword its make developing for data easier and you can run lines of code instead of having to recompile it all
bananacat98: I have no idea what is going on but his typing sure is relaxing FortBush
dj_vicio: georgehotz researches/RE Corona while drinking bath soup
georgecruece: jupyter sucks
Juankinator: @georgecruece amen to that
KruptWorld: @Juankinator damn that a nice simple way to say it haha
1ntegral_: @fizzword you both code and text in markdown format it's used a lot in Data Science
dontusethiscode: @brownyyyylocks i made fresh pasta with bat and tomato sauce
georgecruece: total messy codes after certain time
yevheniiushtyk: I'm staying careful during this pandemic, since I don't have my 30% of lungs to be permanently damaged, on other side, USA is gonna get it bad I think
Juankinator: @KruptWorld haha you did explain it better
yevheniiushtyk: *don't want
zak_krack: i want to see the diff of those two strings
SpecialAgentSkye: Bath soup drink rice while researching geohotz /RE Corono
JustAsGoodJo: might have differences in residues
Danilok100: !uptime
Nussinov: @georgecruece messy brain
dongmuya: Is what Hotz working on have anything to do with what Folding@Home is advertising? Borrowing your idle GPU/CPU?
thejuror8: @Nussinov That's very exciting. I'm kinda hoping to get an opening in Bioinformatics using my soon to be solid background in ML
pistolpetepcp: this is the glycoprotien that binds to the ACE2 receptor?
almonte550: Let's do edit distance to it
brownyyyylocks: lets hope bitbucket goes down
thejuror8: @Nussinov It's a very interesting domain for sure
zak_krack: does anyone else keep trying to copy paste things off of george's stream
KruptWorld: haha true
dontusethiscode: where is Alex @georgehotz
georgecruece: @nussinov i like codes are split into files in traditional IDE
brownyyyylocks: thats it im starting a cooking stream
thejuror8: @georgecruece If you try it you will see how practical it is with Python, it's a lot better
fizzword: @yevheniiushtyk as far as I know your lungs only get damaged if you start showing serious symptoms, which would only happen if you have a preexisting condition
georgecruece: pycharm is nice
Nussinov: @georgehotz you might want to try a multiple sequence alignment. there are web tools
thejuror8: @georgecruece Almost no reason to use something else
Maxmemix: Whats the goal here?
KruptWorld: @Maxmemix im trying to figure it out
thejuror8: @Maxmemix Having fun learning I guess
Bo0sted05: yea what are you trying to do
360Plato: https://msa.biojs.net/ check this out
SpecialAgentSkye: If its made by jetbrains, you know its prolly top tier imo
georgecruece: @thejuror8 it is just good to do small tests in jupyter
ak0ya_: to understand I guess at this point
thejuror8: Lol guys this stream is just not going to be a 24 hours DSLAM coding session, just get on with that
ak0ya_: to formulate a problem?
yevheniiushtyk: @fizzword ah okay, still it's important not to be ignorant during this pandemic, made me mad how people labeled it as "oh it's just an flu" when it started
thejuror8: @georgecruece Yeah it's just very very practical
JustAsGoodJo: yeah sequence alignment allows for miss matches like indels and gives scores
KruptWorld: i think its to find what will bind to it and destroy it
nashesvobodnoye: I would be bored to sleep... Guess thats why i'm not George Hotz
yevheniiushtyk: bruh im hungry af over here and this mad b eating all the time
yevheniiushtyk: man
georgecruece: why do americans also eat rice ArgieB8
georgecruece: it is weird
yevheniiushtyk: don't we all ove rice
yevheniiushtyk: love
Waywoah: Why wouldn't we eat rice?
leesingods: Rice = best side
brownyyyylocks: side? bruh main dish
brittonx2: http://www.virology.ws/2020/02/13/furin-cleavage-site-in-the-sars-cov-2-coronavirus-glycoprotein/
georgecruece: i thought u ate hamburgers everyday :( :( :(
dj_vicio: it's not about the tools. It's about Methodology.
SpecialAgentSkye: @yevheniiushtyk People are still saying its just a flu because they dont understand how pandemic research and statistics work. Comparisons of #cases to deaths is fundamentally wrong, but thats their argument. Its #cured vs deaths that matters. Rest is a buffer for death or cured. (cured = beat the virus as you cant "cure" a virus)
JustAsGoodJo: tools give us high dimensional data that is inherently difficult for most people to find structure within
SpecialAgentSkye: People tend to live in their own narratives. Sad really.
mlgdotca: did he cure it yet
justdoityourself: It's all about the cleavage sites... simple LUL.
Lizardan: @mlgdotca he cured his hunger :)
Vindalis: jailbreaking the coronavirus LUL
saixj: could you zoom in a tad bit for your webbrowser please
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz you ever listen to bas? think youd like him
dj_vicio: not yet. he has another rice plate with bat to go
Juankinator: coronara1n incoming
leesingods: import Cure
brownyyyylocks: viruses are like ideas. it does not go away completely because it never truly dies
leesingods: fk didnt work
JBirch10: ever thought to find a chemist/virologist to help understand what you are looking at??
georgecruece: is he reading a paper ArgieB8
skieth028: can anyone explain what is he doing? is he like trying to remake the virus? XD
gollosadstation: found anything yet?
sillybaboy: how are you gonna reverse engineer a virus just based off of sources you don't know can be trusted?
fafws321: How do you undersand those biological terms? Do you have a minor or smt???
T3chHS: Does george has biology background?
yevheniiushtyk: I love how my country (Czech Republic), has been handling this, compared to other EU countries I think we have it pretty good. They immediately started to take action, school were closed almost immediately, public gatherings, social distancing
thejuror8: @SpecialAgentSkye Cases is still very relevant if compared to the total available hospital beds, it's when cases exceed this total that death tolls skyrockets
KruptWorld: lol
SpecialAgentSkye: Yo you prolly wont see this, but i still think your rap talents BEAST @georgehotz LUL That light it up contest was sick to this day
brittonx2: http://www.virology.ws/2020/02/13/furin-cleavage-site-in-the-sars-cov-2-coronavirus-glycoprotein/
Nussinov: You don't need a biology background to be skeptical of a paper
pistolpetepcp: isolation_source = "fecal swab " LOL
georgecruece: @t3chhs yes he has doctor degree in biology
dj_vicio: he understand them because he's geohotz man! How dare you?!
360Plato: their not top minds the y just memorise
Nussinov: but you need to be willing to learn
bufferovrflw: That cough doesn't sound good
gattz_: monkaS
Mariosavitch: BEER IRUS
Ozonemaster: so here's my thought: "... BUFFERING
skieth028: PogChamp
dontusethiscode: F cough
GoldSkis: omg it's spreading
dr_set: corona cough?
publishcoffee: are you feeling hot, George?
almonte550: CORONAVIRUS
Tomishima: cool tactic
Mariosavitch: lol
gattz_: this stream got infected monkaS
thejuror8: @georgehotz Hey give us an example
georgecruece: u get corona. everybody get away now!
PeepRL: corona virus
Tomishima: woman
SpecialAgentSkye: @thejuror8 Correct, but looking solely on these numbers for a conclusion of the "deathlyness" of the virus is wrong is what im trying to say
leesingods: If you look for the Cure the virus has a defense mechanism which is why he is coughing...
PeepRL: whoops. coronga* virus
brownyyyylocks: we need AI Scientists
thejuror8: @SpecialAgentSkye That's fair
Ghost_001: HotPokket
360Plato: not systematic at all no way to derive it
aiis: Most medical professionals aren't meant to really think for themselves by design.
ahahahaitslit: as far as undergrad goes isn't the entire degree memorizing shit?
SpecialAgentSkye: Can you give an example of how you use words wrong?
KruptWorld: hahaha
peter35_: yeah their's barely any mathematics in biology
jagger_rsw: george quoting Feynman from BBC series on ducks :)
georgecruece: information theory
KruptWorld: did information theory exist back then?
theonlymonkas: nice
thejuror8: @georgehotz Hey give us an example of a scrambled interview question of yours please
vaskogomez87: @georgehotz yeah give us an example
Nussinov: @peter35_ you don't know what youre talking about LUL
Tomishima: funny but is true
DatBrownKid999: Hey george can you do my C homework for me?
brownyyyylocks: orange juice and bongo drum
theonlymonkas: richard feynman is cool
Juankinator: honestly i always saw biology as just a shit ton of stuff to memorize
Ghost_001: monkaS
Abnico: what sauce is in that rice
JBirch10: why not find a virologist who is already working on this to see if you are on to something??
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz feynman on this - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lFIYKmos3-s - "Richard Feynman - Names Don't Constitute Knowledge"
JustAsGoodJo: @peter35_ i'm a computational biologist. there's mathematics in biology lol
Tomishima: wlaking wikipedia
pistolpetepcp: Yea it's like physics, you can say you slipped on water, but you need to ask why
11plus4thinking: feynman FeelsBadMan
Skriance: what about engineers
Nussinov: you would not be hard pressed to find a "physicist" that studies biological systems
11plus4thinking: feynman come back FeelsBadMan
Voyburke: dewFeels dewFeels
360Plato: Eric Weinstein talked about this in that prestige goes to hard science fields and so do the top midns
Ghost_001: FeelsBadMan
lelqganka: ti si pedal
Ozonemaster: that prhase is thought spoken
ahahahaitslit: geo do you listen to the portal
SpecialAgentSkye: @georgehotz Can you give an example of a misused word in a question, to test someones knowledge?
raystriker98: !uptime
Lizardan: Feynman the legend
georgecruece: stop watching videos and get back to work now
KruptWorld: @georgehotz how would you know if the virus is lab created or not? is there like some signiture in the genetic code?
360Plato: Easier to build off hard rules then approximations
PiroFloydian: vid very quiet
Crypod: LUL
pedrovictortech: Yep we are listening from the speaker
thejuror8: KEKW TRUE
brownyyyylocks: yo my theory has always been geohot is feynman reincarnated
SpecialAgentSkye: @KruptWorld You need to realize he is not a biologist. Im pretty sure he couldnt tell you. He is a developer, winging biology using google, and the knowledgeable people in chat
JustAsGoodJo: i think people just like to sound smart
KruptWorld: oh thanks @SpecialAgentSkye
Nussinov: feynman wrote about his time doing biological research, some very interesting insights. they ring even more true now that google and online biological databases exist
mashafique: As someone who has a degree in Physics and Mathematics memorizing doesn't get you anywhere. If you don't understand what you're doing it doesn't matter. You can memorize all the equations and theorems you want but if you don't know how they work you're not gonna get anywhere meaningful.
360Plato: @JustAsGoodJo of course
Musashhhi: he lived a cool life
skieth028: PogChamp
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 13 months, currently on a 13 month streak! I shared the 12 months earlier today???
Lizardan: Feynman the legend
Sarkin_dota: As someone who has a degree in Physics and Mathematics memorizing doesn't get you anywhere. If you don't understand what you're doing it doesn't matter. You can memorize all the equations and theorems you want but if you don't know how they work you're not gonna get anywhere meaningful.
Voyburke: big forehead = big brain
thejuror8: Associating names to concepts is probably one of the hardest parts of getting into something new
SpecialAgentSkye: @Sarkin_dota Amen brother
Lizardan: You have to become one with the math to understand it
dj_vicio: as opposed to girls. Big boobs small brains
mashafique: @Sarkin_dota what was the purpose of copy pasting what i wrote LUL
SpecialAgentSkye: Or awomen. I dont discriminate Kappa
AresRai: literature LUL
Nussinov: proofs are criminally undertaught in america
Sarkin_dota: @mashafique I'm just doing twitch chat's job, don't judge me
Lizardan: science Kappa
mashafique: @Sarkin_dota lmao that wasn't a premade copy pasta
Sarkin_dota: @mashafique I made it one!
Mariosavitch: yes
PiroFloydian: it literally says how in the preceding phrase
asaalgk: OMEGALUL
mashafique: @Sarkin_dota I am honored
dj_vicio: written by two diff ppl
brittonx2: the spikes are the key! Read this one! http://www.virology.ws/2020/02/13/furin-cleavage-site-in-the-sars-cov-2-coronavirus-glycoprotein/
360Plato: maybe not relatively
thejuror8: @georgehotz It just means that computational analysis of proteic binding is not perfect
u1337ochka: yo @georgehotz are you going to Joe Rogan for a podcast?
tehEGO: maybe interaction is the premise that they would be in that scenario
thejuror8: @georgehotz Probably very far from that actually
dj_vicio: cant read
ahahahaitslit: can't sees hit
pistolpetepcp: does this mean that it doesn't always bind to the ace2 receptor
nozpheratu: Can't shee shit captain!
tehEGO: but when put in the scenario they do fit
mashafique: Too small to see
abhinavneelam: zoom in bro
norlagg: BeanieHipster
11plus4thinking: why?
PiroFloydian: yeah cant read
AresRai: D:
nitcat: amen
Lizardan: D:
zol0: PepeHands
ahahahaitslit: what about the portal
dj_vicio: well
tokumei64: get a bigger monitor plebs
dontusethiscode: GeoHotz VS Jordan Peterson
gclawes: upvote for the portal
dontusethiscode: best interview
vrooom_vroooooom: joe rogan just reacts to shit people say about the future
whitesaucey: dont want to be famous yet wants to be insta famous????
PiroFloydian: no the xkcd lmao
OnlyB1ade: KappaHD
PiroFloydian: this was fine
raystriker98: you're already famous enough
pistolpetepcp: what is the ACE2 receptor
dj_vicio: yell at the neighbors again
yevheniiushtyk: pop some CBD
Juankinator: joe rogan will just ask you about ai and the terminator scenario
tehEGO: maybe it would be better that papers like this should be refactored to as lamens as possible
Vindalis: george will be the first one to develop an autonomous vaccine for the coronavirus
360Plato: @dontusethiscode what would they even talk about JBP is zonked in rehab
leesingods: You could just go back to normal after the interview what would chage?
Lizardan: Rogan would be the worst podcast for someone like George. Rogan is a comedian.
AresRai: joe will ask about DMT and terminator
raystriker98: Joe Rogan is dumb af
mashafique: To me it just seems like you're just too nitpicky with words. At the end of the every field has a way of talking and if you haven't actually studied that field it doesn't make sense to expect ot understand the way that they are communicating. Also, since a lot of the stuff you loo k at is not aimed just for the average person. It's for people in the field.
Nussinov: @georgehotz I think what is being said is that - using the state of the art computational analyses, one could not reverse engineer the virus seen
PiroFloydian: this was legible the xkcd wasnt @georgehotz
KruptWorld: its maybe saying although its the current form is the most optimized for it its not the best one that can be made for interactions... like the predictive models found better ones?
THX1342: pistolpetepcp the cell's bouncer that let's covid in
Icaro_sama: @Juankinator and gorilaz, and dmt
williamjennings1: do math on stream
pistolpetepcp: @THX1342 thanks
williamjennings1: forget the corona virus
dontusethiscode: @360Plato i imagine hw will be out at some point lol
thejuror8: Guys cmon, this paper is probably of very good quality. Very little people in this stream, including George, have the knowledge required to understand it, so let's say humble
Nussinov: @georgehotz there is loads of literature on synthetic biology and the generation of proteins with specific degrees of binding affinity
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Any review on the papers?
abhinavneelam: prove the shortest distance between two points is the distance formula
bufferovrflw: *any reviews
chillguy269: Does it have an abstract of what the paper is actually trying to demonstrate?
AresRai: yea
ak0ya_: what exact question are you trying to answer with this paper? @georgehotz
mysterykiller1234: no.
mrhdr: explain
360Plato: its all approximates
dontusethiscode: no
raystriker98: these are peer reviewed?
AresRai: its very vague
Lizardan: @thejuror8 exactly. the wording is not for tech people
Nussinov: I see why you're skeptical but you do not have domain expertise
haroldakme: Why is the computer programmer trying decipher a medical paper
jagger_rsw: remind us :) why are we buying your subscriptions? is it something like if you take over the world you won't kill us (first) or sth else? :)
thejuror8: @haroldakme LUL LUL LUL
thejuror8: I love the character tho
peter35_: "stay in your lane tech bro"
thejuror8: That's just great
KruptWorld: oh, are you saying its not written in scientific form as other papers are?
brownyyyylocks: @ haroldakme why not?
AresRai: lets invite a virologist PogChamp
davedavidsonfromdavis: george is right
Juankinator: @haroldakme anyone should be able to read and understand it
nashesvobodnoye: This is only a summary of current information imho
Ozonemaster: what do they even mean by optimized
Mariosavitch: written by the chinese
11plus4thinking: lab scenario what does that mean 🤔
raystriker98: They're saying it's not a designer virus
Ozonemaster: there are so many things in nature "optimized"
skieth028: are you guys really serious? this is twitch.. hes not really revese engineering the coronavirus... LUL if he is on a lab the might believe it.. like LUL
KruptWorld: in before paper is debunked!
Ozonemaster: thats jus a retarded adjective
ak0ya_: that was produced in the lab
Nussinov: @georgehotz you do not need more evidence than what they referred to LUL it is more or less obvious
Lizardan: @georgehotz It would be awesome if you could invite an infectious disease doctor to your stream and help you with this.
thejuror8: @georgehotz It's very speculative but it's a bio paper, the format is very different from a mathcomp sci. paper of course
ak0ya_: it could still be evolved in the lab
mashafique: People in the field are aware of which lab methods and techniques are available so they would know what would be doable at this time
THX1342: there's no explanation of what the signature of a 'lab based virus' is
raystriker98: I guess bio papers allows for speculation
Mariosavitch: weird flex, but ok
Lizardan: Different from com-sci and math. yeah 4Head
EdwardSnowden25: Hello gerogehotz
JustAsGoodJo: it's a correspondence paper, not a real bio paper. it's like reading a review or a letter, not the same as a bio paper
almonte550: Did you voice changed?
mescal33t: Superhuman AI for multiplayer poker beastyPoggers
skieth028: title is just for views... attract viewers... LUL and its working LUL
thejuror8: It's the Alpha0 paper from DeepMind ? Yeah they are very good
fission1110: this is a letter to the editor not a peer reviewed bio paper
JustAsGoodJo: ^
Nussinov: ^
AresRai: @skieth028 u bite so keep biting
Michaeltth: KonCha
thejuror8: @fission1110 Lol that explains it then
chillguy269: @fission1110 If that is the case that makes a ton of sense
Mariosavitch: it contextually makes sense
skieth028: @AresRai hmmm yummy LUL
dj_vicio: lack of details in the Corona paper because they dont know shit about the virus yet but yet they want to comply with something to filter out dumb vs smart ppl believing in their "facts".
tehEGO: its not a paper
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz fission said it, this is a letter to the editor not a paper
davedavidsonfromdavis: does anyone know what percent of bio papers can't be replicated??
Nussinov: @georgehotz its still subjective LUL you understand the domain-specific jargon better and are therefore more comfortable
tehEGO: no it says at the top its not a paper
pistolpetepcp: can we replicate the virus infection lol, i volunteer
shlver: @georgehotz you need to simulate the environment of inside of the human body, it's impossible to simulate the interactions or other cofactors in the human body. When they say computational analyses they are doing electrostatic interactions between the simple interactions of structure only.
Juankinator: maybe bio papers have stuff that is harder to replicate
ak0ya_: There are good papers
bigie: the ones that stack 10 refinement networks and don't publish code or trained models
ak0ya_: of course
AresRai: some bio papers are very good
Nussinov: this is a letter to the editor
Tomishima: drowing in pappers . information overflow
skieth028: instead of working on. hes comparing biology papers.. again this is purely for enternaiment.. dont be serious about this guys LUL
teslost: paper 7
PiroFloydian: this is a letter to the editor not a paper lmao
williamjennings1: lol
JustAsGoodJo: lol
badmyt: maybe this example works because chess algorithm is a bit easier than NATURE's one? I guess you cant dive too deep in explanations as you'll get to write whole book explaining every single step, maybe people related to medicine know this shit and dont need such descriptive details in the articles
360Plato: a good bio paper imo https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4488989/
Mariosavitch: ur waisting valuable CTF time
thejuror8: Guys if we keep spamming it he will read it eventually
Juankinator: yeah you lost me at the title
jagger_rsw: I sometimes want to read papers on fuzzing, b/c ppl claim great research, and half of it is beyond paywalls. I asked why, and they told me it's for university prestige points.
thejuror8: Hey George apparently it's not a paper but a LETTER TO THE EDITOR
Nussinov: @360Plato go away
archer723: archer723 subscribed at Tier 1.
Michaeltth: robust
davedavidsonfromdavis: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Replication_crisis
mashafique: Literally just highlighting and clicking things and putting on a show and then being confused why you don't understand something LUL
thejuror8: @mashafique cmonBruh
williamjennings1: read the whole paperr
nashesvobodnoye: Knowledge should be free, and intellectual property is BS
skieth028: LUL
saixj: you should do a coding tutorial to bypass some insecure paywalls if possible
imsuperficial: bernie sanders: leading the biological revolution
KruptWorld: the format isnt the same as other science papers
mickjaggerrrr: u should switch to biology
Mariosavitch: Martin Shkreli Hotz == Will cure everything
thejuror8: Unrelated but Elsevier should get lost
lsankar4033: lsankar4033 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
raystriker98: revolution fueled by quantum computing?
GoBerserk: @nashesvobodnoye most of the paywall problem is the publisher not the author
JustAsGoodJo: 1953
Jehhred: What did he say the way to get passed paywalls was?
thejuror8: @Jehhred Sci-Hub via Tor
thejuror8: @Jehhred sci-hub.tw
thejuror8: It's illegal
mashafique: @thejuror8 ?
thejuror8: (Disclaimer)
zwisch: LUL
KruptWorld: sickkk
nitcat: unreal lol
KruptWorld: what is this site
skieth028: LUL
Nussinov: if you knew francis crick you would be afraid to share it
thejuror8: cmon you guys don't know about sci-hub
DecayingSkullz: http://cbm.msoe.edu/markMyweb/sepaTimeline/assets/1. A Structure for Deoxyribose Nucleic Acid.pdf
JustAsGoodJo: watson and crick don't even make any claims in that paper though lol
DecayingSkullz: there it is^
Ozonemaster: why is sci-hub banned in spain anyways? XD
DecayingSkullz: http://cbm.msoe.edu/markMyweb/sepaTimeline/assets/1. A Structure for Deoxyribose Nucleic Acid.pdf
thejuror8: only realistic way any masterdoctorant does any research is Sci-Hub nowadays
ahahahaitslit: probably 90% of people here know sci hub
nitcat: April 25, 1953 and it's paywalled in 2020 unreal
Michaeltth: Rare to come across really good bio papers
thejuror8: @nitcat LUL LUL
Nussinov: LUL LUL LUL
DSykes_: @georgehotz Can you sum up what the fuck you are actually doing
RobotTard: the kid is now a man
thejuror8: When reading old papers I also noticed that the style is so brutally different
UniversalGeneve: yo. its the original DNA paper by crick and watson
imsuperficial: @DSykes_ hes doing coronavirus
pistolpetepcp: Yay functions
thejuror8: Today style of papers is very much pragmatic
Nussinov: uh oh a bessel function nobody tell him about structure refinement and validation
Mariosavitch: yes we do
skieth028: you cant reverse engineer a virus with just googling stuff... you need to be Virologist... LUL even scientist needs 3 years min to make VACCINE and hes doin it on by GOOGLING? LUL LUL LUL LUL
localcanofdutchgold: "bitch"
o______________________k: @dsykes_ just exploring and learning from an autist :)
almonte550: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Replication_crisis
thejuror8: @georgehotz The previous paper that you read is not a paper, it's a letter to the editor. I think it mostly explains the weird style that you highlighted
JustAsGoodJo: bio is separated into subdisciplines. in bio, we use biochemistry and biophysics like that paper. in computational biology, we do analyses. it's not all like a "correspondence letter to the editor" type paper you were reading
AresRai: @skieth028 dude ... stfu
yevheniiushtyk: these streams make me more interested in science and math
Juankinator: @skieth028 dude we are just fooling around shut up
whitesaucey: post modern neomarxists!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! screw em
mashafique: The arrogance of someone who is not a specialist in a field trying to talk about how that field should do something
JustAsGoodJo: LUL
logi6000: we back bois
KruptWorld: @georgehotz could you explain how youre attempting to hack the corona virus? i heard you say 'payload' n stuff which reminds me of jailbreak days
GoBerserk: @JustAsGoodJo is correct
KruptWorld: oh i guess youre doing it now nice
THX1342: rememeber the human genome program? hhundreds of millions of dollars and decade to finish
JustAsGoodJo: @GoBerserk <3
Nussinov: we have been attacking it that way for 30 years
360Plato: but is it really a full picture without the epigenetics?
raystriker98: so the papers should be backed by maths and cs?
KreuzCroix: I mean, it's a really new virus and is not really controlled under a laboratory environment...
williamjennings1: it all makes sense now
JustAsGoodJo: we use statistical analyses, probability densities all the time lol
dj_vicio: if they change concepts/theory/history they can manipulate the future
dj_vicio: its all about perspectiv e
skieth028: "probability" "permutations" "permi" "mutation" LUL LUL LUL
williamjennings1: is that a bed next to his computer
Ozonemaster: yeah
kleyy: fermi
Mariosavitch: me
Nussinov: you are absolutely right!! this is exactly the kind of analysis that was most certainly done and yet NOT communicated in a LETTER TO THE EDITOR LUL
whitesaucey: nobody is george lol
ahahahaitslit: biology is lit
nashesvobodnoye: @georgehotz research computational biology
tshields44: first principle thinking is not common
Tomishima: just 5000 ppl global
dongmuya: nextstraing.com
Abnico: gonna start a biotech company
Tomishima: is the find ppl that understand this shit
shlver: @georgehotz the sequence doesn't exist in a vacuum, how the proteins fold depends on its environment and that environment is in the human body. We know coronavirus binds ACE2 because we can see viral load increasing, computational analyses is limited in scope and cannot take into account the cofactors and physiological factors that could contribute to the change in the structure of the glycoprotein and uptake of viral rna.
Abnico: next bull market biotech will be the new crypto
reportyourself: nice to catch you here bro. luv your wisdom and the interesting content. w000t
Mariosavitch: imagine showing this to someone in 1918
logi6000: @mariosavitch yo just like the TV
hiimwatchingu: @georgehotz hey can u hack into my school and change my grades
GoBerserk: @shlver another person who gets it
ahahahaitslit: u listen to the portal?
nashesvobodnoye: learn to code LUL
Jehhred: lol learnig to code is easier said than done
KreuzCroix: Finally @shlver
KruptWorld: but besides coding domain knowledge is important
pistolpetepcp: Visualizing stuff is fun
logi6000: @hiimwatchingu well you could do that but that's not learning anything. learning is the best thing you can do
Nussinov: dont listen to that viral load guy LUL
Tomishima: learn to code is easier than using this data
Juankinator: anybody can code, writing good code is another story LUL
liejoes1: i
imsuperficial: True. I've been coding for 20 years and my code is mostly shit LUL
360Plato: couldnt you quantify the structure with some characteristics
sit_d: refactor tomorrow
dj_vicio: no, its easier if you turn off all destructive things that deviate you from the goal of learning to program like social media
justdoityourself: @imsuperficial all code is shit LUL
imsuperficial: thanks :)
Jehhred: @Juankinator Then how would you suggest being able to learn to code really well?
williamjennings1: should i buy a mac book pro
Mariosavitch: look it up in the diff viewer (MSA)
Nussinov: this website is super
logi6000: @williamjennings1 do you have the money
pedrovictortech: @williamjennings1 depends on what you want to do
teslost: @shlver is not protein folding still one of the unsolved problems because of the computational complexity?
justdoityourself: @Jehhred do it because you love it
Juankinator: @Jehhred get people that know how to code well to review your code, or check source code from big projects that are well done
WhatDaRob: May I ask what are those charts showing_
WhatDaRob: ?
WhatDaRob: Mutations?
Nussinov: teslost https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Levinthal's_paradox
georgehotz: https://nextstrain.org/ncov?
Jewishrambo: damn this application is complex
GoBerserk: @teslost I'm pretty sure that's correct
Tomishima: THis DNA is worst then X86
pedrovictortech: @WhatDaRob spread
badmyt: diversity of conoravirus types Iguess
yevheniiushtyk: i'm 20, not too late to start taking coding seriously? I'll have to self teach myself though, since HS here taught me almost nothing )-:
pistolpetepcp: i think these are spectrometer graphs
logi6000: yes paradoxes let's go
aliman_21: how much progress have we made?
brownyyyylocks: im self taught! you can do it!!
Riqour: @yevheniiushtyk no it's not this is one of the few things you can start super late and still get decent at
justdoityourself: @yevheniiushtyk the best programmers has certain personality traits, dont discount this
GoldkettenManfred: @yevheniiushtyk its not to late
logi6000: man I learned python when I was 12
bigie: they're poor
dongmuya: The two strains are S-strain and L-strain
Crypod: poor italy FeelsBadMan
25missedcalls: will you play animal crossing tonight?
xPolarDreamz: i dont get what hes doing?
Ghost_001: good question
dongmuya: L mutated from S
Lizardan: @xPolarDreamz title
williamjennings1: @xPolarDreamz i dont know either
Ghost_001: @xPolarDreamz Hacking the world
raystriker98: mutations are usually useless until that one mutation "evolves" it
yevheniiushtyk: like i have been fiddling with code for so long but I haven't made any significant progress, this stream really made me want to pursue coding more seriously and learn all the things
xPolarDreamz: @Lizardan reverse engineerring what
badmyt: this is ridiculous how fast it mutates, how should the vaccine stop it anyhow if it changes itself a thousand of times daily
myaocat: mutation - the changing of the structure of a gene, resulting in a variant form that may be transmitted to subsequent generations, caused by the alteration of single base units in DNA, or the deletion, insertion, or rearrangement of larger sections of genes or chromosomes.
tokumei64: mutation is just any change in the genetic code iiuc
KruptWorld: bro programming is just logic
Usisuvach0: L is the dangerous one
Nussinov: KruptWorld not really
Jewishrambo: if it mutates wouldn't it get weaker because it has had more transmission chains, but if its more lethal less mutation chance idk
dongmuya: L Mutated from S
Crypod: results on masks FailFish
Usisuvach0: S is the mild one
KruptWorld: learn logic and then you can translate that between languages
dongmuya: L is the newer one
Usisuvach0: no
KruptWorld: why not @Nussinov
Usisuvach0: L is the dangerous
Nussinov: KruptWorld syntax, structure, style
dj_vicio: nsa with disinformation
justdoityourself: @yevheniiushtyk you need a full feedback cycle to grow and improve
ahahahaitslit: lmao
Nussinov: LUL
peter35_: there's an isomorphism between logic and computation Nussinov
costcospizza: true
dorkmo: he's on nextstrain github contribtors
Tomishima: ok
tokumei64: @badmyt it's not as simple as that, not all mutations change the virus in a way that makes research/vaccines obsolete
KruptWorld: @Nussinov right, but logic doesnt change
dj_vicio: aderall shot
abhinavneelam: maybe simplified for the general public
thebiggaeboi: LMAO
skieth028: Programmer: i know a lot of stuff im really brainy.. Programmer: *sees a covid-19 publication paper for public consumption* Programmer: wtf this is really complex and complicated XD LUL LUL LUL LUL
thebiggaeboi: adderall shot lol
roach_swalower: adderall shot ftw
elon_musk__: HeyGuys
santi_264: how long has he been straming for
Liz3DE: this the first stream i see live. until now i only saw the uploads on the archive
myaocat: What does "Split into L and S stains with L" means?
iKanak_: iKanak_ subscribed with Twitch Prime.
myaocat: *strains. sorry
thejuror8: @KruptWorld It can, under different axioms D:
tokumei64: the effects are basically stochastic, it couild have no noticeable effect, or it could drastically affect the virality or behavior
Crypod: hear that? that's the hand wash
guacDev: wash for 20 seconds georgie
skieth028: this is recorded... and playing it live LUL LUL LUL
whitesaucey: L strain is more contagious than S strain
pedrovictortech: @georgehotz Just call that dude out! Start some beef!!
KruptWorld: he started at 1:55pm pst
Mariosavitch: rice and ice cream. love it
dj_vicio: more bat icecream
thebiggaeboi: stop taking adderall shots man
luigifrcruz: @georgehotz Preprint paper with more information about strains https://academic.oup.com/nsr/advance-article/doi/10.1093/nsr/nwaa036/5775463
SneakyGamerr: Just got here and i might have a stupid question. What is the purpose/goal of doing this or what is this trying to achieve realistically?
Liz3DE: should i sub?
Jehhred: This man about to eat his bodyweight in ice-cream
pleasepolitethanks: ice cream with a fork
roach_swalower: this dude using a fork for ice cream>>>
Greaser_1: :-)
Mariosavitch: lol
Nussinov: @georgehotz you are misattributing the behaviour of "biologists" to the behaviour of novel science. mistakes are made in all fields, especially in the situation where the science is SEXY and must be published quickly. not all math or ML papers lead to worthwhile results either. while some papers provide significantly more information that others, science is accumulate
Mariosavitch: are you really holding the fork like that
elon_musk__: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid
skieth028: reverse engineer the coronavirs... *EATS ICE CREAM* LUL LUL LUL LUL
Emanuell45: @Liz3DE im pretty sure hotz is loaded
dj_vicio: same fork he used to eat the rice
justdoityourself: corona-virus is already hacked... it breaks down at only slight temperature increase. Viral load can be reduced by just stepping into a sauna
Tomishima: imagine having a fridge
brownyyyylocks: my fav is honey maca
whitesaucey: where is the gf george??
THX1342: myaocat there's a running hypothesis the virus has split into 2 'families', one suposedly being worse than the other
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 subscribed at Tier 1.
Pin__top: good afternoon
ahahahaitslit: yee boi
thiefer20: Check out the account @Bobbeus on twitter I believe it may be an account sending out coded messages relating to Coronavirus
THX1342: myaocat this tweet is calling bullshit
brownyyyylocks: honey macadamia from connosieur
Rydberggg: is he really reading that fast ?
Juankinator: whats the process of getting a paper to in nature?
Mariosavitch: what we need is a simulation of the human so we can run different tests against our cure
Nussinov: Rydberggg yes he is a genius
brownyyyylocks: for all my aussies!!
mashafique: @Rydberggg nah it's just showman shit
360Plato: I would be funny if the classisica etymology of all these bioterms got thrown out for a quantitative classification
williamjennings1: georges studio is so cozy
Pin__top: ice cweam esfandH
whitesaucey: whitesaucey subscribed with Twitch Prime.
badmyt: @justdoityourself tell it to equatorial countries full of ill people
mickjaggerrrr: contact him
edu4594: what is p values
Rydberggg: he has 4 eyes or 2 brains
pistolpetepcp: Dude I hated stats class
THX1342: well, compsci has the benefit of infinite samples
Nussinov: nowadays youd get laughed at in biology for reporting p-values LUL
thejuror8: Yeah I mean, p-values have always been used in bio right ? And Comp-Sci papers used std which is not always better, especially in ML papers in which they're used to bullshit results
Mariosavitch: yay
Jehhred: What else are these biol majors going to do with the introductory stats unit they took?!?!?!?
edu4594: ah, pi
thejuror8: I'd rather have p-values used in Comp-Sci
KruptWorld: fuck youre making me crave icecream
pedrovictortech: P value is the probability of getting a certain respons
danisokpg: gd
sillybaboy: @thiefer20 what makes you think that?
elon_musk__: ezclap
edu4594: valeu @pedrovictortech
lemonboxed: p values is more stats i think
danisokpg: geo everybody can code?
Tomishima: scripted
justdoityourself: @badmyt reduced viral load doesn't mean it doesn't exist. But it changes all the mortality calculations
pedrovictortech: De nada cara @edu4594
u1337ochka: its weird cause statistics itself basically emerged from biology
AresRai: monkaS
Juankinator: cant remember what p value is but i remember it was from stats class in college
williamjennings1: What are p-values?
thiefer20: Check out the account @Bobbeus on twitter they have been sending out coded messages about coronavirus
lemonboxed: std deviation in bio papers
Srule: What key board do you use?
leidad32: @pedrovictortech ué tem BR aq
theonlymonkas: ban
dongmuya: This is the difference https://covid19data.com/2020/03/04/coronavirus-has-mutated-and-2nd-strain-is-even-more-deadly/
THX1342: ban
YellowSnowman_23: rip
mashafique: @Srule monkaS
thejuror8: @georgehotz They do use std in ML papers a lot, most of the time even
williamjennings1: @Srule i wouldnt ask
Vjasal: big pp value
Pin__top: its never a good idea to interpret too much from numbers
sidthescikid: does george always have this many viewers?
Mariosavitch: what is actually a "cure" is it something that stops the spike protein from working?
dorkmo: choo choooooo
theonlymonkas: no LUL
pedrovictortech: @leidad32 EU sou de Portugal! Mas o Brasil é muito bom!! Já vivi lá por um pouco. Petropolis
d0ubletruth: whats a good site for finding ML papers, im new to all this
reportyourself: @dorkmo choo chooo
THX1342: Srule e only answers kb questions if you highlight your message
ahahahaitslit: scihub
Tomishima: @skieth028 is live. all other points are true
edu4594: mano aqui tem muito br
williamjennings1: @sidthescikid no its cause he let non subscribers to view
elon_musk__: ?????????????
danisokpg: everbody can code ? viewers
KruptWorld: yo @georgehotz have you been working on that church thing you talked about hacking nature in like a tedx talk or what??
360Plato: @Juankinator it has to do with statistical significance
Srule: I'll infect your mom with the big D type
mashafique: I can't. The level of arrogance is astounding.
leidad32: @pedrovictortech moro no litoral, Fortaleza
thejuror8: @mashafique LUL true
luigifrcruz: Chat only in english...
Nussinov: @mashafique hes now trusting a tweet over the literature LUL
Mariosavitch: @mashafique leave or contribute
AresRai: @mashafique close the window LUL
Pin__top: penny pinching
pedrovictortech: @edu4594 Brasil e ecnologia estão cada vez mais ligados!! Tem imensos canais de tecnologia fodas do brasil
KruptWorld: loool
BernardoFire: @leidad32 tamo junto BR
edu4594: @leidad32 ja morei na praia do futuro, agora to morando no rj, niteroi
elon_musk__: Promiscuous
araeasmes: LUL
Psycarlo: loooooooooo
1ntegral_: @danisokpg Yep if you're here than you must be interested
nitcat: they got both
sidthescikid: @williamjennings1 wait non subscribers couldn't watch his stream?
ad5k: simplest explanation
mescal33t: beastyLULWW beastyLULWW beastyLULWW
pedrovictortech: @leidad32 Tenho que visitar um dia!!
nashesvobodnoye: welcome to science jargon
mikhailangelo: fight PogChamp
edu4594: @pedrovictortech sim, é muito bacana ver isso
BernardoFire: @pedrovictortech BR BR BR TAMO AQUI
FargioFarmani: Which mouse are you using @georgehotz ?
brownyyyylocks: MAMA SAID KNOCK YOU OUT
luigifrcruz: @georgehotz another preprint talking about mutations.. https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.15.991844v1.full.pdf
leidad32: @bernardofire salv
Jehhred: Why do people use larger words to seem smarter?!?!? make it easy for us simpletons to understand
williamjennings1: @sidthescikid yeah before he would only have subsriber streams
dorkmo: Theranos paper
thejuror8: @georgehotz Btw they do use std in ML papers a lot, most of the time even, how am I bullshitting you when I say that
pedrovictortech: @BernardoFire kkkkkk
dj_vicio: his ricebowl is his mouse
THX1342: bio bois getting triggerred
360Plato: @dorkmo LUL
KruptWorld: lol
Nussinov: @georgehotz reminder that any bio paper written by entirely chinese authors should be taken with a massive grain of salt
Sky_Light_37: @georgehotz can you link the world map with the branches of the viruses pls?
leidad32: @edu4594 praia do futuro era dhr
shlver: @georgehotz you know sickle cell anemia is caused by a single point mutation?
sidthescikid: @williamjennings1 dang, I thought he was all about free info/data
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ so evertbody can code right?
Psycarlo: Big fan. Keep it up! Love from Portugal
raystriker98: do you think half baked bio papers are being published to gain some recognition?
1ntegral_: @danisokpg of course
thiefer20: https://www.mesvaccins.net/web/news/14930-nouveaux-cas-de-syndrome-respiratoire-du-moyen-orient-a-coronavirus-mers-cov-au-qatar
pedrovictortech: @Psycarlo Portugal caralho!!!
williamjennings1: @sidthescikid he post the streams on youtube after
saeveritt: saeveritt subscribed with Twitch Prime.
hexstatik_: @georgehotz are you not concerned about touching your face? :)
thejuror8: @raystriker98 Not in Nature at least LUL
dj_vicio: no bad words @pedrovictortech
KruptWorld: oops it was in the SXSW 2019
Psycarlo: @pedrovictortech mai nada
sidthescikid: @williamjennings1 ahhhhhh
pedrovictortech: @dj_vicio Sorry! hahah
patulskitime: https://seekingalpha.com/news/3554056-ibm-white-house-put-supercomputers-coronavirus-research
elon_musk__: AMAZIN
dj_vicio: @pedrovictortech nah, im fucking with you man hahaha
Nussinov: spoken like a true STEM lord
pedrovictortech: @Psycarlo Como é que está isso ai com o corona
Wireballz: @georgehotz is it man made ?
williamjennings1: i feel so focused
happypuppppy: LUL
Nussinov: @skieth028 LUL
Mariosavitch: lol
elon_musk__: DISGUSTING DansGame
Natterz : Can you not just jailbreak the coronavirus ?
zol0: LUL
Khilimanjaro: LMAO
edu4594: LUL
grey_street: LUL
Lizardan: LUL
Ozonemaster: LUL
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ a lot of practice?
pedrovictortech: @dj_vicio HAHA I got you dude
esence: ban him
yevheniiushtyk: LUK
ColdZer0o: LUL
yevheniiushtyk: LUL
Mariosavitch: LUL
Ozonemaster: disgusting DansGame
ad5k: big profit
Juankinator: LUL
rstk1: LMAO
araeasmes: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
happypuppppy: silenced LUL
Ghost_001: LUL
Ozonemaster: Kappa
mescal33t: beastyS beastyS beastyS
Mariosavitch: HOW DARE YOU
THX1342: Nooooo let him entertain us more
beefydangles: need to wash my hands after seeing this
Nussinov: imagine malding over clickbait LUL
Psycarlo: @pedrovictortech Tens whatsapp?
dj_vicio: show him @georgehotz
nitcat: LOL
PiroFloydian: DansGame
AresRai: disgusting SwiftRage
Mariosavitch: LUL
Waywoah: Waywoah subscribed with Twitch Prime.
edu4594: plot-twist: he really do it
thejuror8: LUL Martin Shkreli V2
Lana_Lux: LUL
akaCube: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
justdoityourself: The Hardness of every science falls off after mathematics, biology has always been filled with incomplete claims
pedrovictortech: @Psycarlo ya
gabo_sk: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
Michaeltth: Kappa can't go anywhere
Lizardan: Go out WutFace
johanoutdoors: yikes
SpecialAgentSkye: LUL
brownyyyylocks: dat sub money
elon_musk__: TREW
Kyoto_o: what a dumbass kekw
norlagg: LUL
patulskitime: money is the root of all good
Mariosavitch: Mariosavitch subscribed at Tier 1.
beefydangles: coronaS
thejuror8: NEW SHKRELI Pog
Jadess: @georgehotz You cant go out. #CoronaVirus
AresRai: going out monkas
on111: monkaS
Sky_Light_37: smogW
bobert_____: Cheer69
williamjennings1: george hotz gets sued by china
zol0: monkaS
Michaeltth: 😷
yevheniiushtyk: monkaS
vaskogomez87: yo temos aqui alguns tugas :D
beefydangles: monkaW
Miestensauna: i'm saving up to get a self driving car one day
beefydangles: monkaS
almonte550: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
sidthescikid: mmonkaS Geo u good?
beefydangles: 😷
AresRai: monkaS
dorkmo: hype train profiteer
Crypod: woke?
KruptWorld: @williamjennings1 haahhahha
dj_vicio: @almonte550 shut the fuck up troll
c0rz1: @Lana_Lux See what reading does to you?
lemonboxed: 10 monies pls
elon_musk__: @almonte550 TREWWWWWWWW
THX1342: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
Psycarlo: @pedrovictortech vai ao mey github, @psycarlo, saca de lá o meu email, e manda-me um mail com o teu numero para falaremos
dj_vicio: @Lana_Lux ban these guys
SneakyGamerr: Hi, this might be a stupid question but here goes. So what is the purpose/goal of this and what is it trying to achieve? No clue what is really going on but i'm hugely interested.
williamjennings1: read a paper front from back
pedrovictortech: @Lana_Lux You here?
edu4594: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
Mariosavitch: All you care about is real world CTF hacking.. HOW DARE YOU!
dorkmo: !claim
icanthitthose: im new to programming i just wanted to know how you reverse engineer corona virus using computer programming
theonlymonkas: ResidentSleeper
u1337ochka: yeah, guys want only one thing and it's fucking disgusting
thejuror8: They got first place in some open competition with AlphaFold, by quite a wide margin too. But they did recycle a lot of existing methods, and well they have Google money so
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ its necessary a lot of practices
mutrx: from corona import *
esence: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
Juankinator: Lux: LUL Direct Relief - Charity 2018akaCube: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting subscribe to me if you agree Kappa
nitcat: @mutrx LMAO
360Plato: ban this schmuck @almonte550
dj_vicio: @icanthitthose you can only reverse engineer it with HTML and javascript/css
THX1342: from covid import pwn
d0ubletruth: from corona import vaccine
ad5k: something like zfc proofs for biological findings would be useful
KruptWorld: hes making a jailbreak for the corona virus
ralaxe: are you a biologic man or something like that?
Lana_Lux: @pedrovictortech yes
Ekshernul: p values are an ok instrument, there are several huge problems with how it's used though since people just use 0.05 threshold without fucking thinking and knowing how tests work and what p value implies.
AresRai: @icanthitthose its his first time doing this, ask in a week FeelsGoodMan
pistolpetepcp: reverse(corona)
Wireballz: @georgehotz do you think this is man made?
Lizardan: Lot of people here that dont know George prob thinkin he's serious about getting subscriptions and attention LUL
JesseSkinner: i heard it normally takes 10 years to make a vaccine, is that true?
Jadess: It's all fun and games, until you cough!
lemonboxed: its hard to get good weights to train a deep learning model in a field where the data is inherently messy like bio
Vjasal: you can ban one person in chat, but can you ban the truth?
bob_babyelephant: from dumb import corona virus
THX1342: @Lana_Lux I knew you were a hacker
elon_musk__: @Wireballz Yes I made it
AresRai: @Lizardan LUL
skieth028: ROFL dont copy paste man i have a wrong spelling there LUL LUL LUL
on111: LOL how are people getting baited by this title. geohotz just does random coding stuff when he streams
Wireballz: lol
lemonboxed: i wouldnt get my hopes up
Dawoud3: have you heard that Santor Rand Paul tested positive from the Virus https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1241897485779468288
pedrovictortech: @Lana_Lux How are you??
SneakyGamerr: @georgehotz Hi, this might be a stupid question but here goes. So what is the purpose/goal of this and what is it trying to achieve? No clue what is really going on but i'm hugely interested.
Lana_Lux: @thx LUL
Michaeltth: I'm here to watch the cure real time :)
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ broooooo
pedrovictortech: @Psycarlo Ganda trabalheira mas pode ser
thejuror8: It really is tho
Lana_Lux: @pedrovictortech doing alright!
skieth028: and PLEASE SUBSCRIBE guys... you're welcome LUL LUL LUL LUL
KruptWorld: @SneakyGamerr im tryn to figure it out too. he put up the library he made on his github
lemonboxed: its hard to get good weights to train a deep learning model in a field where the data is inherently messy like bio
elon_musk__: NO
Mariosavitch: no
Lana_Lux: @pedrovictortech how you doin?
elon_musk__: MAYBE
almonte550: here we go again with the simulations
kevin21071: whats folding@home for?
mickjaggerrrr: lol
Mariosavitch: we are in a sumulation
Rydberggg: you can do everything
beefydangles: with quantum computing
pedrovictortech: @Lana_Lux I am great and you??
360Plato: other factors are missing again like epigenetics
thebiggaeboi: add me on linkedin george
SneakyGamerr: @KruptWorld i've looked at the github just now and i'm trying to make sense of it. But i feel like this goes way over my head. :p
dj_vicio: we live in a simulation - The Matrix (1999)
elon_musk__: WE NEED A MATYOSHKA BRAIN
justdoityourself: @almonte550 when the only tool you have is a hammer....
kevin21071: You might need a quantum computer
anotherkidnamedaustin: to coagulate
Nussinov: google molecular dynamics simulations Kappa advanced stuff right there
u1337ochka: lemonboxed i think there usually isn't that much data in bio either
Usisuvach0: i think computer cannot help with this
thejuror8: It's NP-HARD
luigifrcruz: Simulating how simple proteins work would be a good starting point..
theonlymonkas: games
thejuror8: Protein structure prediction is NP-HARD
KruptWorld: @kevin21071 you donate your computer power to scientists who are running computations on folding proteins
beersnbits: George you should checkout folding@home
tj_rl: Let's start by simulating the universe
1ntegral_: @danisokpg Should begin with simple language like C to learn the basics Data structures memory etc
pedrovictortech: @Lana_Lux Did I just ask how you were twice? hahaha my dumbass
Not_Saercy: https://www.scottaaronson.com/talks/colloq.ppt
lemonboxed: protein complexity is like max complexity iono
anotherkidnamedaustin: the planck era of proteins
t_lokus: iBM had their mainframes doing protein simulations for covid, there are results published
williamjennings1: he wasnt joking when he was doing his talk at sxsw he really does think about hacking nature constantly
elon_musk__: ResidentSleeper
almonte550: If we simulate the whole universe can we solve coronavirus?
lemonboxed: its convoluted af
KruptWorld: folding@home currently doesnt do corona virus
saeveritt: cheer500 Lattice models are a trap
1ntegral_: then you can learn easier languages like python @danisokpg
GTozzi: LaTeX shows makes you look legit
mutrx: Its called molecular dynamics simulations
Nussinov: yes
JesseSkinner: yeah you just upload the human genome and it spits out a 3D image of a human body. WEIRD SCIENCE
Jehhred: of course similation works. We're living in one!!!!!
sidthescikid: what's the goal for this stream, is it just to formulate a plan of attack?
elon_musk__: it's to cure void
Lentaij: What's the dataset he's working with?
williamjennings1: @sidthescikid fun
Wireballz: Wargames "do you want to play a game"
elon_musk__: monkaS
Mariosavitch: beer virus monkaS
Usisuvach0: make a corona virus fuzzer @georgehotz
justdoityourself: @sidthescikid to enjoy watching how george prods at issues
AresRai: @sidthescikid pass time learn and share
thejuror8: There are a lot of Protein Folding problems that are proved to be NP-Hard at least
almonte550: @sidthescikid we are just learning stuff, it looks like we are doing stuff but in reality we aren't
mutrx: @georgehotz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lLFEqKl3sm4 molecular dynamics simulations
Krylexx: we live in a simulation
magicallyphysically: Can you link?
magicallyphysically: Please
KruptWorld: @Lentaij no dataset i think its the dna sequence of the virus
jagger_rsw: massively parallel search process
Mariosavitch: so how do you make a cure? do you block the spike protein?
elon_musk__: We can destroy the virus with a nuke
sidthescikid: I see I see, I like his process at problem solving
tshields44: https://github.com/yangkky/Machine-learning-for-proteins/blob/master/README.md
magicallyphysically: The Simulation
luigifrcruz: @Lentaij a handful of public nucleotide sequences from SARS-CoV-2
beefydangles: link the vaccine
superduperepic: ah yes of course 5Head
t_lokus: @georgehotz IBM has some results on protein simulations for covid https://www.ibm.com/blogs/nordic-msp/ibm-supercomputer-summit-attacks-coronavirus/
tenseroverflow: Whats going on?
williamjennings1: just take addearall and watch this stream
ageMonkey: is this thunderfoot?
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ yeeee bro
ehisoka: bof the virus for win
elon_musk__: y=kx ez
justdoityourself: @elon_musk__ lol you can kill it with a blow dryer
KruptWorld: jailbreak it @georgehotz !!!!! hahahah
Kyoto_o: keyword RANDOMLY
elon_musk__: @justdoityourself m8 that's a bit overkill
tj_rl: shake that
Kyoto_o: how much random is random
tj_rl: What is random?
anotherkidnamedaustin: simulate the planck era of proteing coag
anotherkidnamedaustin: pogger
magicallyphysically: 2012? quite ancient information to go off..
Lizardan: CNAT HEAR WutFace
KruptWorld: @Kyoto_o not random at all
Nussinov: @Kyoto_o stupid person has an interesting question, strange
williamjennings1: cant hear anymore
elon_musk__: Molecules DansGame
KruptWorld: quantum physics is the only pure form of random
Kyoto_o: you know nothing about "randomness" if you think it's a stupid question
cactusvacuum: https://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Research/namd/
Kyoto_o: @Nussinov
lemonboxed: hes basically saying to simulate nature they use a random model bc we have no idea how it actually works
ehisoka: youtube volume down
danisokpg: somebody knows about of sockects in Python?
Iknowyou123456789: pytorch or tensorflow @georgehotz?
ehisoka: is geohot ready for rap ?/
oubriq: wait til you read the fortran code :P
360Plato: see STRUCTURE can be quantified
Nussinov: @Kyoto_o LMAO i said you were stupid and the question was good. nice reading comprehension dummy
FargioFarmani: Please meditate again @georgehotz
justdoityourself: @Kyoto_o does randomness have a reference frame? that is the core issue
tj_rl: @Nussinov stfu
Kyoto_o: @Nussinov that makes even less sense, you are braindead
kevin21071: is this the lynda guy, that voice
shlver: They are lol
tj_rl: Stop bullying
Iknowyou123456789: why does he use chromium vs chrome?
mutrx: @georgehotz software is called GROMACS you can download proteins from https://www.rcsb.org/
Kyoto_o: @justdoityourself it does if it's generated within a personal pc, every state can be predicted
araeasmes: ultra-fast PogChamp
danisokpg: anybody knows about sockets in Python?
williamjennings1: puting your desk in your kitchen is great idea
tshields44: https://github.com/sha256feng/mldl-md-dynamics
rgbeezus: 2080ti fast
sidthescikid: @georgehotz do you have a reading/book list for 2020?
luigifrcruz: Folding@Home is trying to simulate the behaviour of the spike protein to find know weak points for medicine.https://foldingathome.org/2020/03/15/coronavirus-what-were-doing-and-how-you-can-help-in-simple-terms/
mutrx: @georgehotz software is called GROMACS you can download proteins from https://www.rcsb.org/
whitesaucey: George "is it open source" Hotz
Emanuell45: @sidthescikid he just skim reads everything
Lizardan: There's nothing more random than George's brain
sidthescikid: I kinda see that now lmfao
beefydangles: just read everything 4Head
tenseroverflow: @sidthescikid you think your skills are as good as his?
tokumei64: @williamjennings1 that's probably his whole apartment, if it's like mine
xPolarDreamz: get corona and research yourself
Khilimanjaro: LUL
nitcat: LMAO
pistolpetepcp: LOL
Mariosavitch: LUL
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Krylexx: PogChamp
360Plato: kek
yevheniiushtyk: easy money LUL
AresRai: LUL
tj_rl: lol
Emanuell45: KEKW
edu4594: LUL
sidthescikid: LUL
DecayingSkullz: LUL LUL LUL
くじょう: LUL
BOODLEG: LUL
xx_owlcapwn_xx: LMFAO openly admitting that LUL
Pin__top: D:
tj_rl: HAHA
beefydangles: EZ
esence: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
dj_vicio: how dare you?!?!!
cankunwang: cankunwang subscribed with Twitch Prime.
mutrx: LUL
oMYTHRA: LUL LUL
Mariosavitch: worked on me
ddd_dota: !uptime
brittonx2: Hahahaha
zeroeagle1: dammit just lost 5$
eiscosogin1: LUL
Liz3DE: LUL
KruptWorld: LUL
aiis: 200iq
sidthescikid: LUL TRUE
beefydangles: 4Head
1ntegral_: LUL
Nussinov: REEEEEEEEE I CLICKED AND SUBSCRIBE FUCK YOU FOR TRICKING ME
Mariosavitch: big if true
1ntegral_: So smart
kevin21071: dude how much money?
justdoityourself: galaxy brain
beypazarigurusu: disgusting
SneakyGamerr: Exactly the explanation i expected :D
Jehhred: Sounds legit, keep it up
Lentaij: easy -$5
almonte550: he world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
anotherkidnamedaustin: oh
kevin21071: Lets al go do it
Daniel_Duan: 4Head
IndoPridePinoy: HOLD UP TRUTH HAS BEEN TOLD
peter35_: clintSuave
anotherkidnamedaustin: so ur the scam
Pin__top: when am i getting my corona bux george
xx_owlcapwn_xx: 4Head hahahahah
edu4594: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
RomeoR77: I'm sold
KruptWorld: i gave him all my life savings
anotherkidnamedaustin: ur the scam, not the state
SneakyGamerr: This is who we should all give our money to!
bufferovrflw: PogChamp
THX1342: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
mutrx: PogChamp mark up price 5000% like Martin Shkreli
Emanuell45: what is this corona bro science
Ghost_001: not high btw LUL
SpecialAgentSkye: Works for me PogChamp
gollosadstation: place coronavirus for clickbait and study biology insted LUL
dongmuya: clutching my pearls right now
yevheniiushtyk: You laugh, but that's actually what some people are doing rn lmao
tokumei64: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
lemonboxed: the best scams tell you they are scamming you in the first clause
pz3300: Give us corona some hype George!
theonlymonkas: LUL genius
IaMvAzU: im in on the joke
sidthescikid: He's in
Mariosavitch: ban 'em
zeroeagle1: im sarcastic
IaMvAzU: stockGachiBear stockGachiBear stockGachiBear stockGachiBear stockGachiBear
PiroFloydian: we're all in on it
edu4594: on the joke, lul
beefydangles: its the next martin shkreli
RomeoR77: But george, how I get you to take my money?
Mariosavitch: yes
dj_vicio: yes
tj_rl: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
pz3300: We cool George?
theonlymonkas: martin shkreli is cool
samthedogg: some guys cant take a joke/get offended at the slightest
tj_rl: ;)
DecayingSkullz: he world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
Pin__top: elizabeth holmes D:
Ghost_001: FeelsBadMan
RexRothx: He must be new to Twitch...
KruptWorld: hell yeahhh
Lizardan: how do I donate a million dollars to your channel?
oMYTHRA: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
vaskogomez87: well guys, 2:30am here. in 5h already up. bye guys
mutrx: this is a great copypasta
sidthescikid: NEW COPYPASTA LUL
AresRai: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
edu4594: LUL
dj_vicio: aderall shot again
SneakyGamerr: he world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
bufferovrflw: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
ColdZer0o: he world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
nitcat: wheres the gofundme
mutrx: stock buy backs
xx_owlcapwn_xx: rofl
PiroFloydian: maybe the original guy was meming too @georgehotz
yevheniiushtyk: DiSgUsTiNg DansGame
williamjennings1: Is he drinking tap water!
beefydangles: PogChamp
Mariosavitch: big if true
Emanuell45: you know youre smart when your head is that big proportional to your body
mattdacentaur: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
sidthescikid: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
herrmuckelmann: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
Mariosavitch: nothing
nashesvobodnoye: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgustin
t3rminal: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
不好意思: LUL
ehisoka: ROFL
Pin__top: how did you know about my erectile disfunction!
t_lokus: @georgehotz IBM had some simulated proteins runs for "pre-fusion spikes": https://www.ibm.com/blogs/nordic-msp/ibm-supercomputer-summit-attacks-coronavirus/
reportyourself: stop spamming clowns
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ i have a questtion bro...
Lizardan: @Pin__top your username
JefeBezos: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to “REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS” and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
justdoityourself: watching geohotz give you big pp. You heard it here first
patulskitime: where is the github?
1ntegral_: @danisokpg Go ahead
samthedogg: @georgehotz lol was that an idiocracy reference? about baldness and ED
Penguino138: Just got done watching Devs, what is George up to now? Still parsing out the RNA?
JakobJayJohnson: !uptime
xx_owlcapwn_xx: killing the virus with python 4Head
KruptWorld: oh thank god your going over it
williamjennings1: what the fuck.
THX1342: that quote is pure gold
Tomishima: STOP with your highlight SPAM. Avoid useless and meaningless words and certain phrases that will bring zero value to the chat. You are destroying not ONLY my chat EXPERIENCE but everyone's chat EXPERIENCE.
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ so, to code its necessary a lot of practices
Nussinov: the membo
1ntegral_: @danisokpg Of course
SneakyGamerr: How is doing all this even possible?
beefydangles: STOP with your highlight SPAM. Avoid useless and meaningless words and certain phrases that will bring zero value to the chat. You are destroying not ONLY my chat EXPERIENCE but everyone's chat EXPERIENCE.
SneakyGamerr: :o
anotherkidnamedaustin: a membrane
Nussinov: it is correct
Sullyboy: sounds righ to me
anotherkidnamedaustin: its just a membrane
Sullyboy: right*
tokumei64: nice try @Tomishima
Mariosavitch: so to stop a virus you have to prevent the spike protein from functioning? @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: fluid
Kingxpecc: when did you start streaming
danisokpg: @1ntegral_ how much?
sidthescikid: Its a generic cell membrane in biology jargon
tenseroverflow: it is NOT correct
tenseroverflow: it is correct
mutrx: !uptime @Kingxpecc
xPolarDreamz: i dont know how you can use code to reverse engineer the corona
THX1342: the image on the wikipedia page, on the replicaiton seciton, gives some light on how the layers are formed during covid reproduction
Kingxpecc: !uptime
Kingxpecc: ! up time
不好意思: this is really interesting
mutrx: @Kingxpecc it isn't enabled lol
360Plato: ACE 2 is the vector right?
THX1342: I still don't get how the quine works....
Kingxpecc: lol
ghu90: https://plnkr.co/edit/TNuAIB1mFn01O1tG6KtM?preview
Kingxpecc: lol thanks thou
almonte550: Which one of those spikes has more information?
Nussinov: ah, i see you're misusing words to weed out the dumb memorizers Kappa
SneakyGamerr: I just love how he explains all of this!
t3rminal: med students feel free to correct him in chat
KruptWorld: ive been waiting for this @SneakyGamerr
thejuror8: @Nussinov LUL
Mariosavitch: rna transcription?
AresRai: you're speaking about the place where peptides take their shapes ?
williamjennings1: not loged in google
SneakyGamerr: @KruptWorld YEP me too! Sooo hugely interested in this!
barbadose: a ribosome..
Nussinov: a replicase
hellonearthis: touching face and biting nails is bad right? Is this work similar to the folding at home dot orgs sars-cov-2 floding?
williamjennings1: khanacademy
Nussinov: would copy the genome of an RNA virus
esence: just transpile that RSA into JavaScript bro
Lentaij: Is there really no interpreter like SMILES for proteins?
THX1342: RNA translation happens with the ribosomes
whitesaucey: talks about corona on twitch STONKSSSSSS
THX1342: ribosome is the organele
ghu90: this may help https://plnkr.co/edit/TNuAIB1mFn01O1tG6KtM?preview
yevheniiushtyk: we need a discord server lads
l1ght5p33d: NOVEL TRANSPILE 2020
sidthescikid: no a ribosome is the process to hook tthe randa
sillybaboy: @esence Javascript is an illness itself
tj_rl: Challenge corona to CTF
SneakyGamerr: How does one even begin to learn about all of this stuff. Does this come from previous knowledge or did he just started learning about all of this recently?
Mariosavitch: ribosome is the compiler?
sidthescikid: this is pre-ap bio
THE_korbi: geo you are so cool!
barbadose: ok so, what is this guy's background? what did he study?
danisokpg: so what is the meta ??
whitesaucey: the mitocondria is the powerhouse of the cell!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Nussinov: @georgehotz i think youre thinking of a replicase? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RNA-dependent_RNA_polymerase
MorningScifi: check his wikipedia page hahaha
tj_rl: @SneakyGamerr He doesn't know everything. But he's really good at learning on the go
AresRai: @barbadose no biology dont worry :)
THX1342: ribosome is a parser
tj_rl: @barbadose Computer science
barbadose: @AresRai didnt think so lol
l1ght5p33d: novel dynamics 2020
THX1342: Qira for BIo when
1ntegral_: How do you do Dynamic analysis on corona ?
SneakyGamerr: @tj_rl Yea i've noticed. I'm just getting increasingly impressed by the minute
1ntegral_: difficult no ?
barbadose: what lvl of cs? :P
lemonboxed: except its not a cpu its just similar
THX1342: we need a bio debugger with breakpoints and all
tyrobigboy: 5Head simple really
Kingxpecc: whats your twitter geo
Lizardan: @barbadose god level
Mariosavitch: exactly mr hotz
esence: trial & error method
tj_rl: @SneakyGamerr The point is you can do this too. Don't be afraid to jump into a subject just because you don't know a lot about it
thebiggaeboi: truuuuuuuuuu
DecayingSkullz: First Principles
Minghello: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: geohot = ultra leet
1ntegral_: That's the spirit yeah
Kingxpecc: nvm
thebiggaeboi: truuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Pin__top: immediate feedback
danisokpg: geo hack something
Nussinov: you don't get anywhere if you try to learn only the things you already know Kappa
chillguy269: Most people so afraid to look dumb that they do not even start
tehEGO: in the words of missy elliot, flip it back down and reverse it
mutrx: @georgehotz MDS simulator is called GROMACS, and you can download proteins from https://www.rcsb.org/
mickjaggerrrr: problem solving
dongmuya: He doesn't care about being right, he cares about profit! SeemsGood
theonlymonkas: no
SneakyGamerr: Yea the learning process is amazing! And seeing you step through it honestly is really educational. At least in my eyes.
Mariosavitch: the fact that you can cross discipline is awesome.
portitforward: a lot of people end up in tutorial hell when the real way to learn is to continuously attempt things
THX1342: most people are afraid to learn. they get intimidated when they don't know something and stop at that
Juankinator: he only wants that twitch money Kappa
l1ght5p33d: all the datas is are belong to us tho
lemonboxed: unless the underlying central dogma of bio is wrong, then we wont be going foward
bacca18121: everyone in silicon valley is a charlatan
MorningScifi: hahahahaha
lemonboxed: microbio
nitcat: "did you sub to geohot on Twitch?"
KruptWorld: lolol
Michaeltth: back to the grind
Mariosavitch: lol
Pin__top: learning things are very frustrating when diving in with no prior education
Psycarlo: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
1ntegral_: @nitcat LUL
Mariosavitch: heaven is gated for a reason
lemonboxed: isnt that just what calvanist think
Stegosaurian: Is anyone you know infected?
GTozzi: That's what the Ferengi believe
hellonearthis: ask a for different god
gabo_sk: LuvBrownR LuvBrownR LuvBrownR LuvBrownR
abdcw: its fine guys i got my virginity back i paid my church 2k
lemonboxed: thats like the most boring version of heaven
araeasmes: LUL
theonlymonkas: but do you have 1M dollars?
Lizardan: No corona in heaven BlessRNG
Emanuell45: ??????
araeasmes: lmao
esence: AYO, 1MIL AND FIDDY
dj_vicio: whats this?
Psycarlo: God's only accept Bitcoin
Mariosavitch: so thats why theres a gate
Lizardan: @theonlymonkas LUL he's got more than that
360Plato: or you just do a bioinformatic startup selling snakeoil
KruptWorld: lool
sidthescikid: ???
Pin__top: speaking in riddles again
Ghost_001: ???
gollosadstation: that's aint matrix can't be right
zeroeagle1: ahhahahahaha
Ghost_001: G OMEGALUL D
THX1342: LUL
nitcat: LMAO
anotherkidnamedaustin: should be backtesting data..but love watching u stream and its rare
mutrx: what's God's bitcoin address
liiiiiig0: LUL
dj_vicio: time for aderall again
Psycarlo: loooooooooooooooool
akaCube: bitcoin cash DansGame
Snowlav: LUL
tehEGO: NAh you get to the gate and says work to earn enough to get to earth 2.0
thisuserisdeleted: THE MATRIX HAS YOU
samthedogg: bitcoin cash is trash
liiiiiig0: LMAO
zeroeagle1: BitConnect !
yevheniiushtyk: BITCONEEEEECT
Juankinator: god only accepts doge coin
不好意思: lmao
DecayingSkullz: Bitconnect
Not_Saercy: Spoilers! Not cool man
lemonboxed: bitcoin cash
chillguy269: Those poor 20th century fucks
samthedogg: bitcoin, eth, tron
ToxicVulpes: BCH or BTC?
CompestLive: whats his btc address
lemonboxed: its bitcoin but still cash
SpecialAgentSkye: BRB buying btc cash
chillguy269: wrong time to be alive
Abnico: bitcoin cash has a tax now lol
THX1342: Faketoshi IS God... (at least in his head)
thisuserisdeleted: Coronacoin
xPolarDreamz: bitcoin cash is a joke
nitcat: so right the ribosome is the parser right
danisokpg: this boy is rich?
justdoityourself: the constant stream of trolling... pog
samthedogg: Bitcoin, eth, and tron are he only good ones rn
ToxicVulpes: cant get into the Citadel without Bitcoin Cash
Lizardan: @danisokpg google him
dj_vicio: rich? idk maybe not. Using the same fork for rice and ice cream.
luigifrcruz: meta
sidthescikid: Humans make humans 5Head
pistolpetepcp: sheit what makes that ribosome
tyrobigboy: like a human making another human
tehEGO: which came first the ribosome or the ribosome
FargioFarmani: f
esence: SERIALIZER
thisuserisdeleted: what is a human?
Michaeltth: an event last week 👀
l1ght5p33d: Recursive ribosome(Recursive ribosome)
THX1342: tehEGO the golgi complex
hellonearthis: it seem like your reproducing the folding at home work. https://foldingathome.org/2020/03/10/covid19-update/
nitcat: that'd be crazy
thejuror8: You mean, an FPGA ? LUL
KruptWorld: fuck me
danisokpg: @lizardan i think that ye
Emanuell45: brains are cheap?
sidthescikid: Actually true
thisuserisdeleted: Has anyone seen toilet paper? I am looking for it and I cannot find it anywhere.
lemonboxed: brains arent really that cheap to build it took like 300 million years
Mariosavitch: big if true
mattdacentaur: @lemonboxed
thisuserisdeleted: brains are useless when you let someone else think for you
nitcat: just a learning experience shared to us
Emanuell45: do you know how much food a brain needs hotz?
l1ght5p33d: we find corona cure here open source
saixj: preach
mattdacentaur: its cheap now because that 300 mil was just r&i
Liz3DE: Learning!!!
thebiggaeboi: toilet paper machine learning
cankunwang: This is self learning
KruptWorld: aaahhh
yevheniiushtyk: Would be cool if we had an Discord server where we could share knowledge at
Juankinator: i feel scammed, unsubscribing Kappa
esence: OK, GUYS, GET THAT COPYPASTA OUT THERE, IT'S DISGUSTING
THX1342: @georgehotz it's interesting exploration but a fresh viewpoint and framework can bring novel ideas
dongmuya: He's trying to make profit, not save the world. Geez how many times does he have to say it? HeyGuys
thejuror8: @georgehotz Hey a good move would be adding "#learning" to the title of your stream :)
GTozzi: pepega
xx_owlcapwn_xx: lol
akaCube: so insperational Pog
thisuserisdeleted: did you guys find the cure yet?
Nussinov: im just here because im lazy and want free entertainment
justdoityourself: 90% of brains are NPC brains so they are a waste
MorningScifi: and novel coronaviruses @THX1342
eiscosogin1: did you make 1million yet?
sidthescikid: There's no TTV here cmonBruh
thisuserisdeleted: NPC brains lol
anotherkidnamedaustin: martin skrelli said the same things
KruptWorld: disgusting you profited from exploring the corna virus
theonlymonkas: D E E P
thisuserisdeleted: we just scripted to consume
BrodatyWhiteBear: Well... I'm not gonna lie, I would accept his Kappa
eddoo: hello
rgbeezus: arxiv
thisuserisdeleted: but the problem is where there is nothing to consume our programming breaks down
myaocat: they try to make a potential vaccine https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yP8GH1MkuRK5rmMpJSOF4OgFwqdx5b7y/view
l1ght5p33d: ecoli grows cure protien novel open source 2020
cankunwang: Most journals do not accept BioRxiv papers
KruptWorld: hahaha
tehEGO: lol
Pin__top: charity is a scam
araeasmes: nice
abdcw: yo sci-hub also kinda slaps no cap
MorningScifi: LOOPHOLE!
Nussinov: true
lemonboxed: were journals ever alive tho
danisokpg: how are your toyota geo
thisuserisdeleted: we live in the future
PiroFloydian: charity shouldnt need to exist and yeah it is a scam
sidthescikid: What's the alternative to charity
idkfa22: idkfa22 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
dongmuya: Invest the profit right back into yourself and write it off as a loss cmonBruh
Nussinov: sidthescikid hell
PiroFloydian: @sidthescikid a functioning social safety net
justdoityourself: @PiroFloydian except when it isn't
dj_vicio: I heard the 3rd stage of CoVID-19 uses antibodies to fight against you and ultimately kills you
thisuserisdeleted: nobody told me memes can't save me
THX1342: @georgehotz did you check the mRNA vaccine video I shared yesterday?
sidthescikid: @PiroFloydian like a UBI lmao
myaocat: Are they legit? https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yP8GH1MkuRK5rmMpJSOF4OgFwqdx5b7y/view
dongmuya: @idkfa22 iddqd
lemonboxed: it could just be a rebranding of a terminoolgy to patent a new class of drugs
Mariosavitch: How do we know that the spike protein will bind to a specific receptor?
thisuserisdeleted: i think last phase of the disease is where we meet it in person face to face and comes out of a spaceship
Pin__top: i will gift 5 subs if you find the vaccine by the end of stream
saeveritt: Yo. Next stream you should make a digital asset protocol inside OP_RETURN for bitcoin cash
THX1342: Mariosavitch chemical bonds
barbadose: some chode
swagomgswag: chode
l1ght5p33d: pure f#$%ng magic
dj_vicio: mother chode
herrmuckelmann: no ssl
herrmuckelmann: oof
Nussinov: oh hey i used to work with this guy
justdoityourself: @Mariosavitch because people get sick :)
thisuserisdeleted: we figured it out guys. download your brain into twitch and then you can never get infected. genius
Ghost_001: good animation = future LUL
Mariosavitch: I meant if i have a spike protein do I have to simulate wha receptor it will bind to?
AresRai: @Ghost_001 indeed 5Head
mattdacentaur: @thisuserisdeleted but you do get cancer
lemonboxed: the future of bio is to animate your protein models with random wiggles
barbadose: what is the purpose of this btw? what is he trying to figure out?
AleexM: What is computational power of fold@home used for? @georgehotz
Nussinov: the language is good
lemonboxed: the future of bio is sick animations
luigifrcruz: @georgehotz Greg Bowman is the director https://twitter.com/drGregBowman
thisuserisdeleted: how can you get cancer if youre just bits on a server? you cannot get anything anymore. you good for ever
tj_rl: ^
KruptWorld: @AleexM folding the protien
justdoityourself: @Mariosavitch of course, if you want to trace the pathology
shlver: @Mariosavitch by cell electrophoresis.
cankunwang: p<0.05
Pin__top: more like poo values
thisuserisdeleted: ahaha he pointed at the wrong one
Mariosavitch: thanks
AleexM: Is there any source on how that works @KruptWorld ?
swagomgswag: LUL
360Plato: We can finally quantify outcomes
xa1ry: what's the issue with p-values? @georgehotz
Snowlav: thisuserisdeleted bits still get flipped often
xPolarDreamz: i need some free energy
theonlymonkas: q values
thisuserisdeleted: ain't nobody gonna flip my bits
l1ght5p33d: any study can be flawed and have all the p values you want
Snowlav: thisuserisdeleted u new to cs?
KruptWorld: @AleexM im trying to re-learn about it too. i heard about it when it came out on the ps3 and i would fold@home with it.
thisuserisdeleted: @Snowlav yes
Snowlav: ok makes sense then
thejuror8: The fact that p-values are misused does NOT mean that they should be banished altogether. They are still a great tool
thisuserisdeleted: im new how can i make sense
hellonearthis: Sounds like something from the tv show "Devs"
myaocat: https://reason.com/video/biohackers-are-on-a-secret-hunt-for-the-coronavirus-vaccine/
Snowlav: thisuserisdeleted u don't that's the point
myaocat: Is this real?
nikudino: its exponential, we need quantum
raystriker98: quantum computing levels of compute
dongmuya: Theres no P values in heaven
THX1342: @georgehotz did you check the mRNA vaccine video?
shlver: @georgehotz the structure changes depending on ph. the pka of certain amino acids determines their electroengativity
thisuserisdeleted: yes @Snowlav
Nussinov: @georgehotz are you a frequentist or bayesian thinker Kappa
McAze: disgusting
lemonboxed: you can compute for as long as you want , doesnt mean you will ever make a working simulation
pistolpetepcp: I have a big p-value
Michaeltth: HackerMan
Mariosavitch: Co-Author: George Hotz
thisuserisdeleted: so i guess i was right there are different strains going around
dj_vicio: seems legit
KruptWorld: @AleexM so what i know so far is that after the protein is shitted out in a straight line it just starts to 'fold' on it self. and we are running simulations to simulate that random folding on itself to get the right fold
thiefer20: George Shkreli
THX1342: CRISPR
zeroeagle1: They understood how the world works
THX1342: CRISPR vaccine
myaocat: they didn't use any of the money they received..
BOODLEG: have you heard of DRACO? from MIT?
hellonearthis: does the cure involve gargling bleach and shorting cocaine
justdoityourself: p-values == wrath of khan protomatter
theonlymonkas: martin hotz
sidthescikid: CRISPR is overhyped, its very small scale and isn't feasible
thisuserisdeleted: i m not gonna take the cure if it involves suppositories
lemonboxed: dna vaccines are stupid
swagomgswag: i would for money
l1ght5p33d: find set of all possible folds
Nussinov: just inject that plasmid right up into those cells Kreygasm
luigifrcruz: I don't think these guys have Class 4 Labs..
shlver: @georgehotz the structure changes depending on ph. the pka of certain amino acids determines their electronegativity. High temperature, excessive changes in pH causes differing changes to structure.
Nussinov: ill show you my f-pilus if you show me yours Kreygasm
myaocat: They are making it..(producing it), they are not testing it because it's cost a lot money
Pin__top: what if corona merge with ebola
theonlymonkas: for how long he has been streaming ?
AresRai: 6h
hellonearthis: french news said they hard good results for treatment with anti malarial drugs
Mariosavitch: ACE2
thisuserisdeleted: intelecturals on reddit are calling corona ebola 2? @Pin__top
Ghost_001: !uptime
Pin__top: @thisuserisdeleted, oh god
esence: @Mariosavitch you like Ace Ventura 2 too?
KruptWorld: wait @georgehotz, wouldnt simulating the physics between atoms enough to simulate proteins? or anything for that matter? do we really have to get quantium? i think quantium is just for collapsing the infinite amount of wave functions, if im not mistaken...
Mariosavitch: great movie
MorningScifi: It's literally SARS 2
lemonboxed: the protein doesnt respond to the immune system thats like down a different chain
lemonboxed: proteins just make stuff
theonlymonkas: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: need quantum because tunneling
AresRai: @hellonearthis its because it contain zinc something else that allow zinc to go through cells, which slow the ATP process and slow reproduction of the virus according to a video
thisuserisdeleted: theres a lot of sars related diseases tho
Iknowyou123456789: what is your WPM? @georgehotz
luigifrcruz: I think the immune system is trying to bind with the spike protein to prevent it to bind with pulmonary cells.
l1ght5p33d: classical solution is not the same as quantum for small systems like optical tweezer
myaocat: @lemonboxed i read that protein inject to the body and try to make antibodies.. something like that
theonlymonkas: KappaRoss
myaocat: * the immune system tries to make antibodies based on the protein
1jefferson: !commands
thisuserisdeleted: what if the virus mutates to a more deadly strain like mers but remains just as contagious
hellonearthis: thanks @AresRai
hitmanhax: scam
MorningScifi: mix in some frog DNA for good measure
edu4594: they used word...isn't even latex
myaocat: @hitmanhax probability is 50%
shlver: @georgehotz if you truly want to understand how physiological environments affect protein structure, you need to look at how pH affects amino acids and their side chains.
Nussinov: written like a narcissistic undergraduate Kappa
cankunwang: Every saw Jamal Murray's video?
barbadose: I actually don't think antibodies (B-cell response) are too important as a mechanism of defense against the virus, most viruses require a strong T-cell response
almostquiet: Man, i'm coping with this shit as good as i thought, i'm getting serious cabin fever and insomnia. Like i'm used to being socially isolated for but it's somehow 10x worse when the world is falling apart
THX1342: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MtDMXypfnTY watch this later if you didn't yesterday, geo, mRNA vaccines are interesting stuff
Mariosavitch: its like patching
lemonboxed: its probably better to understand the heirachy of order for each system before trying to "hack" anything
almostquiet: not*
lemonboxed: if you want to get anywhere
liiiiiig0: PogChamp
thiefer20: protonmail btw
astrailz: George "This is awesome" hotz
myaocat: no .. how do you know they are legit?
mickjaggerrrr: wow
KruptWorld: disgusting
williamjennings1: lol
theonlymonkas: instinct
hitmanhax: haHAA
sidthescikid: 6 grand bruhhh
barbadose: @georgehotz I actually don't think antibodies (B-cell response) are too important as a mechanism of defense against the virus, most viruses require a strong T-cell response
williamjennings1: donating realy money
thisuserisdeleted: haha ez money
myaocat: How do they know they are legit?
Mariosavitch: scamaz
bob_babyelephant: !time
almostquiet: what are they doing exactly that's so awesome?
Nussinov: oh, so this is an ad then Kappa
theonlymonkas: rich boi
lemonboxed: barfhackers
thisuserisdeleted: diy biologist
Mariosavitch: a scama scaming a scama
1ntegral_: Biohackers LUL just hackers
Emanuell45: seems scuffed af
thejuror8: Lmao imagine giving money to those guys
thisuserisdeleted: bioscammers
imfunniee: saw the corona repo, came here asap Kappa OhMyDog
NuHaru: yo george what are you doing?
Lizardan: Biohackers Kreygasm
lemonboxed: here we go again with barfhackers
williamjennings1: 20 bucks!
Pin__top: there is a book written in 2010 about corona D:
l1ght5p33d: open source only
thisuserisdeleted: Bioscammers are on a search for the ultimate heist.
thejuror8: Are they going to test vaccines on themselves ? what even is this
imopfloors: b i o h a c k e r s
mickjaggerrrr: 50 mate
MrYasser2194: can i get a link ?
NuHaru: @georgehotz u are a nice guy, what is the paper about?
pistolpetepcp: sending them $5
eaterenrgy: Pog $20
Nussinov: okay chat 4 people subscribe its the only way to keep this streamer from going under
Keyeh: lets donate 1 BTC!
eiscosogin1: if you send 20 bucks your profit will reduce
yevheniiushtyk: bit co neeeect
Ghost_001: biohackers PogChamp
sidthescikid: @Pin__top Proves my conspiracy theory
eaterenrgy: zentrePOG
KruptWorld: @NuHaru hes just exploring the biology of the corona virus
thejuror8: From fecal transplantations to COVID-19 vaccines, bioscammers truly never stop FailFish
almostquiet: b i o h a c k e r s aka ultimate cringe
esence: refresh the page to prove it to us
Kodaly: u ab out to leak your bitcoin address by saying that O_o
samthedogg: deff gonna guy more bitcoin if the fed prints another $1.5trillion like they did
pistolpetepcp: since I lost all during the crash lol
SneakyGamerr: why exactly would it be worth donating? What about that document peaked your interest?
almonte550: Can you send us the transaction hash to make sure u r not lying?
imfunniee: bitconnnnneeeccctttt
Pin__top: https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/978-3-642-03683-5.pdf
zombiedigital: biohacking is more like with crispr i assume,
SpecialAgentSkye: sending 10 as well
Mariosavitch: so nice
niiq: donate to CureVac Kappa they need it Kappa
swagomgswag: @esence do it urself
almostquiet: Nice document though
tokumei64: @Kodaly doesn't matter, you can't just randomly pull bitcoin from an address
Vnz0v: u hacked sony
l1ght5p33d: this is the best stream
thisuserisdeleted: i bet these biohackers bought out all the toilet paper
tokumei64: i think he's aware of the lack of anonymity as well
360Plato: gatekeeper
happypuppppy: did he post the doc link already
Kodaly: @tokumei64 one of the advantages of having a bitcoin is that it's anonymous...
thejuror8: @zombiedigital Biohacking = Attempting to do medecine outside of academy with mostly weird motives
DecayingSkullz: yes
myaocat: full screen?
almostquiet: I hear just farting noises
eaterenrgy: Yes
Nussinov: i would have spent that 20 dollars on more toilet paper Kappa
IaMvAzU: yeaaa
almostquiet: Is that correct
MllCZ: geo about to become a bio engineer
Pin__top: springers also has another book written in 2005
Emanuell45: wtf
keith282: @Kodaly bro most people have a few hundred bitcoin addresses and the money with unique ones being used for almost if not each new tx chill lol
thisuserisdeleted: nice animations
t3rminal: its a front for a meth superlab
thisuserisdeleted: what vide game is that?
thejuror8: FailFish
myaocat: that's BTC not BCH .
Nussinov: FailFish
shlver: imagine people injecting themselves LOL
thejuror8: Oh my god
Michaeltth: the fear was these kinda guys were going to cause the next outbreak lol
justdoityourself: GMO Dogs?
JakobJayJohnson: @almostquiet i farted very noisy. Sorry bro
Zenzutsu: they use themselves as test subjects
imfunniee: wait so they are hackin real life
thejuror8: Imagine injecting yourself with a vaccine YOU MADE
thisuserisdeleted: imagine living in 2020
thisuserisdeleted: wait
almostquiet: @JakobJayJohnson np
mutrx: yikes, that's a lot of ethical violations
Emanuell45: imagine one of them creates hulk POG
almostquiet: Coronope? lol
Nussinov: They all sound like they injected one too many vaccines not gunna lie
mutrx: they probably made a vaccine that causes autism
sillybaboy: concerned about anonymity, voice not even scrambled ....
thejuror8: Absolutely immature
thisuserisdeleted: They deff inject something and is not vaccines
GTozzi: Do you have a public key @georgehotz
Zenzutsu: bionerds
sidthescikid: @Nussinov LUL
myaocat: I hope you didn't send to BCH address..
zombiedigital: this is starting to look like that movie "contagion" where this random guy comes out with a fake vaccine and makes millions of dollaz
s0rrz: actually hidden meth laboratory
thisuserisdeleted: I didn't know crack addicts are called biohackers now
THX1342: Dengvaxia
sidthescikid: Bureaucracy kills
Michaeltth: worst sideaffect allowed is autism Kappa
l1ght5p33d: They also blew up astronauts a few times so stuff happens
THX1342: Dengvaxia is an mRNA vaccine that failed hard in the Philipines in 2018...
shlver: lol so it's cool for people to make DIY vaccines and inject themselves. FailFish
mattdacentaur: autsim Kappa
dj_vicio: why he's using bitcoin cash?
thisuserisdeleted: nice jar bro
almostquiet: 3d printed antibodies bro, it's the new hype here in cali
dongmuya: China: no fucks given with red-tape testing SMOrc
Zenzutsu: just ask china for the vaccine
thejuror8: @zombiedigital Hey the Contagion movie is incredibly accurate, I rewatched it recently. Scenario was so realistic that almost everything that happened in the movie pretty much happened in this last month is some way or another
Nussinov: okay this might actually be a good thing
AleexM: "Get Johnny Knoxville to try it!" LUL
zombiedigital: @thejuror8 yeah true, i rewached it aswell
thisuserisdeleted: imma gonna watch Contagion movie now
ahahahaitslit: cleavage (Y)
saeveritt: Who's going to sequence the spike protein though
IndoPridePinoy: how much bitcoin is that?
almostquiet: 20
solitarynative: does he know anything about viruses before this
Sniky83: what's the goal of you're doing ?
xPolarDreamz: view the owner of pdf file
almonte550: @solitarynative no
georgehotz: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yP8GH1MkuRK5rmMpJSOF4OgFwqdx5b7y/view
SneakyGamerr: @Sniky83 From what i understand. Exploration and education
RHN_X: So what exactly are we doing here, just tuned in
thisuserisdeleted: yesterday america had 24k cases now is close to 33k
xPolarDreamz: 3 dots -> details
Nussinov: can we see any more technical details for this proposal? explaining the requirements for a plasmid is not really enough, you know
l1ght5p33d: geohot know everything becuase python
JakobJayJohnson: Are vaccinations safe?
almostquiet: Can confirm america is fuk
robg_10: !uptime
B0tch: DONT TOUCH YOUR FACE GEORGE
xPolarDreamz: Zach Weissmueller
hitmanhax: he's the author of the article
sidthescikid: @solitarynative From what I can tell he has taken chem classes in college
thejuror8: LUL Just realized they get paid in Bitcoins at the worst possible time to get paid in Bicoins, possibly
THX1342: a DNA factory
solitarynative: ok
siazhenwei: hi
THX1342: uses bioreactors
thisuserisdeleted: imagine combining heroin and corona everyone will get addicted Kappa
edu4594: btc takes 10 minutes to confirm
buckkets_: 10m block time sir
THX1342: they use bacterya to replicate the DNA
Keyeh: usa has the best spread of the covid19, the greatest --- absolutely
myaocat: he probably sent to BCH address and this is BTC.. (shrug)
Sniper_pro497: the Queensland government of Australia has just given 17 million dollars to the scientist's of the Gold Coast Queensland Australia the scientist's said they will have a vaccine for the conorvirus in January 2021
keith282: @RHN_X making a vaccine using python, online subscribers get to have it
THX1342: @georgehotz under development. they are way cheaper when they work
Lugueiro: !uptime
barbadose: !uptime
eaterenrgy: 6hr 8 mins
mutrx: a vaccine really isn't going to help us at this point
hitmanhax: ^
Pin__top: there is an article written in 1983 about corona im trying to find it
eaterenrgy: zentreDerp
thisuserisdeleted: can you even create a vaccine for this virus?
keith282: woah mutrx D:
Vnz0v: protonmail lmfao
THX1342: mutrx wrong... this is endemic now. a vaccine would help immensely
wootawee: Might be of interest: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1kP2w_uTMSep2UxTCOnUhh1TMCjWvHEY0sUUpkJHPYV4/edit
thisuserisdeleted: i thought this virus mutates incredibly quickly how you gonna make a vaccine that can target all possible mutations
l1ght5p33d: vaccine for corona 202(*)
ahahahaitslit: how tf would a vaccine not help
zombiedigital: sars is a rna virus
Mariosavitch: because big pharma wants to monopolize the industry and the use the FDA to keep it that way
niiq: valve worked with "Perfect World" to launch cs go in china.... the first case of corona virus was on 17th november. On 18th november they released a big update to cs go. the theme: a virus outbreak ... coicidence ? surely not!
KnollBoss: dna vaccines on humans doesn't get through testing
KnollBoss: FDA hates the shit
THX1342: @georgehotz Look at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MtDMXypfnTY
pz3300: @VnzOv is protonmail the feds?
thisuserisdeleted: i feel like retroviral are the only way and they are still lots of years until we can use those
GTozzi: APS are limited by patient locks
thisuserisdeleted: or maybe nanotechnology ? but thats just scifi
KruptWorld: thanks @georgehotz ! it was fun!
GTozzi: patent***
kevin21071: theres ton of open source closed loop systems
thisuserisdeleted: i think this disease is just a new seasonal flu
mutrx: @THX1342 the time it would take to develop one is much better spent on implementing lockdowns, and social distancing (to reduce the curve); not to mention the money is probably better spent supporting citizens. Wuhan managed Cov19 without a vaccine, it isn't essential to manage the spread.
pz3300: Or just eat healthy
thisuserisdeleted: they probably gonna create a seasonal corvid 19 shot
THX1342: DNA are the new hype because of the development speed. it is code, you can edit it and reuse code
THX1342: DNA vaccines
Mariosavitch: Skype SHKRELI from pirson and ask questions
Pin__top: here is an article from the 80's https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC288755/
Michaeltth: they gonna release shkreli so he don't get the rona?
JakobJayJohnson: Is life a big fucking scam?
THX1342: mutrx you have to think on future epidemics, not just the current one
thisuserisdeleted: see they shouldnt have jailed Shkreli . now they need all the help they can get Kappa
hitmanhax: free shkreli he's the only one that can fix this
pz3300: Do you use signal a George?
Ghost_001: actually high look at him LUL
justdoityourself: shkreli didn't kill himself
thisuserisdeleted: im glad biohackers are on the case. With biohackers we gonna win this pho sho
Mariosavitch: imagine if shkreli comes out of prison and then cures corona
pistolpetepcp: martige shreklihotz
l1ght5p33d: Shkrelis has bad interview ediquette he f*(&#d himself
thisuserisdeleted: but he charges 1 million for 1 shot
PiroFloydian: LMAO
Nussinov: l1ght5p33d actually stealing is what fucked him
GTozzi: But there are multiple other boards/stages you have to go through in the European system (negotiation stage ostensibly) with governing bodies that do require ethical evaluation
mutrx: @THX1342 right now we need to focus on the current epidemic, and then we can investigate better strategies
KnollBoss: i would settle for jack dorsey consumating passionately with me
dorkmo: noise complaint from Twitter hq
myaocat: https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-working-treatment-coronavirus-blood-recovered-patients-n1165231
PiroFloydian: what about the ability to edit tweets? @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: the judge couldn't let him go after all his talking sh#t
YoungScootah: Free shkreli
peter35_: to shkreli clintSuave
pz3300: Disrupting his yoga
Nussinov: one thing is for certain - you would benefit from him being innocent Kappa
THX1342: mutrx I think we can handle multiple things at once :D
myaocat: this may be faster https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-working-treatment-coronavirus-blood-recovered-patients-n1165231
keith282: i put all my ooin into chainlink XD
keith282: coin*
mutrx: @THX1342 not when the labs themselves are being closed, at least that's happening at my facility
thisuserisdeleted: i think if we all pray for america together at the same time that praying power concentrated on only one place will cure it. so we can do that for every country
samthedogg: bitcoin is going to recover after the halvening in May
DecayingSkullz: maybe you sent it to a BCH address instead of BTC
samthedogg: @DecayingSkullz nope
KnollBoss: @mutrx how did u find this stream sir
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz u gotta refresh the page
Lugueiro: @samthedogg ohh yeeahh
Nithron: omg 1 BTC
FastCashCoding: yea we still headed up
FastCashCoding: bullish AF
3ygun: Remember when Ethereum was worth something
KnollBoss: VITALIK
KnollBoss: crash it
PiroFloydian: i think if we all pray for america together at the same time that praying power concentrated on only one place will cure it. so we can do that for every country
YoungScootah: @georgehotz do you have any advice for a computer science student who wants to be a software engineer?
KnollBoss: @YoungScootah usually boils down to gain skills and code
mutrx: @KnollBoss i watched his vods on youtube and followed his stream on twitch
thisuserisdeleted: Christian viral healing bois
JakobJayJohnson: George looks like he's doing bodybuilding.
keith282: @YoungScootah if you want to become a software engineer then engineer softeare
KnollBoss: interesting
peter35_: you think ada/cardano is going anywhere?
mutrx: confirmed 20$ scammed
THX1342: lightning network?
l1ght5p33d: watch all geohot streams... strive to be a fraction of the leetness
FastCashCoding: fuck... if its confusing for geohot we got problems on mass adoption
FastCashCoding: its a segwit address
YoungScootah: @keith282 4Head
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz it's a segwit addres, refresh the page
sidthescikid: We're still doing the payment? I thought Bitcoin was fast...
Abnico: its a bep32 adress
Abnico: adress
samthedogg: @georgehotz itsa BECH32 address
Abnico: address
thisuserisdeleted: BETCH 32?
localcanofdutchgold: @YoungScootah switch all software design classes with math classes
FastCashCoding: not*
Abnico: https://ibb.co/1TpCsd0
YoungScootah: @localcanofdutchgold Sounds like a trap lol
Hawklite: btc can take up to an hour or two it's slow af
myaocat: https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-working-treatment-coronavirus-blood-recovered-patients-n1165231
im_drew_: george your the man bro!
axlebear: Yoink
localcanofdutchgold: @YoungScootah opposite, just don't know yet
YoungScootah: @localcanofdutchgold Explain please
Abnico: Bech32
saeveritt: Time for a bitcoin stream. Make an asset protocol for Bitcoin Cash where the data is nested in OP_RETURN
JakobJayJohnson: It Was At This Moment That GEORGE Knew He Fucked Up.
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz should have arrived regardless
thisuserisdeleted: time to juice up the recovered patients
Nussinov: @myaocat vampires
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz if you scanned the qr code
Lugueiro: @georgehotz segwit native (bech32)
Emanuell45: noo
NuHaru: dont worrz george i got zour bcoin man
williamjennings1: so many tabs.
Mariosavitch: i learned a lot thanks mr hotz
l1ght5p33d: BEST STREAM NOVEL BIOHACK 2020
youngmarsh: damn I'm late
DSykes_: hmmm yes
Lugueiro: yess
FastCashCoding: brian armstrong @georgehotz
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz part 3 when?
ahahahaitslit: the portal
KnollBoss: @georgehotz how many hours of leisure per day do u think is necessary
THX1342: if anyone has 3D printers, you can help out https://blog.prusaprinters.org/from-design-to-mass-3d-printing-of-medical-shields-in-three-days in my town were printing 320 and giving it to hospitals
Pin__top: i member
thisuserisdeleted: i learned quite a lot man now i know a cure is on the way for sure by next month plz
pistolpetepcp: I sent my $5 I don't see it yet
CompestLive: How much was it?
JakobJayJohnson: Great stream, great 20 Dollars scam
Abnico: @georgehotz relevant meme https://ibb.co/1TpCsd0
DecayingSkullz: gn
o______________________k: !claim
Lugueiro: 1m2019.com
ahahahaitslit: u listen to the portal?
firmstool: How close are you to finding a cure? PepeLaugh
dorkmo: choo choooo
Lana_Lux: good night!
imopfloors: gn
hitmanhax: !claim
l1ght5p33d: Lets do bio startup
PiroFloydian: gonna stream more soon?
edu4594: gonna stream tomorrow?
thisuserisdeleted: i had some summer plans so ideally if the cure could be delivered by april 1st would be grand
mutrx: 3 minute q&a?
hefty_sum: 10 push ups
localcanofdutchgold: @YoungScootah software design is meh in terms of ideas
ad5k: Later
nitcat: night man, thanks for the stream, learned a shit ton of new stuff alongside you
georgehotz: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
CompestLive: How much did you lose?
KnollBoss: 3 minute qna
Mariosavitch: IG is for women
KnollBoss: sir
KnollBoss: only 3
Abnico: https://ibb.co/1TpCsd0
DecayingSkullz: 1m2019.com
ghu90: https://plnkr.co/edit/TNuAIB1mFn01O1tG6KtM?preview
keith282: HOW ARE YOU NOT VERIFIED ON IG YET
keith282: WTF
thisuserisdeleted: april 1st we found the cure!! sych
sidthescikid: sidthescikid subscribed with Twitch Prime.
elektroids: ty
DecayingSkullz: #verifygeohot
mutrx: end of stream q and a?
mik12f4: do more videos please
Ne0Zer0: o/
sillybaboy: facebook is an illness
PiroFloydian: well fb is shit so
pistolpetepcp: Tik-tok
Tsoding: VoHiYo
AleexM: george u da man
inciMage: any audiophile here on chat i need headphone rec
un3okapi: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on black women
ahahahaitslit: do you listen to the portal podcast @georgehotz
Iknowyou123456789: tensorflow or pytorch @georgehotz
djcows: easiest way to get rich as fuck?
sidthescikid: Good stream <3
mutrx: have you been tempted to make an algo for trading?
360Plato: wouldnt trust you if you had a blue check
DecayingSkullz: what does 2021 hold
myaocat: #BlueVforGeohot
lsfa: How to get past coders block?
edu4594: streamm tomorrow?
williamjennings1: do you sleep in your kitchen?
JakobJayJohnson: How big is your diaaack?
Nussinov: @georgehotz cya! keep reading and learning! thank you for the stream! :)
dj_vicio: fucking cancer
thisuserisdeleted: 2021 will be more of the same thing
Pin__top: what ever happened to that waffle maker
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are your reasons doing anything?
dj_vicio: say it
thisuserisdeleted: quarantine 4 lyfe
Abnico: bro check my meme otherwise i suicide https://ibb.co/1TpCsd0
NuHaru: im a computer science major, should i do bioinformatics @georgehotz ?
KnollBoss: @georgehotz if ur not doing stem should you switch subjects
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz tik tok is for the younger generation lmao
CompestLive: How tall are you?
DecayingSkullz: What book are you currently reading?
samthedogg: @georgehotz what do you thing about the NEAT algorithm
ahahahaitslit: do you listen to the portal podcast
saixj: delete tiktok that piece of garbage
Penguino138: Are you an Alex still dating?
kevin21071: TikTok has an algo that measures how good looking you are
dj_vicio: that's it? you quit?
aiis: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
Pin__top: yay
ahahahaitslit: lmao
Ne0Zer0: every night PogChamp
PiroFloydian: fun
l1ght5p33d: SOLVE THE WORLD WITH PYTHON
saixj: yes pls do it ever night
hitmanhax: thanks homey
pistolpetepcp: lol tik-tok is like vine, not ideal
Hawklite: what time do you typically go live
Nussinov: @NuHaru read about it and see if you are interested. if you are interested, do it!
yevheniiushtyk: Pog
samthedogg: NeuroEvolution of Augmenting Topologies NEAT
Stegosaurian: !uptime
ghu90: i loved learning with you
THX1342: yep keep going
CompestLive: How tall are you?
myaocat: biology is like computer.. there is the theory and practical.
FastCashCoding: can we make alot of money @geo?
THX1342: gn
jay_al97: have you got a shell yet?
dj_vicio: what??? already?
saixj: it is a great learning experience
dongmuya: g'night!
highxsnow_: tiktok is a gay dating app
el_pirulote: i understood that i am retarded
Nussinov: clickbaiting that hard takes a lot of energy dont it
williamjennings1: its only 8pm
brittonx2: I'm really enjoying these! Thanks George!
ahahahaitslit: u gotta listen to the portal podcast george
mutrx: only 8pm LUL
JakobJayJohnson: What you think about Alex Jones?
YoungScootah: @georgehotz can you be my CS mentor ?
PiroFloydian: CmonBruh bedtime?
saeveritt: Yo lets DDOS Bitcoin Core Nodes by abusing OP Codes in the Scriptsig
Newlax: @georgehotz why don't you use linux?
williamjennings1: what time do you wake up?
dj_vicio: @georgehotz you doing the 24-hr stream challenge?
hefty_sum: sleeb well
KnollBoss: slee
KnollBoss: p
Ne0Zer0: tomorrow we won't pretend to reverse engineer corona PogChamp
NuHaru: yes!
CompestLive: Yes! How tall are you?
dj_vicio: NO
Wireballz: @georgehotz do you think virus is man made ??
gabo_sk: yeah
sidthescikid: PogChamp
DecayingSkullz: yes pls do that
mutrx: what would we do as emotes?
yevheniiushtyk: PogChamp more streams means more knowledge and more fun PogChamp
l1ght5p33d: we would run out of proplems to solve
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Pin__top: yas queen
Alwaysidle_: where would you recommend to learn python?
ad5k: tea emote
gabo_sk: PogChamp
eaterenrgy: zentrePOG
GTozzi: Is there a place I can private message you? I run a non-profit relating to tech law and would like to her your perspective if interested. Smile face @georgehotz
Nussinov: becoming a twitch partner would be a DREAM COME TRUE Kappa
wootawee: FFS the virus is not man made, sigh
dongmuya: Hotz goal is to buy a yacht he said so on lex freiman
zol0: leaving? hope you made enough money off of this cickbait scam Kappa
AleexM: Just say no to corona guys, it can't enter your body without permission
pedrovictortech: Do it @georgehotz
lsfa: How to get past coders block?
Mariosavitch: lol
dorkmo: is work open in california?
0R4NG3: lol
pistolpetepcp: Same here, i'll be here everyday bro
Newlax: why don't you use linux?
ahahahaitslit: Do you listen to any podcasts
ghu90: lul
Iknowyou123456789: pytorch or tensorflow @georgehotz ?
360Plato: hackerrank bro
KnollBoss: @georgehotz how easy is it to get rich
jmp0ut: how do you know it's not manmade
edu4594: miss backspace.ai
williamjennings1: meditation stream?
Ne0Zer0: corona no coroning
Pin__top: some places its open
dj_vicio: just say it louder to Corona. She'll understand eventually.
jmp0ut: i heard china was testing broad spectrum antivirals last year
l1ght5p33d: the journey is the destination
mutrx: algo trading
myaocat: how long do you think it will takes to hack the brain?
sidthescikid: don't say it!
NuHaru: making roblox maps
Pin__top: be a full time streamer
KnollBoss: thank u sir i am renowned for my dumb questions
Jehhred: sell drugs. easy money
cankunwang: Short the market now
THX1342: hacking a bank
Mariosavitch: start a "Reverse engineer corona" stream
yevheniiushtyk: a lot of money
rgbeezus: stock options
saeveritt: algo trading
Crayonsss: Bitcoin couple years ago LUL
0R4NG3: hack crypto exchange
dr_set: Crypto scams?
Iknowyou123456789: pytorch or tensorflow @georgehotz
THX1342: algo trading is a fast way to get poor
djcows: like 5 million
mutrx: visit r/wallstreetbets to get rich @georgehotz
pistolpetepcp: Ask for money
Newlax: @georgehotz moneyz
sillybaboy: commiefornia
williamjennings1: millionaire.
Pin__top: rich spiritually
saeveritt: CoronaCoin
JakobJayJohnson: Would you work for google if they contact you?
AleexM: easiest way to become rich? Be super rich and donate to biohackers
ghu90: founding funeral ompany
DecayingSkullz: What is your perspective on neuralink
samthedogg: Most of getting rich is about having alot of charisma to bs people
KnollBoss: @georgehotz independently wealthy enough to not have to work daily
l1ght5p33d: extracting money from the economy should not be the goal
cankunwang: Look at Vix
sidthescikid: @samthedogg True
Nussinov: can you make a myfreecams stream called engineering a reverse coronagirl
saeveritt: CoronaCoin ICO soon
jmp0ut: financial stability involves selling packaged sawdust to refugee camps via UNESCO
keith282: if you want to be rich, make your own crypto
raystriker98: opinion on rust
samthedogg: you still shittin on waymo?
Jehhred: What company would you work for then??!?!?!?!??!
dj_vicio: was the NSA On the phone earlier telling you to "shut it" and then reprogrammed you with meditation?
djcows: ferrari as a daily driver and a house in the hills
archer723: Any chances we can do another $10 for the song stuff, really miss that, bro
boneitis: didn't he work for project zero for a time? :P
saeveritt: Have you seen those Crypto with useful Proof of Work? You could make one for simulating protein structures probably in a provable way
360Plato: 750k is fuck you money
NuHaru: is bioinformatics the future @georgehotz
pistolpetepcp: If god could ask you for money, you could too
mutrx: @georgehotz easiest way to get rich is to be born into a wealthy family
pjayys77: Why do you say no way in hell for working at google @georgehotz
scarbromangler: would you rather get corona or genital herpes
l1ght5p33d: kitchen is so nice
firmstool: Why would you not work for Google or deepmind?
AleexM: LUL
sillybaboy: @saeveritt the antibodies are your private keys
sidthescikid: @mutrx Key word: get
saeveritt: @sillybaboy let's do it
Nussinov: im 80 and ive been working at mcdonalds for 60 years im now a millinoaire AMA
JakobJayJohnson: Do you ever dreamed of sucking your own diiaaaack on the beach in winter?
KnollBoss: yeah the game just seems so bad
Digital_donger: @firmstool culture I think
jmp0ut: if you're a babyraping UN peacekeeper then raping a haitian woman and paying her in food scraps for sex to feed her baby means you're richer than her
saeveritt: Have you seen those Crypto with useful Proof of Work? You could make one for simulating protein structures probably in a provable way
Iknowyou123456789: Why no to google?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what would you do, if you werent streaming ?
ahahahaitslit: u listen to any podcasts tho?
DecayingSkullz: Do you follow first principles way of thinking
Emmaralds: are you rich george?
williamjennings1: lol
iKanak_: @georgehotz ever consider playing CTF again?
myaocat: How long do you think we will be on isolation?
sunole: You are a researcherand not developer??????
360Plato: working on contract in faraway places is "easy"
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what would you do, if you werent streaming ?..
sillybaboy: your dono is still not there
jmp0ut: real news
CompestLive: How tall are you?
djcows: do you think net worths on the internet are genrally lower or higher than the people's true net worth?
firmstool: Why would you not work for deepmind?
dj_vicio: where you work at @georgehotz
ahahahaitslit: podcasts?
yevheniiushtyk: do you need college to be good? NotLikeThis
pistolpetepcp: Oh I got it: Ask for money, in return for services
sidthescikid: monkaS
Crayonsss: could you get rich illegaly if u wanted?
magicallyphysically: Imagine if Rich People are feeling overwhelmed at this point in time?? Imagine how the poor Lower Class and Middle class are dealing with this. This is some bullshit.
esence: why don't you want to work for Facebook?
saeveritt: Useful Proof of Work == Protein Structure SImulation
Stegosaurian: How many people do you estimate COVID-19 is gonna end up killing? And what do you think it's economical impact will be?
l1ght5p33d: meta principals way of thinking only obviously
Iknowyou123456789: Virus would go away if it turns warmer right @georgehotz ?
cankunwang: Do you lost in stock market?
CompestLive: How tall are you?
sidthescikid: You need poor people to get rich people
samthedogg: is a straw bent in half 1 holes or 2 holes?
esence: @georgehotz do you watch TechLead?
jmp0ut: @georgehotz come to the canadian shield with me to build a particle beam from the asthenosphere to the vanallen belt so we can make the small arms dealers stfu and world peace for deep space engineerring
ahahahaitslit: podcasts?
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are you reasons for doing anything?
almonte550: When is this crisis going to end?
THX1342: lies... virus is well in south america
xPolarDreamz: Do you think is the end?
myaocat: Is coronavirus changed the world? would we change the way education system works?
Emanuell45: @esence i was going to ask the same thing lol
ak0ya_: what do you read every day?
YoungScootah: @georgehotz you remind me of Martin shkreli
sillybaboy: @Stegosaurian the economical impact will kill way more people than the virus
Pin__top: how many people will gain from corona virus
magicallyphysically: Yes exactly every class SUPPORTS eachother.
un3okapi: @georgehotz how do you fit a square peg into a round hole?
ColdZer0o: @georgehotz what happened to your VR headset
magicallyphysically: You need every class to cooperate.
Iknowyou123456789: When is your IPO? @georgehotz
nitcat: lmao what a question
firmstool: Why did you say you would never work for Google?
zol0: 2 holes confirmed Kreygasm
boneitis: toilet paper hang over or under?
jmp0ut: i got planets to teraform
xPolarDreamz: Is this the end?
magicallyphysically: Yes this is the end.
hellonearthis: hope it brings in a UBI
lsfa: How to get past coders block?
magicallyphysically: End Times.
gill_bates_macrosoft: hey @georgehotz can you do something like the cryptopals challenge
NuHaru: its 1 hole watch vsauce
ahahahaitslit: podcasts?
ghu90: dont be extreme
Nussinov: @georgehotz MUST ANSWER THIS QUESTION MY LIFE DEPENDS ON IT https://embed.gyazo.com/611a66d1dfd1dc187ab289c302b6bba9.png
dj_vicio: where you work @georgehotz ?
PiroFloydian: thats the stupidest take ive heard in a while
360Plato: put it one
pjayys77: think there was a study that a combination of warmth humidity not just warmth might effect the spread of the virus
ghu90: its just a virus
djcows: LUL
CompestLive: How tall are you?
dj_vicio: another aderall? damn
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
zol0: over PogChamp
hitmanhax: pro play
dorkmo: make bet on date of 1 million infected
magicallyphysically: I have used 1 roll of Toilet Paper in `one month EVERYONE IS STUPID
magicallyphysically: ...
Jehhred: Would you rather be the worlds best racquetball player or receive $70.00?????!?!?!!?
samthedogg: if you go to college for an art degree.....enjoy poverty
roystang: tabception
boneitis: i'm floored that you had to check that. thanks for the response geohot
bfgz: if your TP hangs under youre a mutant
THX1342: @georgehotz is Idiocracy a documentary or a comedy?
dr_set: can we get more Hack The Box some time? That was fun.
Not_Saercy: What is something you would like to work on but can't?
keith282: @dorkmo april 3
ahahahaitslit: you listen to any podcasts?
zol0: LUL
360Plato: can you engineer a better adderal after this is over
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Hawklite: why should we care about prolonging humanity?
Morality: lul
PiroFloydian: LMAO
Lana_Lux: LUL
mutrx: LUL
almonte550: When is this coronavirus crisis ending? weeks or months?
saeveritt: Whens the next track dropping
eaterenrgy: zentreKEK
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are your reasons for doing anything?
Emmaralds: whos the most famous person uve met?
xPolarDreamz: How much money does it cost for a vaccine for corona?
ahahahaitslit: u listen to any podcasts?
myaocat: Can you hack recaptcha? Kappa
l1ght5p33d: covmap > nmap
JakobJayJohnson: Are you 6 foot 2?
sidthescikid: @georgehotz What classes did you take in college?
magicallyphysically: Cool
Nussinov: dogs are having a great time these past months, everyone working from home and walking their dogs more often
ehisoka: tomcr00se?
esence: dog in China. GULP
lsfa: How to get past coders block?
Newlax: @georgehotz If humans lost the ability to sneeze, how long would it take for us to realize?
dj_vicio: where you work?
vrooom_vroooooom: how did you meet kanye
KnollBoss: @georgehotz what fields do you see a big future in (like if you did computer science 20 years ago)
yevheniiushtyk: Ye PogChamp
happypuppppy: you met the lyrical genius of our generation PogChamp
Stegosaurian: Do you have enough food stockpiled in case your city gets put on lockdown?
cankunwang: Cat or dog?
ColdZer0o: @georgehotz what happened to your VR revolution
pistolpetepcp: Night, I gotta work also, but in the same place i am at now
sillybaboy: dono still not there hotz
ahahahaitslit: u listen to any podcasts?
magicallyphysically: Everyone just needs to clean up there act.
jmp0ut: deep space engineering is where it's at my guy
magicallyphysically: Easy clap.
ehisoka: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Yhyp-_hX2s
mik12f4: any family still in your hometown?
adamdavis1211: did you say computer science is the future. couldnt here
Crayonsss: how much bigger then the statistics do you think the virus is? and how long before the reported "first infected" in each country do you think the virus actually came? i had the flu 1 week before the craze and i just wonder.. what if
jmp0ut: money is a scam
mutrx: does size matter..asking for a friend
xPolarDreamz: India is the cause
buckkets_: Whats sectors do you think will go permanently remote because of this?
jmp0ut: humanity held hostage for charity
myaocat: money
DecayingSkullz: Do you miss NJ
almonte550: @georgehotz How long will it take until this coronavirus crisis pass away?
pwnbase: @georgehotz would you take funding from YC?
PiroFloydian: Money
Emmaralds: will u have fully self driving b4 tesla?
axlebear: What is your overall life philosophy
saeveritt: My mom's on tiktok
magicallyphysically: Well I ask you this @georgehotz How many lives have been lost to Cancer?
bufferovrflw: I kid you not, he turns himself into a pickle, he calls himself “Pickle Rick”, funniest shit I’ve ever seen
PiroFloydian: thats a pretty simple question
JakobJayJohnson: Would you work for SONY if they contact you?
yevheniiushtyk: neuralink when?
criiscarpenter: !uptime
jmp0ut: aaron shwartz died to those intellectual property racketeers
nikudino: 2.5
cromed56: !uptime
pjayys77: what movie are we headed to World War Z , I am Legend ?
Digital_donger: think we'll see humans on mars in our lifetime?
karnbirr: What drives your work ethic?
360Plato: people will realize college is just a rubber stamp?
hitmanhax: pork roll or taylor ham?
magicallyphysically: Hmm
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
dj_vicio: even a childs life?
jmp0ut: all the post secondary institutions just hold published IP's on a shelf and does not use it
magicallyphysically: I doubt Humanity.
samthedogg: starlink?
ipo___: Hey Gutz, hows progress?
Nussinov: one life is worth around 700 dollars isnt it
magicallyphysically: At this point in time.
ColdZer0o: level 5 autonomy or deep space travel
Emanuell45: @360Plato college is not a rubber stamp lol
nremind: thoughts on UBI?
Sniky83: https://foldingathome.org/about/
jmp0ut: like smart traffic lights, published in university, bought out by property trolls and 3M corporation and never used
666bingbong666: @georgehotz looking for SWE interns?
Newlax: u should start a company to cure corona
l1ght5p33d: we want AI folding on the GPU's
CompestLive: How tall are you?
saeveritt: Do you listen to lofi
8bitben: how much should the stimulus check be?
yevheniiushtyk: D:
Pin__top: D:
xPolarDreamz: People bought slaves for 1000s
5_betbluff: NJ represent
Emmaralds: whats your IQ?
Emanuell45: 150
Nussinov: traffic lights that can solve differntial equations
samthedogg: UBI will raise the cost of everything so $1000/mo is the new $0
Hawklite: how is a person being born now a negative value to society when it requires people being born now to keep society going?
tj_rl: Do you allow WFH ;) I'll apply
JakobJayJohnson: Do you watched Paris Hiltons porn?
dj_vicio: where do you work / WFH?
jmp0ut: waiting on consulproject to replace politicians
jmp0ut: archaic shit
saeveritt: Check out Will Smith's new lofi playlist on youtube. It actually slaps
Stegosaurian: If there is a socio-economic collapse and the internet is shut down. What will you do?
CompestLive: Do you know what hackfourms is?
360Plato: Is IoT bullshit buzzword or real field
lebop: what are your suggestions to learn things fast?
mutrx: traffic lights that you connect to via bluetooth
ghu90: sadly it depends on where it is born
CompestLive: Do you know what hackfourms is and if so have you been a member?
ipo___: Have u met zuckerberg?
tj_rl: 100% agree
dj_vicio: jewckenberg
sidthescikid: @georgehotz UBI is a scam, 3.2 trillion in spending
l1ght5p33d: wellfare has benefits but diminishing return
yevheniiushtyk: What are you looking forward to?
lebop: what are your suggestions to learn things fast like you do?
pedrovictortech: pizza with or without pineapples
williamjennings1: can you make autopilot hack the traffic lights to turn green and never have to have a stop light again
Jehhred: Have you met zoidberg, I mean, zuckerberg?
myaocat: can we make a model immune system of human body to make a potential vaccine?
mik12f4: What are your thoughts on limiting how many kids people have???
brownyyyylocks: why are there no women engineers at comma?
5_betbluff: you ever play poker?
CompestLive: Do you know what hackfourms is and if so have you been a member?
Pin__top: the zuck!
DecayingSkullz: have you met Elon
mutrx: @brownyyyylocks there are
pec_adillo: jeeze chat so many questions
lsfa: Who is the richest person you've met?
8bitben: when will Openpilot support volkswagen
zol0: @georgehotz which TTS voice does zuckerburg have when he talks?
AleexM: best book you ever read?
sidthescikid: @DecayingSkullz Yup.
Pin__top: he met elon, he was in contract with him
StevenTalking: !followage
jmp0ut: forget wage slave problems, look at the the depopulation problem of the western civilization, we literally need 14 wives with 3 babies each male just to keep up with the silver tsunami of dying pensioners to move the economy forward rolling
magicallyphysically: Instead of making Toilet Paper.. make more Money Maker
tj_rl: At least UBI gives the individual freedom to spend the money. As opposed to welfare programs that control and supervise the use of money
im_drew_: favorite movie?
Emanuell45: people are not having kids anyway
pogu: Isn't elon musk the most famous person lol? He has 3rd biggest following on twitter
pjayys77: have you met Hackerman
360Plato: IQ means test to have kids lul
KnollBoss: Pog
Stegosaurian: What TV shows are you watching?
imperiex: are you doing ok on toilet paper?
Michaeltth: lol
lsfa: Who is the richest person you've met?
Hawklite: how is a person being born now a negative value to society when it requires people being born now to keep society going?
KnollBoss: Geohot anti discrimination
Emanuell45: @pogu bulllshitt. no way
StevenTalking: what are you working on right now??????????????????? long time follower first time chatter uwu
AleexM: Pog
ipo___: This person is rich so im not gonna hire them
jmp0ut: like what kind of actuary says yes open a business in the u.s. where babies arent being born and the wealth is stuck in the funeral home
Emmaralds: any cool stories with rich/famous people?
brownyyyylocks: fine my dream job is biz dev at comma anyway
xPolarDreamz: Where is the end?
sidthescikid: I never said welfare is good, the poverty cycle removes the incentive for people to work if they take away benefits
lsfa: How did you meet Zucker?
Newlax: are you a myth?
PiroFloydian: sounds like eugenics!
Stegosaurian: What are your top 3 favorite books of all time?
jmp0ut: nuclear family = nuked family
saeveritt: Where's that MATH hat I saw on instagram
iKanak_: @georgehotz what keyb0ard key are you going to name your biotech startup after?
almonte550: @georgehotz If this coronavirus crisis goes on until end of this year, how is this affecting comma ai?
Iknowyou123456789: future of bitcoin? @georgehotz
pjayys77: are we living in a simulation
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz you back to regualr streaming? Pog
kubaaa6: At all the companies you did work for what one was ur favorite
JakobJayJohnson: Do you watched MR ROBOT?
lsfa: What did you do at Facebook?
Emanuell45: @Stegosaurian he doesnt read bro
DecayingSkullz: Do you think going to Mars would be productive
Iknowyou123456789: what is the future of bitcoin? @georgehotz
Nussinov: @georgehotz whats your favourite book
pwnbase: @georgehotz what did you think of the silicon valley finale
Emanuell45: @georgehotz favourite tv shows?
Maagicbr: what are u doing?
jmp0ut: in Canada our birth rate is going to 0.48 by 2050
Jehhred: You going to stream hackerrank soon??
jmp0ut: wtf is that
magicallyphysically: Mars is not an option o.o
5_betbluff: lol
astrailz: Which year do you think mankind will land on Mars? @georgehotz
Newlax: Why are you a part of my simulation?
8bitben: why did bitcoin go lower when stocks went lower too?
hitmanhax: PogChamp 100k
im_drew_: 100k confirmed
keith282: 100 thousand? its going to a million!
myaocat: i saw your video in youtube that you was in facebook hackathon..
Emmaralds: you worked on the facebook android launcher?
JakobJayJohnson: You chess elo ranking is?
dorkmo: oh I remember the facebook phone thing
5_betbluff: @8bitben cash is king in a recession
weedlord666: why should i care about anything at all
AzzoDio: do you watch Devs, great soundtrack
THX1342: thoughts on the fermi paradox?
l1ght5p33d: Cloud Llifee
ipo___: I already told 14 people that George hotz says it will go above 100k soon
lsfa: Best field of comp sci to get into right now?
keith282: @8bitben same reason, people liquidating assets
jmp0ut: how does the money move to less people expediently without turning everyone jibhead on stripper pole land
brownyyyylocks: 8bitben i have same question!!
williamjennings1: will you be having kids?
samthedogg: mathematically the stock-to-flow ratio (which BTC has followed with 99% accuracy) indicates a 98k bitcoin by December 2021
l1ght5p33d: we care because we want to
bob_babyelephant: what vim color scheme do you use
5_betbluff: You meant Bitcoin cash to 100k right?
tykabmo: @georgehotz Do you play Rocket League?
magicallyphysically: I'm working on my theory at the moment.
edu4594: yeah, what vim colorscheme do you use?
THX1342: yeah
magicallyphysically: Nearly complete
tj_rl: I second Rocket League :)
im_drew_: do you think that life is a simulation?
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
myaocat: what do you think about injecting chips to body?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz ever played league of legends?
8bitben: gold, btc, and stocks all went down together
jmp0ut: i wonder if martin schkreli is bankrolling cigarettes in jail rn
magicallyphysically: same here lol
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
AlexEDM: lol
magicallyphysically: I hate that game
Keyeh: changed github photo omg
Emmaralds: how smart do u think u are?
Ozonemaster: @georgehotz how do u have time to paly league
elon_musk__: LEAGUE OF OMEGALULS
FastCashCoding: yea bch for real
bufferovrflw: What are the qualities of a person you look for?
magicallyphysically: Injecting Nano-Chips?
YoungScootah: Shkreli is the man
Newlax: Why are you a part of my simulation?
Jehhred: You ever waste your time playing runescape?
l1ght5p33d: play with AI, gain all wins
xeroeffect: Do you still use 2 fingers to drive?
KnollBoss: @georgehotz is emailing you a good idea or is that business only
Pin__top: starred
C4TFive: all the windows on your screen give me anxiety
360Plato: low spatial high logic iq?'
jmp0ut: i learned inuktitut syllabics in 20 mins, small things to stop civilization destruction
5_betbluff: just got here, any short explanation on what you've done with corona?
jmp0ut: easier than english
Liz3DE: ever tried emacs?
KnollBoss: i will try not to
ipo___: George u rich??
KnollBoss: but i can not make any gaurantees
nurbscrv: @georgehotz TRUE or FALSE? 🍑💨🦠 COVID-19 is transmissible via flatulence. PLEASE EXPLAIN YOUR ANSWER.
magicallyphysically: Time Loop is almost at the end
magicallyphysically: :(
brownyyyylocks: how is comma10k used by segnets? i made 2 PRs!!
AlexEDM: starred
adamcernycz: Stars hype train! Kappa
yevheniiushtyk: Spaces or Tabs?
Michaeltth: D:
Pin__top: sstvMisc
myaocat: Would you drink a batsoup for million dollars?
nitcat: LOL
C4TFive: speak for yourself
Ne0Zer0: a github star isnt much, but its honest work SeemsGood
8bitben: PyCharm or VS Code
Nussinov: dump your COVID load in my mouth
l1ght5p33d: i need to see the p values
elon_musk__: TREW
Maagicbr: XD
brittonx2: hahahaha
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
jmp0ut: glycoproteins from fartbomber
almonte550: @georgehotz so farts are better than coughs?
YoungScootah: Do you drink energy drinks ?
keith282: @8bitben vim
pjayys77: great anatomical term, asshole
THX1342: that was too precise for a bio paper
saeveritt: How do you feel about golang
360Plato: aight imout
AlexEDM: ask and thee shall receive
Newlax: Why are you a part of my simulation?
lubold: how is the fermi paradox monte carlo paper called @georgehotz
bufferovrflw: CAN WE GET CORONA TRENDING ON GITHUB
GTozzi: The only reason I asked about private messaging you was because twitch a limited forum to talk about the intersection constitutional law and contemporary technology
8bitben: vim vs. nano
GTozzi: but I need ot update my website anyway
mutrx: what scares you the most? @georgehotz
myaocat: Would you drink a batsoup for 10 dollars?
solitarynative: nim?
Sky_Light_37: anal is the cure
djcows: Thoughts on WallStreetBets?
nitcat: LOL IQ OF 130
CompestLive: Have you heard of hackforums and have you used it before?
l1ght5p33d: i only read and write assembly
adamdavis1211: what is your iq george
Emanuell45: everyone has an iq of 130 lol
im_drew_: What is the possibility that life is a simulation?
8bitben: do you vape tho
xPolarDreamz: what is the iq to code in python
scarbromangler: would u rather get coronavirus or genital herpes in your lungs
DecayingSkullz: VScode vs VIM?
Keyeh: D:
samthedogg: @georgehotz are A.I trading bots legitty or shitty?
peter35_: same bro FeelsBadMan
Nussinov: xPolarDreamz 85
AlexEDM: love the profile picture on github
KnollBoss: as a kid which books did you read @georgehotz
yevheniiushtyk: Even tried CBD?
xeroeffect: Do you believe in magic?
666bingbong666: @georgehotz do you sponsor interns?
Couchmann941: how is your life going in general?
jmp0ut: know how i cured my stimulant needs for narcolepsy, training my dopamine receptors with noopept citicoline
lsfa: Most lucrative field of comp sci right now?
C4TFive: your github profile looks mean AF
THX1342: man the descriptions from the frontlines are scary af.... people neeeding to be tied up...
weedlord666: you know about joe exotic?
icanthitthose: do you need a high iq to be a good programmer
Liz3DE: ever tried emacs?
CompestLive: Have you smoked weed before
FoxMcWeezer: If you were rehired at Facebook, what level Software Engineer would you be?
Emanuell45: i mean everyone interested in computer science generally have an iq of 125 or higher
saeveritt: golang = small brain python = ?
CompestLive: Have you smoked weed before?
Krissam: Genital herpes in your lungs is the easy pick
C4TFive: sponsor sounds like out of country
mutrx: @Emanuell45 mine is well below 60
AlexEDM: LOL
jmp0ut: citicoline and noopept is the best stack for add/adhd issues that i've found
dorkmo: tiger kinggg
llIIIIIllIlII: damn he looks edgy in that picture
tj_rl: Would you rather discover aliens or the corona virus antidote?
jmp0ut: i went superhuman
xPolarDreamz: are u still hiring for comma?
AlexEDM: the fact that you remember Buck Angel
yevheniiushtyk: lmao
Emanuell45: @mutrx calling bullshit on that
THX1342: georgehotz have you hired anyone that switched careers into coding?
homestarr: lets go over t cell flow cytometry data :)
smarttties: it's the new Netflix show
localcanofdutchgold: @Emanuell45 doubt it
CompestLive: Have you smoked weed before? lmao
CompestLive: Have you smoked weed before?
KnollBoss: what books would you recommend reading @georgehotz
almonte550: @Emanuell45 125 in computer science is the new 100
lsfa: Most lucrative field of comp sci right now?
hordead: so did you crack the code?
pedrovictortech: @georgehotz Opinion on Serverless?
magicallyphysically: Kappa
magicallyphysically: Never smoked
Nussinov: Kappa
sidthescikid: Kappa
Keyeh: Kappa
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
barbadose: @emanuell45 true..l1
Emanuell45: @almonte550 trueeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
ahahahaitslit: nobody has read infinite jest
PiroFloydian: dont believe that for a second LUL
ipo___: insane, never smoked weed
Pin__top: those dank kush
saeveritt: Book: Holographic Universe
magicallyphysically: Sure Kappa
sk84uhlivin: The Last Question :D
jmp0ut: hourk
KnollBoss: David foster wallace
samthedogg: @georgehotz have you read 48 Laws of Power?
axlebear: Kappa
weedlord666: why does everyone care about your opinion on trivial things like your editor of choice
KnollBoss: ....
dorkmo: tiger king on netflix
jmp0ut: HURK
Pin__top: infinite jest is so long
8bitben: could you create a DIY ventilator
pwnbase: have you finished the will to power yet
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now??
tornpaperyoyos: @georgehotz favorite weed strain?
bufferovrflw: Thoughts on transgender people - thoughts on substituting hormones in their body?
zol0: @georgehotz is minikeyvalue reliable enough?
myaocat: Does Folding@Home doing integrity check or someone can send fake data to cause millions of death?
Nussinov: good thing you said those last two books otherwise i woulda thought you were mentally a high schooler Kappa
Pin__top: robert greene!
icanthitthose: whats your iq?
PiroFloydian: fav food?
THX1342: admirable new world
lovelyhashbrowns: What do you think of the Nim programming language
Pin__top: human nature was great
Emanuell45: https://thetab.com/us/2017/04/10/which-major-has-highest-iq-64811
mutrx: when can i marry my anime waifu in VR @georgehotz
AzzoDio: atlas shrugged so boring, but infinite jest is great
nic0latesla: please sing "It Was Called the Cold"
jmp0ut: actually only fiction worth reading is the hackers manifesto
l1ght5p33d: everyone needs to read MATHEMATICAL AND COMPUTATIONAL PHYSICS FOR ENGINEERS
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
gill_bates_macrosoft: have you tried to use emacs @georgehotz
gamozo: gamozo subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months! Heya
CompestLive: Do you have ADHD? lmaooo
jmp0ut: and maybe simulacra et simulation
xPolarDreamz: Thoughts on trump?
DarkEpopt: @jmp0ut how? :)
pwnbase: I swear Nietzsche founded RL with the will to power
brownyyyylocks: is mimetic desire stronger than reverse psychology?
jmp0ut: @DarkEpopt elaborate?
Liz3DE: i wanted to know more about the firefox 0day, but couldnt find anything useful
Iknowyou123456789: when is your IPO @georgehotz
FoxMcWeezer: If you were rehired at Facebook, what level Software Engineer would you be?
peter35_: clintSuave
Abnico: have you read Simulacra and Simulation?
Pin__top: the orange man
myaocat: Does Folding@Home doing integrity check or someone can send fake data to cause millions of death?
magicallyphysically: Trump is not fit for this situation.
Abnico: @georgehotz have u read Simulacra and Simulation
bufferovrflw: That's not an answer, lol
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
Nussinov: I nothing trump
CompestLive: Do you have ADHD? lmaooo
Pin__top: middle is the comfy zone
hitmanhax: haHAA
AlexEDM: that was a political answer to a political question
solitarynative: based centrist
fuddy12345: centrist KEKW
elektroids: fence rider
Abnico: the matrix is based on that
eaterenrgy: In the middle zentreCOMFY
ahahahaitslit: have you read anything by nassim taleb?
rndmsqnce: how do u date so many women
magicallyphysically: I would prefer not a jackass
jmp0ut: i noticed neo in the matrix holding simulacra years later was a whoa moment
magicallyphysically: :)
DarkEpopt: You said you helped your narcolepsy by dopamine training
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now??
axlebear: Favorite move?
scarbromangler: NIetzsche is post-modern
rstk1: favourite website?
l1ght5p33d: middle cloud
AlexEDM: how many women HAVE you dated?
Abnico: bri the matrix is based on it
samthedogg: Trump gets shit no matter what he does
AlexEDM: I must know :)
theonlymonkas: your eyes don't hurt with the white theme??
CompestLive: Do you have ADHD? lmaooo
solitarynative: have you tried nim-lang?
cankunwang: 35199 total cases in US
ahahahaitslit: black swan yeah
magicallyphysically: Whose the Black Swan!?!?
peter35_: yuval
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
dr_set: Harari
barestalk64: Favorite albums?
magicallyphysically: I keep bumping into the Black Swan everyday
magicallyphysically: Who are they?
l1ght5p33d: geohot has lain with many womens
PiroFloydian: bronze age mindset looks like some cryptofash stuff at first glance
yevheniiushtyk: @georgehotz your favorite movies?
AlexEDM: well.... been in a relationship with or 1 night stand? numbers? I'm a numbers guy
Emanuell45: lmao
myaocat: Why should i use folding@home if they will sell a vaccine for thousands of dollars? @georgehotz
THX1342: LUL
ahahahaitslit: lmfaoo
theonlymonkas: favorite albums?
williamjennings1: lololo
barestalk64: Thoughts on essays on pessimism?
jmp0ut: stims are garbage from doctors causing heart disease and dopamine problems
xPolarDreamz: have u ever coded in brainfuck?
jmp0ut: noopept is a lot cleaner
jmp0ut: same with citicoline
brownyyyylocks: mimetic desire stronger than reverse psych?
ak0ya_: Do you like to visit you parents?
seasamborn: seasamborn subscribed with Twitch Prime.
rstk1: favorite github project lately
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Where do you get most of your information/studies?
PiroFloydian: bernie's def not a communist but trump is pretty fashy in a lot of respects
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
Liz3DE: Have you ever tried emacs
williamjennings1: were you addicted to kratom?
cankunwang: Ideology makes ppl stupid
scarbromangler: How is Nietzsche not post-modern? The 'God is Dead' diatribe is basically a lament on the death of long-standing cultural assumptions and truths
nurbscrv: @georgehotz You neglected to toast your hamburger bun that one time. If you read postmodernism you would realize the irony of your condition.
almightykod: who is your favorite (most interesting) historical character?
hordead: George where is your college degree?
CompestLive: Let me get mod, I proivde great content in the chat kappa
Rovelo: 4Head just get some crystals if you're sick
yevheniiushtyk: github.com/trending
tj_rl: Pithy sayings make people stupid
pjayys77: can you even say there was ever a true communist country
saeveritt: youtube "Will Smith Lofi Playlist" and thank me later
ahahahaitslit: If you liked black swan by Taleb then check out antifragile, it's better
PiroFloydian: Nietzsche is more existential than post-modern
Anonymous835: Hi @georgehotz just joined how did you tackle the research ? Where did you start?
lsfa: The best field of comp sci to get into right now?
Newlax: SeemsGood
5cl0ck: sup, just got here, is this in the end? what happened to the DNA stuff?
myaocat: If you believe in science would you donate your body to science?
ar2zee: Do the apartment tour
jmp0ut: only reason they dont prescribe phenibut and noopept in the west is coz commies developed it yet as a stim noopept ameliorates myocardial infarction and transient ischemic attacks
peter35_: LUL
Rovelo: LUL
theonlymonkas: favorite song
Panda1Express: haha
karnbirr: Do you play video games?
Nussinov: LUL
FargioFarmani: I am really impressed by https://github.com/geohot/corona
CompestLive: Let me get mod, I provide great content in the chat kappa
nremind: you should switch to arch full time btw :P
magicallyphysically: OKAY DUDE
magicallyphysically: LOL
8bitben: why zsh?
AlexEDM: what's a typical in-office work week for you? how many hours? etc
cankunwang: When will you start stream tomorror
solitarynative: your mbti?
lsfa: Most exciting area right now in comp sci
pwnbase: com-mies is blocked by twitch as a hate word
l1ght5p33d: were livin right now bros
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Where do you find current studies/information?
magicallyphysically: Yes
ak0ya_: do you believe in marriage?
mutrx: are they all Will Smith songs?
Pin__top: looks like you got lots of new viewers after the break
KnollBoss: you're a cool guy, good night sir
yevheniiushtyk: How to not be a noob?
KnollBoss: sleep well
pogu: commies
samthedogg: @georgehotz who killed seth rich?
THX1342: what are options for a hacker do make money other than selling out cheap for bug bounties?
theonlymonkas: will you come back tomorrow?
naabee_: P????
theonlymonkas: favorite song
brownyyyylocks: same time tomoz
pogu: @pwnbase Jebaited
magicallyphysically: Thanks for doing this Stream @georgehotz very insightful and helpful LOL
Michaeltth: lmao
PiroFloydian: LUL
zol0: WTF
C4TFive: bel-air LUL
tj_rl: How many jumping jacks can you do?
magicallyphysically: And hilarious
VGBurnzy: lol
jmp0ut: @THX1342 peptide medicine, biohack yourself cheaper medications
ahahahaitslit: LOL
joivan: LMAO
mutrx: gib_money()
samthedogg: @georgehotz did you say Siraj?? the DIsgraced Ytber??
gamozo: Heh, kinda true
myaocat: How did human created?
PiroFloydian: sativa or indica @georgehotz
pwnbase: @pogu its blocked for me
gamozo: the world pours money into security right now, kinda silly
Nussinov: @georgehotz whats the longest you've ever stayed awake
ar2zee: how do you see development in 5 years ?
anotherkidnamedaustin: working during a global pandemic??
THX1342: I just wanted a rant over bug bounties LUL
tornpaperyoyos: There was siraj drama?
icanthitthose: @georgehotz can anyone be a good programmer?
frostism1: do you like Python 3?
r0xtehem0x: How do you stay motivated?
richfromoil: do you think that no alien civilization explores space because they invent sex bots first and stop trying?
l1ght5p33d: smol drama
treestompztv: BUY PUTS
pjayys77: bug bounties
sidthescikid: M OMEGALUL RGZ
pogu: @pwnbase "commie" completely works
magicallyphysically: LOL
C4TFive: this is cancer
xPolarDreamz: i lose brain cells when i watch morgz
tokumei64: dear god no please make it stop
Pin__top: oh gawd
julien9877: stop
CompestLive: What does dom backwords spell? Can I get it?
tornpaperyoyos: oh god i hate it
rgbeezus: 10k on a date lo
funwayz: @georgehotz do u still plan to drop streaming when it hits 1k?
Nussinov: FailFish
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on doing illegal things, like using stolen credit cards of the net
mutrx: it sounds like satire
CompestLive: What does dom backwords spell? Can I get it? LMAo
Digital_donger: NotLikeThis
Stegosaurian: Why don't you work from home?
magicallyphysically: This is a shit show
mutrx: but it legit
CompestLive: What does dom backwords spell? Can I get it?
hordead: What is the saraj drama?
lsfa: He's gonna cure COVID-19
KnollBoss: this guy has more money than I will ever have @georgehotz
theonlymonkas: nice
8bitben: pizza or pasta
KnollBoss: morgz
homestarr: open source immunology data on immport (made by northrop grumman)
theonlymonkas: favorite album
pjayys77: ehhhh
KnollBoss: please save me from my sins
magicallyphysically: I need some weed
anotherkidnamedaustin: date during global pandemic?
PiroFloydian: sativa or indica? or cbd?
5cl0ck: Way too many cooks
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on doing illegal things, like using stolen credit cards of the net...
Penguino138: Wont smoking weed make corona come get you?
tj_rl: What's your favorite question?
anotherkidnamedaustin: work during global pandemic?
edu4594: where do you work?
pjayys77: youtuber persona on full blast
jmp0ut: just to waste on a date wtf
magicallyphysically: I'm all out Herbal Weed
Liz3DE: ever tried emacs @georgehotz
magicallyphysically: :(
jmp0ut: while i struggle in my social housing unit all my life
mutrx: favorite adult swim skit?
CompestLive: If I find an exploit in comma website, can I get a job lmao
brownyyyylocks: @ 8bitben oh man pasta
homestarr: go to shared data
jmp0ut: the world must have a sick sense of humor :D
homestarr: theres a browser
0R4NG3: lol
CompestLive: If I find an exploit in comma.ai website, can I get a job lmao
mutrx: programming on a 10$ keyboard vs 10,0000$
THX1342: thoughts on phineas phisher?
xPolarDreamz: lol
FargioFarmani: My question: What century was the best to be alive in?
theonlymonkas: will you ever do a cooking streaming again?
Nussinov: you know these motherfuckers know data when they put a word cloud on their site
Iknowyou123456789: why do you use chromium instead of chrome @georgehotz ?
anotherkidnamedaustin: work during a global pandemic????
PiroFloydian: sativa or indica? or cbd? @georgehotz
Rovelo: Kreygasm holy pandas
jmp0ut: the 29th century was the best
mutrx: programming on a $10 keyboard vs $10,000 @georgehotz make it happen
lemonboxed: the best simulation science has achieved so far is animal crossing
tornpaperyoyos: Can I have a job?
magicallyphysically: @georgehotz Love that reference because both is kind of useless bag of dogshit and automobile
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on doing illegal things, like using stolen credit cards of the net...
C4TFive: why are you using a mac NotLikeThis
8bitben: smarthome vs. dumbhome
yevheniiushtyk: We got corona in this century doe
lsfa: Is it worth getting into the field of hacking in 2020 or is it too saturated/over?
jmp0ut: from all of my time travelling days
jmp0ut: the 29th century was decent
theonlymonkas: can we get comma ai on Guatemala
tykabmo: @georgehotz what do you think of hackthebox?
anotherkidnamedaustin: weed is lit
Penguino138: @georgehotz You're smoking even with the threat of corona?
xkasper7: this guy doesn't even know what html is i bet
l1ght5p33d: actual leet hacking >> security
anotherkidnamedaustin: when u dont need to focus
lsfa: iIs it worth getting into the field of hacking in 2020 or is it too saturated/over?
TimoPuukka: !uptime
ghu90: clone humans?
naabee_: Kappa
firmstool: What's your beef with Google?
anotherkidnamedaustin: work during global pandemic?!
mutrx: how funny is rick and morty? the pickle part killed me LUL
yevheniiushtyk: Bud vaporizers are great
brownyyyylocks: 100 years we'd be picking cotton on his cotton farm glad its 2020
Penguino138: @georgehotz You're smoking even with the threat of SARS? lolol
myaocat: why is php still used?
sidthescikid: LUL Me 6 years ago
roystang: whats sad about gogle
nurbscrv: @georgehotz Please explain what a closure would be in the context of Lombardy.
jmp0ut: buy your octopamine from amazon, mainline the spider octopus adrenaline juices bruuuu
Stegosaurian: Why don't you work from home?
xPolarDreamz: inspect element hack
samthedogg: @georgehotz you every play around with Pixhawks?
theonlymonkas: favorite albums
lsfa: iIs it worth getting into the field of hacking in 2020 or is it too saturated/over?
Pin__top: have you stocked up on supplies
CompestLive: cout << "Give mod" << endl;
8bitben: wordpress
ar2zee: Can you recommend to aderall as a performance booster ?
icanthitthose: @georgehotz how often do you read?
HexaField: are you familiar with Eric Weinstein and his podcast? quite interesting discussions
Rovelo: 😂 👌 🔥 pickle riiiick
Lana_Lux: how many stars on github do you need to be truly happy?
yevheniiushtyk: favorite food?
anotherkidnamedaustin: indica = in da couch
jmp0ut: @ar2zee i recommend noopept citicoline instead
PocketsKing: @georgehotz how much IQ i need to have to learn coding ?
anotherkidnamedaustin: sativa for life
sidthescikid: Italy is fucked change my mind
naabee_: Kappa
mutrx: @PocketsKing 0 can confirm
PiroFloydian: TRUE
ak0ya_: do you believe in free will?
saixj: so your compnay does not drug test
ahahahaitslit: please go on the portal
samthedogg: @georgehotz Were you going to AUVSI this year?
Penguino138: @georgehotz When do you realistically expect Corona to be under control?
THX1342: life is suffering
8bitben: pip or pip3
THX1342: LUL
Lamppostic: 90
pjayys77: when are you gonna debate Destiny
pec_adillo: 10 iq
scofflerr: Like Naval Ravikant?
theonlymonkas: do you have a podcast? or a favorite one?
C4TFive: like 17 iq at least
KnollBoss: this thx guy seems smart
5cl0ck: thinking you're better might be what kicks your ass outta bed
KnollBoss: mod him
brownyyyylocks: weinstein is thiel's man at his firm
ColdZer0o: @georgehotz do you still believe we're in a simulation
CompestLive: cout << "Give mod" << endl;
yevheniiushtyk: start that shit github.com/geohot/corona
solitarynative: 60iq masterrace
happypuppppy: 10000 github stars = nirvana
Rovelo: PogChamp
anotherkidnamedaustin: eric weinstein is lit
PiroFloydian: oh it is
Rovelo: destroy destiny PogChamp
Lana_Lux: @happypuppppy :)
AresRai: it is toxic
FargioFarmani: Are you afraid of dying? @georgehotz
iamquote: Thoughts on open science?
myaocat: Do you think Snowden is a russian spy?
xkasper7: you and him actually look like brothers
raystriker98: thoughts on lex fridman
tj_rl: I would really recommend Eric Weinstein's podcast. Especially episode #019
PiroFloydian: debate vaush! LUL
l1ght5p33d: I like being in the simulation it makes me happy
pjayys77: I needa be there for that
dpolar: Destiny? Sounds like a stripper
Penguino138: @georgehotz how long could you survive with only the food in ur house?
anotherkidnamedaustin: el ron hubbard theory
xeroeffect: Do u want kids?
5cl0ck: WTF IS THIS, HOTZ DRIVE THROUGH??
C4TFive: dont talk to destiny hes a loser
ahahahaitslit: I also recommend Weinstein's podcast
jmp0ut: i am in a dream theatre held hostage to optogenomics who tried subversion therapy on me
theonlymonkas: when you are going to play minecraft again?
samthedogg: @georgehotz starting a religion is in 48 laws of power. i think you did read it lol
mutrx: chicken tenders for dayyys
ahahahaitslit: George would be a good guest
jmp0ut: it was a nightmare simulator to begin with
DSykes_: do dmt
Digital_donger: favorite database software?
jmp0ut: when i was 8 yrs old
jmp0ut: pretty messed up
raystriker98: thoughts on Lex Fridman
nurbscrv: What’s your favorite yoga pose? Prove it.
treestompztv: Simulation doesn’t have virus protection 4Head
tj_rl: Smoke on stream?
Nussinov: I haven't bought groceries in 2 months
CompestLive: cout << "Give mod" << endl;
xPolarDreamz: @georgehotz your readme doesnt have the md file extension
djcows: Tendiees
l1ght5p33d: Kids are work the whole point is to get less of it
DSykes_: do DMT
8bitben: you gotta go to the grocery!!
solitarynative: when will you start your own crypto-nation?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz are you worried about getting old?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz are you worried about getting old?.
happypuppppy: did he say chad pose?
jmp0ut: optogenomics games are not meant to be torture chambers for children
Emanuell45: @georgehotz are you worried about getting old?..
firmstool: Imagine this guy bouncing some of his smoothbrain, ill-informed takes off of destiny. Hilarious
theonlymonkas: favorite album
Iknowyou123456789: house tour please @georgehotz
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Is there going to be a Q&A tomorrow?
CompestLive: Who is that behind you????
mik12f4: you ever fall asleep doing a webcast?
anotherkidnamedaustin: SARS just means BUY STOCK
tykabmo: @georgehotz Cobol or Fortran?
Penguino138: @georgehotz What time u planning to stream tomorrow?
archer723: house tour please 1
Juankinator: anything you watched that u recommend? (tv series/movies)
DSykes_: @georgehotz do DMT on stream
CompestLive: Who is that behind you?????
anotherkidnamedaustin: !streambot
Kingxpecc: how long are you going to stream for
Nussinov: @georgehotz can you answer this question? called the portal question: https://embed.gyazo.com/611a66d1dfd1dc187ab289c302b6bba9.png
5cl0ck: are you stoned?
jmp0ut: star trek picard is decent rn
ahahahaitslit: have you seen westworld
julen9601: What is he doiong guys?
8bitben: can you build livestream into openpilot
saeveritt: star trek OP
magicallyphysically: I loved Star Wars
Iknowyou123456789: what car do you drive @georgehotz ?
magicallyphysically: Star Wars best tier
GTozzi: Pecard is good af
THX1342: advice on controlling ADD when you have multiple interests?
l1ght5p33d: Deep Space 9 is best Star Trek
zol0: whose that in front of you monkaS
DecayingSkullz: have you read Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy
jmp0ut: star bores is so boring now
Penguino138: @georgehotz when dogecoin moon?
MorningScifi: Some favorite books?
Digital_donger: @Nussinov good question LUL
myaocat: what do you think of black mirror tv show?
williamjennings1: HeyGuys HeyGuys
ghu90: they cloned Dolly 25 yrs ago, how have they not cloned humans yet?
naabee_: LUL
Nussinov: @Digital_donger LUL
THX1342: LUL
magicallyphysically: Dont believe ANYTHING
magicallyphysically: PogChamp
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz time to buy stocks again
theonlymonkas: favorite netflix show
xeroeffect: What fitness activities do u like?
magicallyphysically: World is a lie
un3okapi: How many times do you masturbate a week
yevheniiushtyk: why is android shit
pogu: @magicallyphysically Pog
tj_rl: China did
zol0: LUL
xkasper7: do something with kubernetes raspberry pi clusters!
kuzan8: @georgehotz any books to read?
magicallyphysically: @pogu LuL
firmstool: Main monitor dimensions/resolution?
jmp0ut: they dont do functional magnetic resonance spectroscopy to verify brain medicine yet change the chemistry though the tech is 30 yrs old
icanthitthose: Elon called, he wants his bong back
mutrx: @georgehotz rate my apartment https://imgur.com/a/WNZIM8t
magicallyphysically: Dude I loved that show same here
C4TFive: shithawks everywhere
HexaField: why do my knees hurt? /s these questions are shit chat come on lets up the intellectual bar
djcows: How do you make sure you don't think too much "outside the box" and become delusional, but still stay innovative
ToxicVulpes: when u gonna make a westworld
almonte550: Do you have a TV at home?
0R4NG3: LOOOL
magicallyphysically: SHITHAWKS ARE A COMING BUBS
Nussinov: LUL
MorningScifi: ... I can't rewind WutFace
vrooom_vroooooom: that was on redditr
grey_street: LUL
bubblesnot: safest mobile app to store documents on with a transparent encryption scheme?
AlexEDM: lmao
Michaeltth: LUL
Emanuell45: lmaoooooooo
djcows: LUL
Emanuell45: LUL
C4TFive: convenient AF
magicallyphysically: CORONAHAWKS are coming
esence: he's a minimalist bro
naabee_: efficient
THX1342: how can you profit off of the suffering of the world like this? disgusting
ahahahaitslit: nice
Pin__top: ahahah
Nussinov: efficient as fuck
jmp0ut: why does my life hurt, i think multiple sclerosis
Rovelo: EFFICIENT LUL
PiroFloydian: gross
happypuppppy: LUL
gamozo: Can prep food while shitting
bloodandsteel: LUL
anotherkidnamedaustin: efficient
okoll: jaja
ehisoka: ROFL
solitarynative: minimalism Pog
xeroeffect: What was your favorite toy as a child?
ehisoka: I NEED THAT
sidthescikid: Cook next to where you shit
C4TFive: dont even need the sink, just wash them in the tub
ahahahaitslit: westworld?
0R4NG3: haha
treestompztv: $3k/mo SF
mehdi_tw: what's the plans for the quarentine ?
nurbscrv: Describe New Jersey from the perspective of a tomato
anotherkidnamedaustin: imagine having a girl over
Emanuell45: this guy never heard of "Dont shit where you eat"
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Psycarlo: Summer or Winter?
jmp0ut: :D
xkasper7: have you ever worked with kubernetes
DecayingSkullz: When will we see the cooking stream
Nussinov: @gamozo the twitch chat way
samthedogg: @georgehotz were you going to AUVSI this year?
DarkEpopt: @georgehotz who are you boring for and why is it Trump?
Miestensauna: rate alphafold?
djcows: Favorite type of mask?
anotherkidnamedaustin: quarantine for SARS ?!
r0xtehem0x: What keeps you motivated/focused?
naabee_: @Emanuell45 LUL
Rovelo: coronavirus started in that apartment LUL
justinlinw: Are you working on CommaAI stuff during quarantine?
l1ght5p33d: Its not in exact same spot
jcowley00: Just out of curiosity but do you think you are at your peak for retaining and using the information at your fingertips or is that something you try to improve on
gamozo: What should I fuzz on stream?
Psycarlo: @georgehotz Summer or Winter?
solitarynative: clone harambe for us
bubblesnot: @georgehotz safest mobile app to store documents on with a transparent encryption scheme?
yevheniiushtyk: How much hours of sleep do you try to get?
theonlymonkas: 1M on instagram
karnbirr: What drives your work ethic?
dadadududede: dadadududede subscribed with Twitch Prime.
mutrx: it all started with harambe
Emanuell45: @Rovelo lmaooooooooooooooo
peter35_: hottest actress
8bitben: do you ever drink
theonlymonkas: do you like your job?
zol0: have you ever used tokyocabinent?
tykabmo: is 42 the answer to the universe ?
mehdi_tw: de you think computer science will help against coronavirus ?
DecayingSkullz: Harambe died for our sins
jmp0ut: hottest actress, none of them they're all boring as fuck and their jobs are trash
tornpaperyoyos: Is the coronavirus a punishment for killing harambe?
xeroeffect: What’s your greatest fear?
nikudino: "drink" a bud light
Penguino138: @georgehotz u and alex still dating?
l1ght5p33d: desire to be ultra leet
anotherkidnamedaustin: alcohol is worse than SARS
bloodandsteel: do you like whiskey?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz what music do you listen to?
mutrx: Kate Upton
magicallyphysically: HELL YEA SAME @georgehotz
zol0: Kreygasm
ahahahaitslit: fax
yevheniiushtyk: Ever been in Europe?
ghu90: goodnight, wash ur hands
mickjaggerrrr: do you know him? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mPbtR4vorgY
logi6000: Yo we back I love when he just talks to chat
Psycarlo: Summer or Winter?
Nussinov: I'm a fan of anya taylor-joy
MorningScifi: Planning on doing any music collabs with Elon Musk
cankunwang: good night everyone
t0rment1337: change 1m2019.com to 1m2020.com @georgehotz
Rovelo: PogChamp 2016 memes
thezedzed: bonjour
Penguino138: @georgehotz favourite type of wine?
xkasper7: are you a fan of sam Harris
samthedogg: How was the GOT ending? was bran useful?
anotherkidnamedaustin: when is the next album?
jmp0ut: alcohol is crap, better to do ketamine in dimethylsulfoxide
nikudino: my landlord thinks that 5g caused corona fml'
saeveritt: How many times do you eat through out the day
tj_rl: Go to Italy, I hear it's lovely rn
mehdi_tw: favorite nba team
xeroeffect: Do you live in the cloud?
jmp0ut: it rubs the ketamine on the skin
logi6000: George are you just trying to find cure so you can fuck that pornstar
Penguino138: @georgehotz you like NDT Cosmos series?
williamjennings1: ghb is a good alternative for alcohol lol
programmer42: Your favorite programming langauge?
magicallyphysically: Time to cast Rezz on Jesus PogChamp
themorph3: which keyb-oard are you using ?
magicallyphysically: AngelThump
nic0latesla: cofee or energy drink?
gamozo: Cya
DecayingSkullz: gn
Ne0Zer0: LUL
l1ght5p33d: talking is overrated we need python politics
esence: cya
logi6000: no
Emanuell45: later
ak0ya_: bb
THX1342: LU:
bloodandsteel: bye
Nussinov: LUL
Pin__top: good night
Ne0Zer0: o/
ak0ya_: thank you
AresRai: gn
FargioFarmani: F
THX1342: bye
theonlymonkas: favorite tea brand?
buckkets_: bye daddy
jmp0ut: lmao thanks for streaming
pjayys77: lol
tj_rl: Peace :)
1ntegral_: GN
IaMvAzU: late
vrooom_vroooooom: bye
sidthescikid: bye dude
samthedogg: F
HexaField: cya georgie
Digital_donger: LUL
0R4NG3: bye
Juankinator: thanks dude
Michaeltth: 🛌🏻
pwnbase: See you tomorrow!
sidthescikid: take care
dorkmo: HeyGuys1
speeddrawing101: lster
xkasper7: later
djcows: bay
eaterenrgy: thanks!
gill_bates_macrosoft: goodnight geo
ColdZer0o: goodnight
CompestLive: Nice see you
williamjennings1: later
yevheniiushtyk: BYE O/
tj_rl: later bois
magicallyphysically: Later dude
CompestLive: Give mod lol
pogu: gn
theonlymonkas: later
logi6000: Goodnight
julen9601: be safe with corona
magicallyphysically: Time Loop is happening WutFace
gamozo: Jebaited
treestompztv: Bye
magicallyphysically: Help
myaocat: Haha2020